Chapter 1192: A Wind Chaser

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Neutron sources, which could be classified as catalyst, provided extra neutrons that could sustain the chain reaction even when Uranium-235 was under its critical mass.

Technically, both polonium and radium separated from natural uranium could form compounds with beryllium to serve as neutron sources. Roland did not foresee any technical difficulties, for polonium could release a large number of neutrons when colliding with alpha particles. All of the three elements were existing in nature, which saved them a lot of time to create elements artificially.

Roland preferred polonium to radium purely out of safety concerns. Although polonium-210 had a short half-life, it released very few photons upon a decay, which meant it was no more dangerous than inactive uranium. However, radium, which released radon and photons upon activation, posed a potential safety hazard. As such, polonium was a better candidate to provide neutrons.

Further, beryllium could reflect neutrons and further increased the possibility for neutrons to interact with other elements. By combining polonium and beryllium, along with a sufficient amount of uranium-235, even the simplest gun model could be lethal.

In addition to that, beryllium was a common element in emeralds that were quite accessible in the Four Kingdoms, so Azima did not have to search for them in the wilderness.

Roland knew very well about Neverwinter's current level of techonology. The principle of the Resplendent Radiation was simple, but to signicantly improve the utilization rate of energy from 1% to 90%, it required tons of theoretical calculations and numerous tests. If the conversion rate was low, he would not be able to reduce the size of the weapons and would thus waste precious uranium resources. Fortunately, Lucia's ability minimized the loss arising from the uranium extraction.

Nevertheless, even with a minimal loss, creating a nuclear weapon from scratch still involved various advanced technologies. Nuclear weapons' destructive power was phenomenal compared to regular explosives. Even 1% of uranium could release unparalleled energy.

Roland had to make every effort to win this battle that would decide the fate of the mankind.

To held the power of the Sun in your palms in this uncivilized era, wasn't it a type of romance?

He would like to give it a shot no matter how impossible it seemed.

"Very well, keep up the good work," Roland said as he patted Lucia on the head. "Once all the cabinets are filled with lead boxes, we can start on the tests."

"Yes, Your Majesty," Lucia said fervently.

*******************

In the meantime, in the Aerial Knight Academy of Neverwinter.

The area to the west of the research institute was quite today, for all the students were on a break visiting their families, except for Good.

"Upwind, gear down!"

"Crosswind, roll over!"

Good seated himself in front of the mock flight deck, practicing according to the instructions in the Flight Manual by changing the setting of the wind directions. The wooden rod creaked like a battered, weathered watermill. The air in the training room was sultry and balmy. His back was dampened with perspiration, and sweat dripped down his chin on the shabby deck.

Gradually, his hand became so wet that he could not keep a tight grip on the lever. Good thus stopped and heaved a deep sigh.

After learning to fly for almost half a year, Good had engraved the basic instructions in the Flight Manual written by Princess Tilly in his memories. He was no longer that lay man who got easily flustered by the movements of the plane. Now, Good had memorized all the instructions and developed quick reflexes. His body would react almost automatically to his mind.

But Good doubted if he could really fly a plane.

He could not envision the picture where he actually maneuvered a plane against the wind by himself. The Manual suggested that he should "feel the wind force and wind direction, sense the movement of the aircraft and operate the plane accordingly". However, he did not understand what kind of feeling that was. The mock flight deck remained motionless all the same no matter how he shifted the gear, as though it were laughing at his futile attempts with an air of derision.

The more Good practiced, the more frustrated he became.

While he was feeling extremely discouraged, the door of the training room was suddenly flung open.

"Oho, you're really here."

"Told you. I was right, wasn't I?"

Good looked around, and very surprisingly, saw two men step into the room, who were none other than his team members, Finkin and Hinds.

"Not having fun during your break?" Finkin whistled. "Well, that's because fun is right here in the school."

"Why are you still here. You have a sister, don't you?" Hinds rejoined as he flung his arm around Good's neck. "She asked me to tell you that you should take a good rest. That's... so sweet of her."

Good's manner tightened. He asked sternly, "Hold on, did you guys visit my place?"

"Of course, otherwise where should we go find you?" Finkin said matter-of-factly, his brows raised. "Her name is Rachel, right? Do you mind introducing her to me?"

"Out of the question," Good retorted fiercely while shooting Finkin a cold glance.

"Aren't we good enough?" Finkin said indignantly. "I have a proper house near Redwater River!"

Good lapsed into a thoughtful silence and then shook his head. "No, it has nothing to do with you. My sister... Rachel has her own problem. I don't think she would like to be with you."

"Why? I think she's sweet," Hinds asked in confusion.

"Come. Spit it out," Finkin urged in curiosity.

"Drop it," Good replied gruffly. "Let's talk about something else. What did you mean by "fun is here in the school?"

Finkin did not insist but lowered his voice and replied fugitively, "Do you want to fly a real plane?"

Astonished, Good said, "What did you say?"

"I saw it a few days ago when I climbed over the wall," Finkin said with a triumphant smile. "There are new planes in the hangar. Although they're covered with canvas, I could see they're about the same size of the 'Unicorn' piloted by Princess Tilly. In other words, those are our planes!"

"A few days ago? Why didn't you tell us back then?"

"Because I don't want you to be too excited and blabber about it," Finkin said while shrugging. "We're on a break, so few people are in the academy. That gives us a great chance to have a peek at them!"

"Are you mental?" Good said in disbelief. "Without permission, nobody is allowed to get in there!"

"Surely those soldiers won't let you in," Finkin said while rolling his eyes at Good. "So we must take another route and go around the airport."

"But..."

"We're just taking a look," Hinds egged on. "You should have noticed that Princess Tilly looks sulky recently and is more strict with us. So it would probably be another two months before we could actually fly them. Don't you want to know what our planes look like, or you actually prefer this stupid wooden deck?"

"If you don't come with us, we'll go without you," Finkin said as he winked at Good.

Good stared at the rickety wooden rod while savoring the sense of loss that lingered upon his heart. After what seemed to be a long internal struggle, Good bit his lip and agreed with a nod, "Alright. I'll come. Show me the way."

Chapter 1193: A Wind Chaser (II)

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The academy was empty just as Finkin had said. The three thus passed through various buildings and stopped in front of a towering wall.

"This is..."

"This is the west side of the airport," Finkin said as he brought a wooden ladder and erect it against the wall. "Follow me."

Good hesitated for a moment before he climbed up the ladder. The moment he reached the top of the wall, an involuntary exclamation escaped from his lips. A swollen red sun was sinking low over the water. The glittery ocean splintered into flecks of gold in the sweltering sunset, and the sky was awash with sheets of blue and yellow. Layers of cloud sloped down to the horizon, below which was the vast emptiness of the airport that would potentially lead them to the sky.

Sea breezes dispelled the irritation that smote upon Good's heart. He closed his eyes and, with his arms stretched, imagined himself clasping on the operation lever while waiting to take off.

"A very nice view, eh?" Finkin said while grinning. "I found this fabulous peeping spot. Just be careful not to fall off the wall."

Hinds asked behind them, "So... what next?"

"Naturally we should go there, but we have to take the ladder with us." Finkin said as he pointed at the hangar not far away. They first saw the "Seagull" parked out there. The hangar was actually not very far from them as its edge was only about two meters away from the wall.

Because of the intense balance training they had received, they could now easily walk along the top of the wall, and reached their destination within fifteen minutes.

The hangar was two to three meters taller than the wall, so they could not clamber onto the roof. However, its windows and the wall were on the same level, so they could peep through the windowpanes while stretching themselves up on their tiptoes.

"Covered planes... covered planes... I saw them!" Finkin yelled.

Good's eyes followed Finkin's, and his chest constricted.

There were four uncovered biplanes in one of the hangars. Good's eyes were glued to their smooth and elegant bodies. His heart swelled with excitement as the knowledge that he would one day operate them struck him.

Who cared about knights? They were nothing next to an aerial knight who could fly in the sky!

Finkin placed the ladder against the window and clapped his hands smugly. "Well, we didn't step into the airport, so technically, we aren't breaking the rules."

Good knew that was a pretty tenuous argument, but he could not help crawling into the hangar through the window.

To his surprise, for the first time since his training, Good felt calm.

After they landed, Finkin and Hinds rushed to the closest plane while Good sauntered behind them.

"Whoa, this is... spectacular!" Hinds apostrophized as he touched the plane. "It's metal."

"Yes, and it's as thin as skin. Look — " Finkin agreed as he pressed his fingers on it, and a dent immediately appeared on the surface. "I wonder how they made it."

"Oi, take it easy. You don't want to break it."

"Don't worry. It's quite bouncy."

"Really? Let me try..."

Good did not marvel at the plane like his two friends. Instead, he crawled into it as if led by a mysterious force and proceeded to the front of the aircraft.

According to the illustration on the cover of the Flight Manual, this was the exact spot Princess Tilly was sitting at while soaring above the continent and the sea.

Good thus sat in the pilot seat.

So this was the world in an aerial knight's eyes.

The wings above and the carriage on both sides obscured half of his vision, which forced Good to look straight ahead. He could even smell the leather chair. The flight instruments were encased in clear glass. Both the operation lever and the pedals were made of metal, the top part of the lever was wrapped in soft fabrics that afforded a nice, comfortable touch.

Good grabbed the lever and geared down. The lever creaked.

Unlike the wooden lever he had been practicing with, Good did feel he was pulling something. The quivering steel string and the increasingly heavy lever told him that the sensation was real.

"Good Lord, what are you doing?" Hinds' voice cracked through the air like a whip that jerked Good out of his musings.

"Er..." Good stammered and instantly relinquishing his grip. "I'm just..."

"Practicing?" Finkin jeered. "Who said we were mental earlier? Now who has sneaked into the cockpit? Didn't we agree to just take a look?"

"Sorry, I couldn't help..."

"Rest assured," Finkin interrupted. "I don't think you'll break it because we're told to do so during the training. But be fast. I want to try it out too."

"Hang on," Good said, a little reluctant. "I just geared down. Do you want to sit in the backseat first?"

"And what about me?" Hinds protested as he climbed up the wing.

While they were fighting for the seat, there was suddenly a screech of an open lock.

Good's face turned white with great trepidation.

Terrified, Hinds said, "Why... why would they come here at this time?"

"What should we do?"

Finkin was the only one who seemed to be composed. He said, "We don't have time to run. Hide first!"

However, there was not a single hiding place in the large hangar, and the pilot seat was too small for three grown-up men. Before they could get off the plane, someone had already arrived.

"Who's there?"

"Freeze!"

With several clicks, Good found himself surrounded by the First Army.

Petrified, the three were soon pinned to the ground.

"What happened?" a voice came as they saw a familiar figure approach them. It was none other than Princess Tilly Wimbledon. "Invaders?"

Finkin shouted in exasperation before the guards could supply an answer, "Your Highness, we're sorry. We are all students at the Aerial Knight Academy. Out of curiosity, we came here to have a look at the planes. Please have mercy on us!"

Apparently, Finkin also knew that they were not supposed to be here. Good had a feeling that they were in big trouble.

After hearing the full account, Princess Tilly nodded expressionlessly and said, "I see. According to the school rules, you'll all receive detention of at least 15 days and be disqualified from becoming an aerial knight. You can choose what you want to be in the future between a busboy and ground staff. Let your officer know."

"As, as you command..." Finkin and Hinds replied while screwing up their faces.

Good's heart sank to the bottom. Suddenly, courage seared through him as the guards began to shuffle them out. He raised his head and shouted in earnest, "Your Highness, please! I want to be a pilot. I would do anything if you could spare me this time! I'm at a loss in the training sessions, so I came here to feel the actual thing, not only out of curiosity!"

"Really?" Tilly said, her brows raised. "Are you referring to... a feeling?"

"Yes, my actions didn't coordinate with the instructions in the manual. Although I was flying, I couldn't sense the wind... Well, that isn't quite accurate. It's something..." Good explained as he tried to find a proper word to describe his feeling. "I can't put it into words. I only know that I didn't feel it right..."

"He's blabbering. It's all nonsense."

"Is this guy crazy?"

"Get him out of here. He annoys Princess Tilly."

The guards conversed with each other.

Tilly took a searching look at Good and said, "You're Good, right? Eagle Face told me that you're doing pretty well in all subjects. You were the first to get used to the training and are also very hard-working."

"I..."

Tilly cut across him haughtily, "So what do you think of riding on a plane?"

"Huh?" Good said, flabberghasted.

"Didn't you say you needed to feel it? So what now? Do you think you could fly?"

Good hesitated for a second, his hands clenched, and replied, "Your Highness... I think I can."

"Then try it out," Tilly said as she turned around without looking at him. "In fact, I'm planning to train you guys on a real plane tomorrow. For other students, they're allowed to fail but you aren't. If you fail, I'll expel you. Of course, you could also choose to be punished. That's up to you."

"I want to fly," Good replied decidedly.

"Very well," Tilly said. "I'll also let the other two choose what way they want to go."

Chapter 1194: The Only Request

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

After dinner, Tilly told Roland what had happened at the airport.

"Because of... a feeling?" Roland said, a little surprised at the reason Tilly had changed her mind.

"What? Not a good reason for you?" Tilly said while folding her arms.

"Well, you made all the school rules for the Aerial Knight Academy, so you're the boss," Roland denied while waving his hand. "I'm just curious about what that feeling refers to."

"It means talent. You really don't know anything about flying," Tilly said while shrugging. "For ordinary people, they simply follow the instructions in the manual mechanically, but some people could visualize their action. These people could foresee the result of their actions beforehand."

"Er... that sounds really amazing," Roland commented indifferently while twitching his lips. He admitted that he had no knowledge of flying. If it was not for Tilly, he would probably never be able to train so many aerial knights. Tilly helped him a lot to build, test, improve, and finalize the plane and train new pilots. Normally, it would take a few decades to build an actual plane based on the blueprints collected from the Dream World and apply it to militeray operations. Having said that, a plane was essentially a machine. Wouldn't it be enough to follow the instructions and keep practicing if someone wanted to learn how to operate it?

"Because I have that talent too," Tilly said regretfully. "The fact that you can't visualize it means that you don't have the talent. If you were a student of the Aerial Knight Academy, you would probably be knocked out of the school, brother."

"Ahem..." Roland almost choked as he heard Nightingale stifle her laugh behind him.

"Are you under the impression that we could be pilots as long as we practice?" Tilly said as though seeing the thought in Roland's mind. "It's true that some people could develop reflexes after numerous practices, but being able to feel is also a talent, although it's not as fast as the former method. Most people probably would never develop such an ability. Flying would be the most they could achieve. Between the two, who do you think will have a higher chance of surviving a battle?"

Roland fell silent.

Without a doubt, the gifted ones would have a better chance. They normally learned much faster than ordinary people, as they possessed the ability to learn from their experience. However, common people could barely survive. In other words, it took talented students less time to learn and absorb new knowledge.

"But that's not always the case," Roland said after a short pause. "Maybe he was just lucky and happened to have the right answer."

"So that was why I asked him to fly," Tilly said casually.

"... What about the other two?"

"They chose to fly too."

"Really?' Roland said while blinking in surprise. "I'm impressed with their bravery. Don't you think it's a pity to expel them?" Being expelled from school was a severe punishment, especially when this particular school was managed by the princess. This meant the expelled students would have a record, and it would be a lot harder for them to seek other employment in the future. Busboys and ground staff were actually paid well, and they were relatively stable jobs. The academy also offered them medical and housing benefits.

There were less than 200 pilot trainees in Neverwinter, so Roland cherished every one of them.

"The Aerial Knight Academy doesn't need untalented students. Bravery would only lead them to an early death. It's better for them to leave now than later," Tilly said in a low voice.

There was a strained silence. Roland got two drinks for both of them, and Tilly changed the subject. "By the way, I came here for my new plane. Any update on that?"

Roland's heart skipped a beat. He knew Tilly must have some important business to discuss. "I think we should take this matter slow. We need you to build the air force. You'll pose a greater threat to the demons if you stay in Neverwinter — "

Tilly did not respond but her eyes were glistening with inflexible determination.

Roland breathed out a deep sigh.

Tilly was not referring to the "Unicorn" but a more powerful military aircraft. After Tilly had cried hysterically in his chest like a defenseless child that night over Ashes' death, she had told Roland the next morning that she wanted a plane that could kill the demons.

She was going to seek revenge.

Apparently, Roland's evasive promise had not changed Tilly's mind.

"Are you sure that's what you want?"

"You weren't so indecisive when you planned to ambush Ursrook."

"That's because logistics is completely different from fighting at the front."

"Not really. In both cases, I use my ability for those in need," Tilly denied while shaking her head. "It was I who agreed to send Ashes to the front. You know very well that aerial knights won't stand a chance to win against the demons in the sky. There are too many demons and the aerial knights are too weak. Only I could change the situation."

"But the academy..."

"I certainly will fulfill my responsibilities. I'll train some qualified instructors so that they could further expand the academy." Tilly paused for a second, her eyes fixed on Roland, and said slowly, "I know I'm being selfish, but this is my only request."

Roland gazed into Tilly's eyes. At long last, he sighed, "I see."

Tilly unclenched her fist and said, "Thank you."

"By the way, any specific requirement on the color of the aircraft?" Roland asked when Tilly was about to leave.

Tilly stopped, a little perplexed, and answered, "No, not really..."

"Then how about red?"

"Does it make any difference?"

"Normally, the party that dominates the sky is in that color," Roland explained gently.

"Really?" Tilly said while curling up her lips. "Then red it is."

After Tilly took her leave, Nightingale said to Roland, "Her Highness is... serious this time."

Roland replied while massaging his forehead, "That's what troubles me." When Tilly said "this is my only request", Roland sensed her perserverance and eagerness behind her words. Roland understood no other person except him could help Tilly avenge Ashes. If he had turned Tilly down, her hope would turn into poignant despair, and dimly, he had a presentiment of losing her.

"She's also changed," Nightingale remarked. "But I understand her. If it was you — " Nightingale broke off and shook the idea off. "No, I can't even imagine it."

Roland fell silent. He suddenly realized that a war could alter many people and things, but the war itself would continue to bring destruction.

To prevent tragedies like this, there was no way other than ending this Battle of Divine Will as soon as possible.

Chapter 1195: Things I Want to Do

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Good could not even remember how he get back to his residence.

By the time he arrived at his house, it was around nightfall, and everyone was on their way back home. Smoke curled up from the chimneys, and he could hear people greet their families. The air was soaked with sweet aroma of porridge and the salty odor of sweat. The neighborhood was so lively and energetic that nobody would believe that this place was actually a residential area for refugees.

Good could smell the hope that empowered the energy and liveliness of the refugees. Residents here would be well fed as long as they worked hard. Within half a month, people could afford eggs and pork. Everyone was hopeful about their future, with their voice confident and their spirit high. Although the residential area was untidy and raucous, it was by no means dismal and miserable like a slum.

Everything here was colorful.

Except Good.

As he saw his neighbors smiled at him broadly, his eyes started streaming, and a scathing voice kept ringing around his ears, "Look at what you did, you thickhead. You ruined everything!"

Had he not been so headstrong to request a trial from Princess Tilly but instead accepted the punishment, he would have still been a student of the Aerial Knight Academy. Even if he could not become a pilot, he could still have a decent job in the future, much better than being homeless.

His courage had soon ebbed away after Princess Tilly had agreed with his proposal. Now, he only felt fear and despair.

If he failed, he would lose everything.

Good pushed open the door and entered as he was crestfallen.

A silvery voice greeted him brightly, "Good, you're home. See what I made for you."

Rachel ran up to him in excitement and settled him in his chair. She uncovered the lid of the plate and pronounced triumphantly, "Tada — egg pancakes! Looks good, eh?"

The so-called egg pancake was divided into two layers. It looked more like a pancake topped with scrambled egg than an egg pancake. Nevertheless, it still looked delicious. Its egg white thin, and its golden rim slightly furled, with an orange yolk right in the middle while yolk was still runny. The melted butter trickled down to the plate, giving off a rich and devilish smell.

Obviously, Rachel had put a lot of efforts into this meal.

Stunned for a split second, Good said, "You bought eggs?" Eggs were not particularly expensive in Neverwinter, but we still could not afford to have them everyday.

"Yes," Rachel said as she handed Good a wooden fork. "Uncle Bucky took me to the marketplace today. Don't worry. I still have savings. You rarely have a break, so it's okay to have eggs occasionally. Plus, once you become an aerial knight, we'll soon have more savings. I already thought this through!" Rachel patted her chest in confidence.

Good took the fork stiffly and mumbled, "Y-yes, you're right."

"Now, eat it and see if you like it," Rachel urged.

After a moment of hesitation, Good slowly put a morsel of the egg pancake in his mouth. Instantly, the flavor of the yolk mingled with the butter permeated his entire mouth.

Memories started to flow out from the deepest part of his mind.

He and Rachel had suffered a lot on the way from the Kingdom of Wolfheart to the Western Region of Graycastle. In the past, he would have never dreamed of having such tasty food. However, things turned better miraculously after they arrived at Neverwinter. They were fed and clothed in this city, and probably, in the near future, Rachel could eat this "egg pancake" every day, only if he continued to study at school.

Good did yearn to soar the sky, but was it really worth him to bet with his life?

He had nothing to lose before, but it was different now.

Good had to take care of Rachel.

Then why did he make such a selfish choice?

He had never thought of Rachel when he had agreed with Finkin to take a look at the planes.

He could not forgive himself for being so selfish!

"Do you like it? It shouldn't be... that bad, right? I haven't cooked for a while, and I'm not sure whether my cooking skills have got rusty or not," Rachel said with uncertainty. "Oi, say something. Is it okay? Hang on, why are you crying? Is the food that bad?"

"No..." Good replied, his face glazed with tears, as he gulfed down the pancake. "It's good, really good. I'm just... I couldn't help..."

Startled, Rachel walked up to him, patted his head and asked quietly, "Did something happen?"

"I'm sorry... I probably couldn't continue to study in the academy..."

Good then told Rachel everything.

"I see," Rachel said at length. "I just have one question for you. Do you... like flying?"

"I — " Good broke off, groping for words that did not come. He found it hard to lie in front of Rachel's face, so he nodded.

"Then there is nothing to worry about," Rachel smiled. "This is your first time finding something you like, right? You've done so much for me on our way here. I asked you to leave the Kingdom of Wolfheart, and you could have refused, but you still did. So how can you be a selfish person?"

"But I..."

"The worst scenario is to start all over again, right?" Rachel suggested with her head tilted on one side. "And I'm literate. Even if I don't... well, I could find jobs by myself. So, just do your best."

"R-really?"

"Anyway, you don't have time to regret. It's better to think about how to pass the trial than worrying about our future. Just make sure to keep your temper next time."

Good stared at Rachel for quite a while until he said, "Sometimes, I feel you know much more about the world than me."

"I'm older than you, so naturally I know more. You insisted me to be your younger sister, remember?" Rachel mumbled and smiled at Good. "If you're expelled, then let's switch it up. I'll be your elder sister."

...

The next day, in the airport for the aerial knights.

Sixteen students stood out in a line at the end of the runway. As these students passed the exam first, they got the chance to have the trial first.

Four brand new planes gradually glided over the runway and came to halt in front of them.

Mumurs instantly swept over the crowd. Everybody was studying attentively at the four beautiful machines with great interest.

Except Finkin and Hinds whose face was screwed up.

Good closed his eyes.

He felt the cool breeze blowing at his face, trying to revisit his training, memorize the instructions of the officer, and visualize each move. Gradually, a blur of images showed up in his mind.

When Princess Tilly appeared, everybody kneeled down on their knees. Finkin tugged Good's sleeve to remind him.

"Your Royal Highness!"

"Rise," Tilly said expressionlessly. "It's your first time seeing these new planes, but you should have been familiar with them by now. All the materials in the textbook are based on the 'Unicorn', and these planes are the upgraded versions of the 'Unicorn', so they function better. Therefore, as long as you follow the instructions received in your training, you should be able to pass the trial. Considering it's your first time flying a plane, I'll sit you through the process and supervise you. I'll also mark your performance. Of course, I would rather you not needing my instructions."

Tilly paused for a second and went on, "However, in consideration of possible errors you would make in this test, I invited Miss Nana here. As long as you don't die on the spot, you'll survive, but it also means that you'll get a really low mark. If you can't improve yourself in the subsequent training, you'll be expelled. So, I hope you'll do your best. Also, if the plane sustains substantial damage, you'll get a zero mark because we don't have enough planes for you to crash. Understand?"

"Yes, Your Highness!" the sixteen students chorused.

"Now, let's begin. First examinant, Good." Tilly announced solemnly.

Good took a deep breath, walked up to the plane, and crawled into the cabin.

Chapter 1196: The Reason to Fly

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

A soldier started the plane and turned on the valve. The aircraft immediately started to shake violently, the engine began to roar, and the propeller spun at a tremendous speed.

When the roar turned into a steady buzz, Good slowly pushed the gas lever, and the plane, as if being pulled by an invisible force, started to slide on the runway.

"Wow..." the crowd exclaimed impressively.

Good felt greatly encouraged, as he had not expected that it would really work. He was now truly operating this giant steel beast!

Good turned his head toward Princess Tilly who was sitting on the left side of the wing, her gray hair streaming behind her, a twinge of smile in her eyes. Was the princess... content with his performance? Good became more confident, believing he should have no problem passing this trial as long as he followed Tilly's instructions.

However, the princess did not say anything.

Good cast glances at Tilly numerous times, but Tilly was determined to maintain her silence, with faint yet playful smile lingering on her lips. When the plane crossed halfway through the runway, Good suddenly came to the realization that he would probably not receive any instructions during the entire trial.

"Considering it's your first time flying a plane, I'll walk you through the process one step at a time."

Princess Tilly's promise did not apply to him who had broken the school rules.

The other students would have a second chance, but he would not.

His enthusiasm was instantly quenched by a surge of disappointment and regret.

"If you don't make me say anything, then it definately would be your best performance."

Good somehow comprehended what Her Highness had meant. If he could not fly the plane all by himself, he would be expelled, which was a price he had to pay for breaking the rules. If he proved his talent to the princess, then he would have some value for further education.

Could he really fly the plane on his own?

Now he had already used up two thirds of the distance, and a patch of grass gradually swam into his view, followed by the wall that encircled the airport. If he ran directly into the wall, even Miss Nana would not be able to save him.

There's no time.

Good wanted to pull back the gas lever, as this seemed to be the only way to slow down the plane and avoid a direct clash.

However, the next moment, he felt a hand pat on his head.

"Do you like... flying?"

Rachel's voice reverberated next to his ears.

Flying...

Yes, if he were a bird, there should be another way.

Which was to fly over the wall.

If he slowed down now, his journey would end here.

It was a second that contained eternity. Good grasped the lever and pushed it forward.

The engine instantly roared like thunder.

The wall streaked toward him!

Good jerked the plane up ten meters in front of the wall. As the plane shook violently, the runway sank below him and slid out of his sight. The patch of grass flitted below him. For a moment, Good felt weightless. The ground plummeted as he soared into the air!

"Faster! A little faster!" Good's eyes widened as the top of the wall pressed in. He was ready to embrace the crash.

But the crash never happened.

It shot up into the sky. All the obstacles in front of him disappeared, and Good saw a view he had never beheld. The academy, the coastline, and Neverwinter far away spun below him, his mind clearer and his heart lightened as the truth of operating a plane dawned on him.

Good wanted to whoop.

It was so wonderful that human beings could finally fly.

...

After he landed, Good knelt down before Princess Tilly.

"Thank you for giving me this opportunity. I saw something that could only exist in my dream."

During the trial that had lasted half an hour, Good had completed the basic flight maneuvers, including climbs and hovering, although with some difficulties.

There was nothing more he could do about his marks.

Even if he failed, the memory of this flight would be engraved in his heart. From now on, whenever he closed his eyes, he would remember this unique experience.

"Why did you join the Aerial Knight Academy?"

Tilly's voice came from above.

Good hesitated for a moment before he replied truthfully, "Your Highness, at first I just wanted to earn some income. Later, I wanted to be a successful man. Now, I've fallen in love with flying."

"I can give you money and fame, and also offer you a pilot job, provided that you promise to kill as many demons as you can," Tilly said coolly. "Fight for Graycastle and kill every demon that comes into your view. You have to exchange everything I give you with their blood. This is the duty of an aerial knight, the purpose of building this school. If you could do that, then report to Eagle Face."

Good looked up in excitement and said, "Your Highness, do you mean — "

"You passed," Tilly said and whipped around without looking back.

The trial did not end until 5:00 in the afternoon. Two out of sixteen were knocked out.

Finkin and Hinds also passed the trial.

After the students were dispersed, Finkin and Hinds grabbed Good by the arm, pulled him next to them and said, "Are you mental? Princess Tilly told us we only needed to take off and land properly to pass. Not only did you almost run into the wall, but you also flew out of the academy and hovered above the sea. Weren't you afraid that you would crash the plane?"

"That was an accident," Good thought to himself while rolling his eyes, then he said, "Didn't Her Highness say that all of us should do our best? I didn't know that you just need to take off and land to get a pass. I thought a few more moves would boost my mark."

"You lucky dog," Finkin said while shaking his head.

"You guys did well, too." Good said while twitching his lips. "You took off so well without instructions."

"What? What do you mean by 'without instructions'? Didn't Her Highness tell you when to pull the lever?"

"Yeah, but she gave fewer instructions to us than the other students," Hinds assented, "because we're wrong-doers."

Good was rooted to the ground. Was he the only person who did not receive any instructions?

While confused, the three of them returned to their dormitory.

An icy Eagle Face was waiting for them there.

The three shuddered. The trainees were actually afraid of their instructor more than Princess Tilly. They were constantly under the impression of being X-rayed under Eagle Face's piercing scrutiny.

"S-sir..."

"I'm very impressed. I didn't expect that you could make trouble even on your break," he said as he surveyed Good, Finkin and Hinds coldly. "Princess Tilly has told me everything. You're very lucky not to be expelled. Well, this isn't the jurisdiction of the First Army, otherwise..."

"S-sir, we're sorry!" the three immediately apologized in earnest.

"Since Her Highness has already punished you, I won't inflict more punishment. However, if you become an aerial knight, you'll become a member of the army," Eagle Face jeered. "To make sure you won't make the same mistake again, you'll have to clean the washroom for the whole month coming next. You got it?"

"What..." Both Finkin and Hinds screwed up their faces.

Only Good administered a salute.

"As you command, sir!"

Chapter 1197: The Torch of the Civilization

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The trial that had lasted a week not only indicated that the students at the Aerial Knight Academy had taken the first crucial step but also marked the official beginning of their training program. The trial, as a matter of fact, had stirred the entire city.

Several citizens spied a "giant kite" hover above the southern part of the city. Although Tilly often flew the "Unicorn" around the castle, most of the time she confined her activity to depopulated areas . As such, the public had never truly witnessed a real plane.

Onlookers rushed toward the southern city, hoping to catch a glimpse of the plane when it darted out of the yard. In the beginning, only residents at the Shallow Port and the industrial area knew about the trial. Nevertheless, within three days, the news was spread out throughout the entire city, and the academy was besieged by curious spectators. Whenever a plane slid into their view, the crowd erupted a loud cheer as if it were them riding the plane.

Honey took advantage of this opportunity and soon published an article entitled "A Recurring Miracle", detailing the trial for the pilot trainees. The article was supplemented with two close-up shots of the biplane, which immediately brought the sales of Graycastle Weekly to a new peak.

Many merchants beyond Neverwinter sniffed a business opportunity and started to purchase the papers at a high price from the locals after they were sold out. Those who were not financially capable of doing that hired people to copy the article and the photos. Such a movement further raised the paper price in the city.

Aerial Knights, therefore, were known to everybody in Neverwinter overnight.

Roland received Tilly's report a week later.

150 out of the 197 trainees passed the trial, which meant that 47 students crashed the plane due to major errors. As there were only four planes used in the trial, each plane crashed around 11 times on average.

It appeared that the crashing rate was pretty high, but Roland understood that the plane was lightweight and had a simple structure. As long as the engine remained intact, it was easy to fix them. Most of the crashes, as Roland noticed, had occurred during the process of landing due to speeding or slow operation. Roland was certain with a little bit of repair here and there, the biplane would recover its splendor.

Of course, the refurbished planes would obviously not function as well as the mint ones. In fact, two planes were so battered that they could no longer satisfy the need of the students. To make sure that the students received adequate training, at least 12 to 15 biplanes were required for the subsequent advanced training program.

This was also the number required for a large fleet in his previous world.

Roland concluded that the whole reported only conveyed one piece of information: "The air force and I need funds, and you shall give me money."

Roland put down the report in amusement. He had to admit that Tilly did have some talent, for she had already grasped the nature of the air force when it was still in its infancy. In fact, a competent fleet not only required manpower but also a large number of planes for training purposes.

At present, all the industries in Neverwinter were severely short staffed. Apparently, they could not build an air force in a short period of time.

Apart from Tilly, Edith Kant, the Chief of the General Staff, also handed him a report.

The report was short but quite interesting.

Edith believed that the aerial knights had a potential to change the situation of the war and would even play a decisive role in the outcome of the battle, provided that they were properly used. Therefore, she wished to establish a research committee and send them to the academy to learn more about the planes for future strategic studies. She also conceived a few tactics specifically for the aerial knights, which she wished to discuss in detail with Roland at the earliest.

Edith was probably one of the few executives who truly cared about the planes. Roland admired her remarkable perspicacity and the ability to quickly associate the planes with potential war practices.

While Roland was planning to summon Edith to discuss aerial knights, his guard reported, "Your Majesty, the Minister of Construction, Sir Karl Van Bate, wishes to see you."

Roland withdrew his hand from the telephone and said, "Send him in."

"Yes, Your Majesty."

"Your Majesty," Karl saluted as he entered the office. "The construction of the Miracle Building is completed."

...

Roland marveled at the towering building as he stared up at it from the bottom.

It took them two years to build this magnificent edifice. The construction cost them tons of gold royals and a large amount of steel and concrete that was more than enough to build three Redriver Bridges. Thanks to Lotus, Hummingbird and the other witches, they managed to complete the construction with relatively little manpower and few resources.

Contracting an expensive habit of squandering national resources and developing an addiction to extravagant architecture would definitely weaken national power. However, the impact this building brought upon civilians was also phenomenal, which could be evidenced by the reaction of the spectators.

The striking contrast between the two or three-story residential buildings and the Miracle Building that stood 50 to 60 meters tall exhilarated Roland.

As Neverwinter's new landmark, the Miracle Building not only astonished the masses with its ineffable grandeur but it was also a manifestation of the most advanced technologies currently available in this era. For example, its drainage system was comprised of various water tanks at different levels to ensure that water could be drawn efficiently.

Further, four outdoor "elevators", driven by the steam engines at the basement, could transport dozens of people at a time between different floors. Although the elevators were quite rudimentary compared to modern ones and they required attendants to manually control the operation, they were unprecedented in this era. Passengers could have a birdview of the city through the french windows installed to the elevators.

"Your Majesty, please say something," Karl suggested while placing his hand on his chest after they reached the podium. "Your subjects are waiting for you."

Roland nodded and waved at the thousands of heads below.

A tidal wave of cheers swept over him.

"Good afternoon, my subjects."

"This is the day when the Miracle Building is officially open to the public. It's a building that sets numerous world records. Today will be remembered by our descendents. However, I'm not dwelling on its degree of magnificence but on what you're most concerned about, that is, who will be living here and for whom it was built."

"Is it nobles? No, Graycastle has stripped nobles of their power. Is it the royal family? Of course not. I don't need such a large building to place my bed. The answer is simple. This building is for the residents in Neverwinter, that is, you all."

"You built the Miracle Building and are therefore entitled to this miracle!"

"Every room in this building will be listed for sale. You don't have to be a noble to buy. Just bring your identification card, and you'll become a resident of this building that is destinied to be a part of our history!"

As soon as Roland finished, another wave of cheers flooded over him.

"Long live the king!"

"Long live Neverwinter!"

After the chorus died down, Roland continued, "Now, let's ignite the torch at the top of the building. From today onwards, this torch will be lit every night and dazzle the whole city!"

In the deafening roar, Roland and some officials of the City Hall entered the elevator and climbed to the top floor.

A huge stone basin was placed at the center of the roof, brimming with black oil. This thick heavy oil, which had been specifically processed beforehand, had a long lasting power. It would not emit a foul odour or produce smog either. Therefore, it was the optimal fuel for a long-burning flame torch.

"Your Majesty," Nightingale said as she handed Roland the torch.

Roland nodded, took the torch and ambled over to the basin.

He suddenly remembered a song he had once listened to, its familiar lyrics came floating out of his memories.

"The moment there was the first sign of life underwater... you've come a long way..."

A smile curled Roland's lip, and he ignited the torch.

This was the flame of the human civilization, and he hoped that it would burn forever.

Chapter 1198: A Foreigner

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

At the Sedimentation Bay in the Kingdom of Wolfheart.

As one of the two port cities in the Kingdom of Wolfheart, the dock here was always busy. Merchants from the interior loaded and unloaded their ships before they set off for their next undertaking from this harbor. Alternatively, they traded their commodities with local marine tradesmen. As such, the dock area was essentially a big marketplace where all kinds of transactions took place, from furs all the way to slaves.

White settled himself in his coach, languishing at the raucous coachmen while gazing upon the ocean.

Ever since the outbreak of the war between Graycastle and Hermes, local churches had stopped sending orphans to the Holy City. Having lost the main source of income, merchants in the Kingdom of Wolfheart struggled to live. What was worse, because of the friction between local lords, peace was not restored after the regime of the church was overthrown. Coachmen like White, being financially unstable, thus had to come to the Sedimentation Bay to seek new employment for a living.

Although the war had also somewhat affected the life in the Sedimentation Bay, the nobility still led their previous extravagant lifestyle. As the passage leading to the Cage Mountain was now under the control of the Token Family, it left other lords no choice but to rely on sea shipping to transport their luxurious goods, which, in a way, sustained the economy here.

Of course, the temporary prosperity was also partially attributed to the fact that the baron in the Sedimentation Bay maintained his neutral position.

This was one of the reasons that White chose to strike root here.

He was old and did not want to wander about anymore.

White planned to carry cargo for a few more times and purchase a property with the money earned before starting his own small business.

"Hey, man, any work for you today?" Suddenly, a young worker clambered onto White's coach and jeered at him.

"Get out of my way. It's none of your business," White said gruffly while waving his hand in the same manner as he dismissed an annoying fly. "Don't you get on my carriage. You can't afford the repair of these beautiful wheels."

"Don't say that. Look at me. I'm tiny. Am I going to crush your wagon?" the young man protested as he patted his stomach and slumped against the compartment. He picked up a straw on the floor, sucked it between his teeth and looked around. "What did you carry last time? Why does it smell so funky in here?"

"Get off, or I'll kick your ass," White grunted. He did not know the young man's name, but all the other workers called him Smarty. White did not see any smartiness in him. To him, this young man was simply an unacquainted coworker.

"Really? With your artificial leg? I bet it hurts on rainy days, doesn't it?" the young man said casually. "It looks like it's going to rain soon. Your joints and bones should be hurting now, right?"

Speechless, White glowered at him, wondering when he had found out his secret.

"Haha, don't stare at me like that. I'm here to help you," Smarty explained while spreading out his hands. "There are so many people looking for work. You're an old man and certainly couldn't compete with young guys."

"What's your point?"

"Very simple. My coworkers will help you get a good spot. Are you interested in collaborating with us?"

"And in return?" White asked.

"A comission of 10%. A good deal, eh?" Smarty said, smiling.

White fell silent. The sky above looked sullen. Sea breezes whipped his clothes, preluding a heavy rain. It was true that his fake leg might hinder him from getting any business from his competitors, and employers would probably not entrust their cargo to a limped laborer.

Hearing no response from him, Smarty snapped his fingers and said, "Well, I take it as a yes?"

"You aren't... just helping me, right?" White asked at length as he stared at him.

"Ahem, if everyone comes to seek me for help, that'll save me a lot of time," Smarty answered evasively. "By the way, can't you switch the straw to cushion? The most popular products in the Sedimentation Bay are the Chaos Drinks from Fjords and perfumes. Although nobles would normally bring their own carriages, you never know what will happen. They would always need a spare carriage. Your wagon is so smelly. Even if I bring business to you, employers probably wouldn't like to hire you..."

White cast a glance at the eloquent young man and finally understood why people called him Smarty. Yet as an aged and experienced man, he had also seen a great deal of life. He thus said, "Did you just ask me what I carried last time?"

"Yes?"

"Cow dung that is used for fuel," he answered slowly. "They were sun-dried, but still it can be wet here and there."

Smarty stiffened. He spat the straw and started to retch.

White grunted triumphantly. A kid was essentially a kid. He rested his eyes back on the ocean and suddenly stood framed to the spot.

Several three-masted ships slowly came into his view, all from the Chambers of Commerce at Fjords, their masts almost 100 feet tall, their golden flags rimmed with black. He did not know what Chamber of Commerce that was.

Whatver ships they were, White only cared about the cargo on them. With such colossal ships, he was certain he would have some business even without Smarty's help.

White got off his coach and untied his horse. He was about to ride to the dock when Smarty suddenly pulled him from the back.

"Hey... it seems something is wrong there."

White turned around impatiently and started at what he saw.

More masts appeared behind the three main ships, their sails forming a "white wall" over the sea.

"God almighty..."

Those grayish-black ships covered every inch of the ocean. White attempted to make a count but soon abandoned this idea after he saw 50 ships come into his sight. As more and more ships followed, White found it hard to catch up with the count. There were probably 100 or 200 ships in total, and maybe even more!

There were giant three-masted ships but also numerous steaming paddle steamers. White had seen these new boats before, but it was his first time seeing so many of them. He was positive even sailors living at the harbor had not seen such a huge fleet.

All the pedlars, sailors and laborers stopped what they were doing and gazed at the approaching fleet.

The dock suddenly became incredibly quiet.

As the ships drew close, they could now see the flags more clearly. White could barely make out the coat of arms on those flags, which featured a lofty tower and spears. All the flags on those ships bore the same coat of arms. Hundreds of banners streamed against the wind and formed a new horizon that awed the spectators.

Smarty gasped.

"Is it... the Graycastle flag?"

White muttered in disbelief, "Are you saying... that the King of Graycastle came here?"

As the Sedimentation Bay could not accommodate so many large ships, most of the ships lowered their sails outside the harbor while the ten steam-powered boats came straight to the dock area.

As soon as the ships disembarked, a group of uniformed men filed out onto the trestle and the dock area, all as expressionless, frosty and reticent as seasoned soldiers.

White swallowed hard. For some reason, he was afraid of these men whom he had never seen before. White had the impression that all the people on the dock felt the same way. Soon, these foreigners occupied the entire trestle but nobody dared to raise an objection.

White realized that this fleet was not here for trading goods.

The air above the dock became thick and heavy.

The leaden clouds in the sky seemed to be even lower.

Chapter 1199: The Commotion in the Kingdom of Wolfheart

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

"What damn weather," the baron, Jean Bate, muttered as he stared at the overcast sky by the window. "It's raining again."

It rained a lot in the Sedimentation Bay, particularly in summer and fall. Unexpected storms visited this city often, so the city was equipped with a well-developed drainage system. Unlike the Broken Tooth Castle and Graystone City where roads instantly turned muddy after a heavy rain, the rain here would only affect the cargo transportation. The impact of the weather was indeed minimal to the urban area.

Jean was actually more frustrated about himself than the upcoming rain.

The sky would soon clear out after the shower, but his mood would remain gloomy.

"Sir, have you figured out how to reply to them?" His clerk, Zum, asked gingerly.

"Reply?" the baron sneered. "What would you say if you have to pick between being hanged and being burned?"

"Er..." The clerk fell silent.

"You can't make a choice either, right? So, let's just keep them waiting."

"But..." Zum broke off, trying to formulate a proper answer.

Jean Bate knew very well that playing for time was just a temporary solution. Like the prospective storm that would come no matter merchants liked it or not, he had to solve this problem regardless.

Everything started with the war against the church.

After the fall of the king's city of the Kingdom of Wolfheart, dozens of lords, all of a sudden, claimed that they were the bastards of the King of Wolfheart. These alleged royal blood formed cliques and factions to fight for the throne. After numerous fierce battles, the kingdom was divided into three major territories, each dominated by the Token Family in the northwest, the "Redstone Gate" Family in the south, and the "Tusk" Family in the mountainous area in the east.

Since the Tokens were relatively far from the Sedimentation Bay, they had never come to bother Jean. However, both the Redstone Gate Family and the Tusk Family were trying strenuously to win him over to further expand their territories.

The baron had been taking a neutral position during the war. His disinterest in political gains soon brought huge profits to his city. Since the two dukes relied on the port to transport food and gold royals, and because they had been busy with conquering other surrounding cities and towns, the two families had not extended their power over the Sedimentation Bay as yet.

However, as the expansion progressed, the Tusk and Redstone Gate Families gradually became two of the most competitive candidates for the future sovereign. Since the Tokens suddenly extended a full reign over the Cage Mountain, the Tusk and Redstone thus again rested their eyes on the baron's domain, the Sedimentation Bay.

Jean knew exactly what they aimed at.

They wanted to seize the Sedimentation Bay and banned commercial trades of their opponents as a way to outpower the other. To this end, both dukes sent their embassadors, along with dozens of knights and mercenaries, in an ostensible attempt to lobby him.

The port was only guarded by a patrol team and several of Jean's own guards. Those guards could cope with savage pirates but definitely not fully-equipped knights. Jean Bate did not plan to resist. He would pledge alliance to whoever that ascended the throne, and he did not care whether this succeeder was the true blood of the late king.

Unfortunately, however, the Redstone Gate and the Tusk Families were powerful in equal measure.

Under such circumstances, he could join neither of them.

Whichever side he picked, he would suffer virulent vengeance from the other party. Losing the right to trade meant they would have to produce food and other military supplies by themselves while the other party would be entitled to a constant supply of resources. Neither of the two families would like to put themselves in such an unfavorable situation.

Therefore, a war would be inevitable.

There was no fortified city wall or deep moat protecting the city, which meant that Jean had to pick a side to defend against the invasion.

However, would the two families support him?

The baron could not take a chance.

Shrewd as the two dukes, they would probably sacrifice the subjects of the Sedimentation Bay to reduce the casualities of their knights and then cut the retreat once their enemy entered the city, for they cared only about the land not the people.

Perhaps, it would be better to abandon the Sedimentation Bay to the two families.

That was why Jean said this was a decision between being hanged and being burned.

Jean sent the two emissary delegations to the same campsite, hoping their acrimony against each other would earn him time to think over the matter. He rather hoped the two parties engaged in a physical altercation. To this end, Jean had even sent women and strong liquor to inveigle them into fighting, but other than a fierce verbal argument, neither of the two parties made the first move.

"Tick, tick..."

The rain finally pounded against the garden of his mansion, draping a misty curtain between Heaven and earth.

Watching flowers swaying gently in the rain, the baron lapsed into silence. He knew it was not wise to play for time, but he could not think of any other way to get out of this dilemma. His grandfather used to advise him that nobles tended to always waver between interests and power. As long as he took advantage of their indecisiveness, he would never lose. Perhaps, it was time for him to stop playing games but start to think deeper and more strategically.

Just then, a pattering of running footsteps interrupted his thought.

"S-sir, bad news!"

"What's the matter? Now, now, take it easy!" Jean Bate said as he shot the guard a glance. "What happened?" He stared at the guard's quivering lips, hoping to hear words like "knights" or "campsite" that hinted a fight between the two families.

"The fleet of the King, the King of Graycastle took the port. They not only took over the dock but also forbade anyone to approach that area!" The news was so shocking that for a moment, Jean stood rooted to the ground.

"What did you say? Gray, Graycastle?" the baron stammered. "Do they want to sell anything here? Hang on... you said they blocked off the dock?"

"Yes!" the guard blustered frantically. "They drove away the boats around the trestle for their own ships. They say they're going to borrow the port for a while and assure that order will soon be established. The patrol team attempted to stop them but was immediately disarmed. It's reported that there are hundreds of Graycastle ships outside the harbor!"

Jean Bate asked incredulously, "Are you sure it's the fleet of the King of Graycastle, not any lord?"

"Yes, I saw them through my telescope," the guard replied with some difficulties. "I confirm that the coat of arms on the flags does represent Graycastle. It has a tower and spears."

Jesus, did Graycastle intend to invade the Kingdom of Wolfheart?

Why did Wimbledon not pick his neighbor but him?

Even if the King of Graycastle desired to expand his territory, he did not necessarily have to launch an attack on the sea. Could the Token Family resist the army of Graycastle who had once defeated the church?

No, this did not make sense...

The baron dealt hurriedly with crowding thoughts.

Then his clerk Zum came up to him and whispered something in his ear.

The baron's face lighted up.

Yes, this was what he was exactly waiting for!

The army of Graycastle definitely had the capability to break the deadlock between the two warring families. If this fleet did plan to wage a war here, they would need the help of local nobles no matter how invincible they were. With just a little guidance, they would be able to conquer the entire land. Jean did not have specific preference over any lord, but apparently, the King of Graycastle could offer him more than any of the nobles. Possibly in the near future, he would become a governor of some jurisdiction if he chose to pledge fealty to the King of Graycastle.

Even if Wimbledon failed his attempt, Jean would not lose anything.

Just at that moment, another guard burst in. "Sir, the Graycastle fleet sent an embassador on behalf of King Roland Wimbledon, who wishes to speak to you."

Jean Bate exchanged a look with the clerk before he said with a nod, "He's our guest. Tell the embassador that I'll come out to meet him."

Chapter 1200: The Will of the King of Graycastle

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

"Now?" the guard asked blankly. "Right away?"

"Yes."

Usually, according to common practices of the nobility, he should let the embassador rest for a few days and welcome him with a sumptuous banquet. At least, he should have set up a meeting time beforehand, possibly at night. After all, the embassador represented the King of Graycastle, and thus should be treated with formality to some degree.

However, Jean couldn't wait any longer. Had it not been rainy outside, he would have rushed to the dock and met this embassador himself. Such a huge fleet would definitely draw the attention of the Tusk and the Redstone Gate Families. If either of them got in touch with Graycastle before him, things would become very complicated.

With this thought, Jean Bate said to the guard, "By the way, tell the Graycastle delegation that I'm the sole authority that governs the Sedimentation Bay."

"Yes, sir."

Yet after the guard left at his bidding, Jean suddenly regretted his impulsive action.

He should not have said "right away". What if the embassador wanted to follow and observe the tradition first then call him a few days later?

Jean blamed his own vanity at the bottom of his heart. He should have been more straightforward.

And why did it rain right as he wanted to go out?

The baron felt miserable.

But surprisingly, the guard returned within an hour and brought him a good news.

"Sir, they're coming."

Jean Bate stood bolt upright and said, "Take them to my parlour immediately."

...

The baron soon met the embassador from Graycastle.

There were only ten people who came, and half of them were soldiers that were guarding outside the door. The rest were all formally dressed, whom Jean gathered were assistants and clerks. The one in the middle was apparently the embassador himself. He noticed that the coats they were wearing were waterproof, as all of them were dry despite the pouring rain outside. The material of their coats had a bright, fresh color. It was, however, neither fur nor leather.

It appeared that the rumor which Graycastle did produce many curious items was true.

However, Jean squeezed his eyebrow as he looked on the embassador. The embassador was definitely a Mojin by his look. Why could a Mojin, who usually served as a slave here, be a noble in Graycastle?

Even though he was shocked, the baron showed a hearty smile and completely hid his emotions. He spread out his hands and said, "I'm the lord of the Sedimentation Bay. As you can see, this is a beautiful and bustling city, a wonderful place for you to take a rest. May I know what brought you here today?"

The baron was speaking in such a humble courteous manner, and he was confident that even a duke would receive him with some civilities.

But the Mojin remained expressionless. He replied flatly, "My name is Iron Axe, the commander of the First Army and also the supervisor of this expedition. Let's save the small talk. The Kingdom of Everwinter and the Kingdom of Wolfheart will soon become a battlefield. I came here on the order of the King of Graycastle, Chief of the Mojin clan, and ruler of the Fertile Plains, King Roland Wimbledon, to save your all."

"What the heck?"

Jean Bate could not believe what he had just heard, wondering what the Chief meant and where the Fertile Plains was. Was the embassador making a war threat against the Kingdom of Everwinter and the Kingdom of Wolfheart? Why did he threaten him outright without negotiation?

"Er..."

Instead, it was Zum who replied first, "Is the First Army the army that defeated the church?"

"Yes," Iron Axe affirmed with a nod.

"Sir Iron Axe, we obviously don't want to see a war here, but we can't make the decision on our own. There will always be someone who will attempt to resist. If you could persuade them, then we can avoid this war." Zum retorted.

Jean nodded vigorously, and he was glad that Zum did a good job. In that case, the Redstone Gate and the Tusk had to fight as well. He looked at Iron Axe triumphantly but was surprised to see a hint of sarcasm in Iron Axe's eyes.

Iron Axe said placidly, "You don't have a choice. The entire human race will have to fight when the enemy comes. In fact, this war has already begun in a place you don't know. I think you've heard about some rumors about the church, the Divine Will, and the attack of a foreign race."

Jean Bate gaped. As the lord of the port city, he had indeed heard about such things from marine merchants. However, these groundless rumors could only serve as the subject of public discussion but not a proper diplomatic topic at the negotiation table. Nonetheless, judging from the embassador's tone, Jean realized he was serious.

"Yes, these are all true," Iron Axe said slowly and firmly.

Thunders began to roar outside the window.

"Wow, are they all made out of iron?" Smarty asked as he leaned dramatically on the stable fences.

"Even iron will rust. In my opinion, they aren't human," White answered as he wiped the water off the horseback and fumbled his wet clothes. "Will a reasonable person stands in the rain? Only a lunatic will do that."

Within an hour, hundreds of people exited from the ships and took control of the whole harbor. Pedlars were dispersed by the storm, but these men put up tents in the middle of the square. A few moments later, dark green sheds filled half of the dock.

In addition to the tents, Graycastle men also set up tube-shaped obstacles on the crossroad and some higher parts of the road. These metal tubes did not look like weapons, but they glinted in the rain, giving White a queasy feeling in the pit of his stomach.

Each "tube" was guarded by soldiers. Although everyone was wearing a waterproof cloak, it was impossible to stay completely dry in this weather. Gusts of wind were so furious that they sent rushes of rain in every direction. White could envision how water trickled down through those soldiers' collars and soaked their clothes.

It must be awful to stand out there.

The Sedimentation Bay was wet and rainy all year round, so the local lord had built many temporary sheds in the dock area. However, these soldiers took no notice of them. They stood straight in their gleamy cloaks like rocks.

"Men from Graycastle are crazy..." White mumbled to himself.

"Hmm, weird," Smarty muttered.

"What now?" White said gruffly.

"Look at those cargo ships, then look at those outside the harbor," Smarty said. "The ones outside the harbour are three-masted sailing ships, but they're shallow on the draft."

"What's a draft?"

"Just view it as a measurement for the cargo weight," Smarty said dismissively. "Even though these cargo ships have been unloaded, they're still much deeper on the draft than the sailing ships outside. I don't understand. What are the Graycastle men up to? Are they bluffing about their forces?"

"What are you talking about?" White said impatiently.

"My point is... that these ships might be empty!" Smarty replied in a subdued voice.

...

Jean Bate did not pull himself together until Iron Axe finished.

He had just heard about the long, distant history of the wars between humans and demons, that this war took place every four hundred years, and that this time, the demons were very likely to invade the interior from the Impassable Mountain Range!

"Are you... sure?" Jean remembered that the north of the Kingdom of Everwinter was girdled by endless mountains and steep cliffs. How could the demons invade from there?

"No, I'm not sure. That's why I brought my scouts here," Iron Axe said while shrugging. "However, whichever direction the demons come from, it won't make a difference. We have to unite together and defend this continent. Otherwise, mankind will be exterminated."

The baron suddenly had a queer feeling as if he were walking in his dream. He knew his clerk and guards all felt the same way.

"Ahem, alright then. Let's suppose that what you said was all true," Jean said after clearing his throat. "So why did the King of Graycastle send you here? Isn't the Kingdom of Everwinter where you are suppose to be?"

"It is, and don't you worry about that. What we want here is very simple, that is, to save as many people as possible from this war, including freemen, slaves, refugees and vagabonds," Iron Axe paused for a moment and then continued, "except nobles. Nobles shall make their own choices. If you cooperate with the First Army, we'll return your properties, land, titles and so on when we depart. If you try to stop us..."

Jean swallowed.

"You'll be the First Army's enemy," Iron Axe finished his sentence coldly.

Chapter 1201: Proof

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Jean Bate absolutely did not want to become the King of Graycastle's enemy.

Although he had never met the King of Graycastle, he had heard a lot about him. The God's Punishment Army of the Kingdom of Everwinter and the Kingdom of Wolfheart had experienced an utter defeat in the battle against Graycastle; the alliance army of the nobles of the Kingdom of Dawn had been flattened within one day; Roland Wimbledon had united his kingdom within half a year; it was rumored that Graycastle had even interfered with the coup on the Archduke Island.

However, these rumors were incomparable to the news that the First Army had been fighting the demons over the past one year. He would have been skeptical had he heard the news from other lords, but he found it hard to refute the commander of the First Army.

Nonetheless, whether Jean believed it or not, he had no way to confirm its validity.

The plan of the King of Graycastle was actually a little too unrealistic and even preposterous in Jean's opinion. Jean Bate would pledge his alliance to Roland immediately if the latter took the throne of the Kingdom of Wolfheart, but the fact was that his true intention was to relocate the people in the two kingdoms! According to Iron Axe, King Roland was planning to ship civilians of the two countries by sea and by land until every single civilian left their native land. Most nobles did not really care about their subjects as long as the movement would bring them profits. However, it would be a different story to evacuate the whole city. A vacated city meant a huge drop in food, taxes and industrial growth. The nobles would not agree to this plan so easily unless it was abosolutely necessary.

Even though the First Army was invulnerable, it could not possibly declare war against all the nobles in the Kingdom of Wolfheart. Without the support of the locals, their military logistics support would be in limbo. Furthermore, it appeared that Graycastle also intended to disperse their forces to attack the two countries at the same time, which was a surpassingly conceited and vainglorious act, as far as Jean could see.

After what seemed to be a long silence, Jean Bate said in a hushed voice, "I don't quite understand the rationale behind all this. If the demons are not coming from the Impassable Mountain Range, and we still continue to support the King of Graycastle, we would lose men, farmlands, cities and mines. I'm afraid we can't bear such a huge loss."

"I can't explain the reason to you. As the commander of the First Army, my duty here is to carry out the mission His Majesty entrusted to me. Yet..." Iron Axe broke off and then went on, "If you come visit Neverwinter, you'll know the answer."

"Fine then. Now, one last question..." the baron said as he moisted his lips. "You said nobles can make their own choices. What if I decide to come with you?"

Iron Axe nodded comprehensively, pointed at a clerk next to him and said, "This is Remy, the immigration officer of the Administrative Office of Neverwinter. He'll explain to you the next step."

"Hello, Mr. Baron, in that case, you'll become a member of the Kingdom of Graycastle," the immigration officer said as he leafed through the a stack of documents. "The first thing that I can tell you is that King Roland Wimbledon is a benevolent king. He'll never ill-treat anyone who has made a contribution to the kingdom. As Graycastle is governed by a series of laws, nobles in the kingdom are stripped of feudal power. Lands cannot be inherited. The same will also apply to you. As you have rich experience in city management, you could join the Administrative Office and assume the post of local governor or help His Majesty to expand his territory, for instance, the Fertile Plains. Of course, if the demons don't invade the Four Kingdoms, you're free to continue to rule the Sedimentation Bay if you want." "If you're lucky, you could rule a land much bigger than this city, considering not every noble would come with us."

It took almost a quarter of an hour for Remy to read all the documents, which indeed detailed all the prospective aspect of the policy that seemed to be the offspring of a long deliberation. Jean Bate believed the person who had drafted these documents must be an extraordinary minister. for he himself did not have the capability to produce such marvelous work.

In short, the main content of this proposal was an interchange between short-term and long-term interests. He could possibly become more than a lord of a bay depending on his performance. Whether it was a good deal solely depended on himself.

Jean should have settled down to the contemplation of this proposal thoroughly. However, the current condition forced him to make a quick decision.

This was at least better than being killed by one of the two families.

Jean was indebted to a belief that it would take more than one or two years to evacuate two countries. During the relocation, he could still rule the Sedimentation Bay without worrying about the threat of the two families.

He thus took a sharp intake of breath and answered, "I would like to pledge alliance to the King of Graycastle."

"A wise choice," Iron Axe commented with the same stony look as though he had foreseen the result. "Now, you could issue an administrative order to start the evacuation. We have a team of professionals to assist you in this matter."

"That fast?" the baron asked in surprise.

"Yes, we won't be here long. The First Army will leave the Kingdom of Wolfheart for the interior within three days."

"But — " Jean Bate pursued after a moment of hesitation. "The knights from the Tusk and the Redstone Gate won't let you do so. They probably won't openly resist Graycastle, but they could interfere with your operation by attacking the patrol team of the Sedimentation Bay."

He felt a little embarrassed to reveal this truth, for just an hour ago, he had told Iron Axe that he was the only ruler of the Sedimentation Bay. However, he must raise this problem now to prevent the two families from stirring up trouble in the event they knew that he had colluded with Graycastle and offered the land. It was also a test to see whether Iron Axe really intended to fulfill his promise.

But Iron Axe's answer again surprised him.

"The Sedimentation Bay is the key to this immigration plan, and I don't allow anyone to thwart it. There will be around 100 people stationed here after the First Army departs," Iron Axe said as he nodded to one of his assistants, who immediately left the parlor. "I've done some research on the Kingdom of Wolfheart before I headed here. Like I said, I won't allow any interference. Nobody could blatantly resist us or play stealthy games behind us. To this end, we'll take some measures to remove these potential obstacles."

"You mean…"

"Seeing is believing," Iron Axe said as he rose. "Don't worry. Those threats they you're worried about will soon be gone."

"It's still raining so heavily," Smarty remarked as he stretched out his hand, feeling the rain drops.

"So?" White asked while hammering his sore leg with his hands. "Why are you still here?"

"I don't want to get soaked. Plus, this shed is for everyone. I can stay here as long as I like," he retorted, grimacing.

"You — " White said, looking utterly affronted. He was about to give Smarty a lesson, teaching him to have some respect toward the elder when suddenly, a group of Graycastle men who left their tents caught his attention.

Water splattered over the pavement as these people trooped out in two columns.

He was very curious about the reflective metal tubes they carried on their backs, They were as ominous as those black facilities they had set up in the sentry boxes.

As the group of soldiers disappeared in the rain, White suddenly understood why he felt so fidgeted. These metal tubes did not look like being made by humans. Regular blacksmiths could by no means forge them.

Some other people who took shelter from the rain also noticed that and started to murmur.

Yet Smarty was surprisingly quiet.

White thus turned around. However, to his dismay, Smarty was gone.

Chapter 1202: A Thunderous War

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The campsite of the Redstone Gate and the Tusk Families were located near the driveway leading to the city, a place originally designed for caravans and mercenaries for temporary use. Now it served as an abode for delegations.

Since the campsite, which was boarded with low wooden fences, was on the opposite side of the Sedimentation Bay and was relatively safe, no particular security measures were taken. Neither of the delegations had put out sentries. They simply drew a line at the center of the campsite with spears and shields to mark out their territories.

Most people understood that the line did not represent anything. As long as the lord of the Sedimentation Bay did not make his decision, the two delegations would keep a civil tongue, and certainly they would not bother putting out sentries on such a wet day.

Therefore, when the 100 soldiers of the First Army stopped at around 200 meters from the campsite, neither of the two families noticed that they had visitors.

The knights did not realize the change in the situation until they heard the First Army demand their surrender.

"This is the First Army of Graycastle, who is now officially taking over the Sedimentation Bay. Under Neverwinter law, your conduct constitutes an illegal intrusion and illegal use of firearms. I demand your immediate surrender, otherwise we'll resort to force and you'll bear all the consequences of your action!"

This was preposterous!

The commander of the delegation of the Tusk Family pulled back the curtains and saw a man stand outside the campsite, speaking to him with a peculiar cylinder. A flag was rippling not far away, on which was an unfamiliar coat of arms. However, he had a hard time associating these uninvited soldiers with Graycastle. For him, Graycastle was a distant and foreign country only existing in various rumors circulated in the neighborhood.

These people were all cloaked and soaked in the rain, looking amusingly pathetic and ridiculous. The fact that they demanded them to be disarmed further accorded him an unrealistic feeling.

The commander went downstairs and found that the floor had been packed with mercenaries, who were now speaking foul language and making obscene gestures. They would have probably spat on that man's face had it not been raining outside.

That was what low people typically did. As a noble, the commander had to come up with some useful strategies.

What should he do if these people were really Graycastle men?

Perhaps, he should wait for the Redstone Gate Family to take action.

He could not really ask his knights to disarm as those people had commanded, nor could he send an embassador to negotiate with them, as he did not want to give them an impression of weakness.

The commander did not think the "alleged" Graycastle soldiers would suddenly attack them. They were, after all, so far away from the campsite, and the mercenaries had already reached their weapons, whereas the cloaked soldiers did not even possess a single horse.

At this moment, he had completely forgotten the warning previously given by the First Army.

For the nobles in the Kingdom of Wolfheart, wars were always time-consuming. They needed to first observe their enemy, issue commands, and then fight. These rules also applied to the battle with the Church of Hermes.

However, the First Army who had fought the demons viewed battles as a completely different matter.

Therefore, nobody realized what had happened when the battle broke out.

15 minutes later, four mortars fired. Although not as powerful as the Longsong Cannons, the mortars were more than enough to destroy wooden watchtowers. Since these mortars were much more portable than the field artilleries, soldiers liked to use them to start a war.

The campsite was instantly razed to the ground. The furious execration of the delegation members was drowned out by the roaring shells. The wooden houses soon collapsed under the impact of the shockwaves, fragments of pillars, doors and windows flying in all directions.

The unit commander of the First Army immediately ordered the soldiers to charge.

They soon besieged the campsite.

Neither of the two families managed to launch an effective counterattack. Some fearless mercenaries dashed out against the dust but were soon shot down. To avoid incidental casualties, the First Army did not advance until the dust was washed away by the rain.

They did this not out of kindness but because His Majesty needed more mine laborers.

Meanwhile, the First Army asked the knights to yield again.

This time, most of them obeyed.

Within 30 minutes, the threat of the two families that vexed the baron was eliminated.

...

Jean Bate was still in a shock after he returned to his mansion.

He knew Graycastle was powerful but had never expected them to be so invincible. The battle that had just taken place a moment ago did not look like a typical war to him.

Jean finally understood why Iron Axe said "Seeing is believing". As a witness of the battle, he had to admit what he had seen was effable. He enjoyed the unfolding of the event with almost an air of contentment. He liked the reticence and steeliness of those Graycastle soldiers. The glaring contrast between their silence and the deafening explosion impressed him even more than the queer weapons themselves.

What had those people experienced?

"Now, do you believe that we could manage the Sedimentation Bay?" Iron Axe's voice interrupted his thought.

Jean Bate was rendered speechless for a moment. He simply nodded submissively.

"Relax," Iron Axe said with a faint smile. "Don't be afraid of the First Army. You've decided to serve King Roland. We won't allow anything to happen to the Sedimentation Bay or anyone to challenge His Majesty's authority. You're now one of us."

"One of them? That sounds so strange..." the baron thought to himself. Over the past few years in the Kingdom of Wolfheart, he had never expected to be associated with a country. However, the commander of the First Army seemed to think this was natural.

Jean found, surprisingly, that he did not repel this idea.

After a moment of silence, he heaved a deep sigh and said, "I'll take care of the relocation campaign."

Chapter 1203: A Black Present

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Jean Bate was indeed fast. He not only offered half of the rooms in the mansion to the army but also sent some maids to serve the soldiers, although Iron Axe refused the service out of confidentiality concerns.

In watching the reluctant look of the several young officers from the General Staff, Iron Axe replied in a stony tone, "Time to work. Don't forget that your performance in this campaign is subject to Edith Kant's review. You should know the consequences if you make errors."

Everyone shuddered at the Pearl of the Northern Region's name and set to work.

"Map, I'll put up the map!"

"What about the schedule? I'll double check it."

"Anyone help me check the food?"

The room instantly became noisy.

"Look at these young fellows, always full of energy..." Remy commented while shaking his head. "The baron seems to have seen through them."

"A common trick nobles like to play," Iron Axe said, frowning. "He'd better employ his cunning little schemes on the immigration campaign."

"Don't worry. The Administrative Office will keep an eye on him," Remy promised while patting his chest. "Now, we've removed our first obstacle. It's better than I thought. The Tusk and the Redstone Gate Families indeed helped us, but it won't be that easy afterwards."

"No, it'll be just the same," Iron Axe corrected him.

"R-really?" Remy said in surprise.

"Because they've fallen behind," Iron Axe said and looked through the window. The overspread sky had cleared up a little bit.

"Because they've fallen behind." This was what Edith had told him before he had set off a week ago. He met Edith at the office of the General Staff, where they held a meeting to discuss how to efficiently carry out the immigration plan, with a secretary writing meeting minutes next to them. Edith said, "Most nobles haven't noticed the changes taking place in this world but are still dwelling exclusively on their personal interests while gloating over their wealth. They saw hardly anything else. I bet you plan to fight those nobles one by one, right?"

"If they impede His Majesty's plan, yes."

"That'll be too slow," Edith disapproved flatly. "This is different from the Graycastle unification war. We need to garrison troops in various foreign cities, so as time progresses, we'll have fewer soldiers at our command, which will thus significantly prolong the campaign. Those nobles won't openly resist the army but they'll definitely play stealthy behind your back. By the time you notice the damage and rush to rescue, it'll look bad on His Majesty."

"Then what should I do?"

"Set your goals beforehand, build alliance and fight enemies together," Edith said while handing him a table.

There was a list of items on the table, next to each of which was a point scale.

"What's this?" Iron Axe asked in bewilderment. It was his first time seeing such a strange form.

"A threat evaluation form? Or a manual of resistance level? Anyway, what it is called doesn't matter. I made this table based on nobles' mentality and other factors, including gender, heir, the size of their domains, the number of their troops, their behavior, etc. You would have a rough understanding of each noble after filling out the form. The more information you obtain, the more accurate the evaluation will be. Since the situation in the Kingdom of Wolfheart and the Kingdom of Everwinter has changed a lot, the General Staff can't complete the form for you. If there's a city that's not on the form, just punch in the information and do the calculation yourself."

"And what next?" Iron Axe asked as he skimmed through the form.

"If the total point is lower than 50, it means the city has limited power and is not so ambitious. You could build alliance with them. These nobles could actually provide many things for you, such as local maps, the city structure, the demographics, and so on. More importantly, with the support of local lords, we'll be able to implement the plan more efficiently," Edith explained.

"As for those that are higher than 50..." Edith paused for a second and said, "Don't waste time on them. Whether they show any inclination to yield or not, you should crush them immediately."

Iron Axe was a little shocked at the method Edith proposed. A simple table would pretty much determine each noble's fate, even though Edith had never met or talked to any of them.

Iron Axe asked after a moment of silence, "Is the form... accurate?"

As the commander-in-chief of the First Army, he understood the importance of work efficiency and knew very well how much time this form could save them. Most of the ships were borrowed from the Chambers of Commerce at the Fjords, so he should wind up the campaign at his earliest, even if the demons were not planning to erect the Obelisk around the Impassable Mountain Range.

"There could be some errors here and there, and I'm not sure if 50 is a correct cut-off grade. However, considering we have limited time, I'll leave the details to your discretion," Edith said as she sipped her tea leisurely. "The General Staff is only providing counsels here."

Iron Axe turned to the last page of the form and found a list of cities that Edith had already graded. All the information was obtained from the Kingdom of Dawn, and the top city below the cut-off grade was precisely the Sedimentation Bay, the first stop of their journey.

Before Iron Axe took his leave, he asked one last question.

"Aren't there any nobles who haven't fallen behind?"

"Of course there's such a possibility," Edith replied smilingly as she played with her hair. "However, in that case, you'll soon find him out even without this form because this person must be like me."

Iron Axe breathed out a sigh as he came out of his reveries and walked toward the campsite of the First Army. As Edith had said, nobles did not pose problems. The problem was how to mobilize civilians in an orderly and efficient manner.

Nevertheless, within two days, the dock of the Sedimentation Bay had been packed with thousands of people waiting to board the ships. Not only Iron Axe and Remy but also Jean Bate was taken aback by such a huge number.

The First Army, therefore, had to postpone their departure to manage these civilians.

"What's going on?" Iron Axe inquired Remy. "Did you exaggerate His Majesty's promise?"

"No, I know I don't have the authority to do that," Remy said while shaking his head. "I strictly follow the procedure set out by the Administrative Office. It really depends on how many people the local lord could persuade. The baron is apparently not so highly respected among his people compared to His Majesty, so I assume there would only be around 300-500 civilians."

"Now it's 20 times that number," Iron Axe remarked. Obviously it was good news to have so many immigrants all of a sudden, but he was also a little disturbed by such an unexpected high volume. Graycastle was, after all, a distant, unknown country for citizens of the Kingdom of Wolfheart. Naturally, Iron Axe suspected that someone was behind all this, who persuaded these people to abandon their native towns and venture into a journey to a completely foreign country.

"There could be only one explanation," Remy said meditatively, "that they're all refugees."

Refugees had nothing to lose. As long as they saw a ray of hope, they would rush for it.

"But these people are all freemen living in villages and towns near the Sedimentation Bay."

"Yes, they are, but my men heard some interesting rumors when they visited those towns. For example, the Redstone Gate Family, who holds an ancient grudge against the baron, plans to reduce subjects to slaves after they take over the Sedimentation Bay. Another rumor I heard is about a monster that takes humans for food in the mountainous area in the north. Some towns were ravaged and human remains littered the roads. Now, this monster is coming to the southeast. There are many other similar, convincing rumors that perturb the community. I guess this is why so many people choose to leave. If they don't go now, they'll become refugees, too."

Astounded, Iron Axe asked, "When did this happen?"

"At least a month and a half ago, not long after we set out from Neverwinter," Remy replied while stroking his chin. "Aren't we lucky?"

"Not at all," Iron Axe thought darkly. Someone was apparently inducing panic to the public, and this person also knew the purpose of the First Army pretty well.

Who was disseminating the news? Why did he help Graycastle? Was he a friend or a foe? A multitude of questions overwhelmed Iron Axe.

Until a soldier came in.

"Sir, someone asked me to hand this letter to you."

"Who?" Iron Axe asked as he took the envelope.

"He didn't leave his name. He's tiny though," the soldier replied. "But he told me the letter was given to him by someone else as well. Perhaps, the writer of this letter doesn't want to be known. I checked it already. There's nothing but the letter in there."

It was an ordinary burlap envelope much cheaper than one made of parchment or leather. Many shops sold this type of envelope. It was not sealed with wax but was laid open very casually. Iron Axe took the letter out of the envelope, and to his dismay, the letter was written on a piece of black, refined paper normally inaccessible to civilians.

He turned over the letter and found a line printed in gold.

"This is a present from your most loyal servant. I hope you like it."

Chapter 1204: The Ridge of the Continent

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The temperature in the mountain range soon dropped after the sunset.

"Time to find a place to spend the night," Lightning thought. The temperature here varied dramatically between day and night. It was scorching during the day, and she would get burned easily if not covered with anything. When night fell, the wuthering wind would take away all the heat, and she would have probably been frozen to death if she had continued to sleep in trees like she had done in the Misty Forest.

Therefore, Lightning must find a shelter before the darkness pressed in.

"Let's call it a day," Lightning spoke over the Sigil of Listening. "I'll find a shelter and you go bring some food."

Maggie could not respond when she was flying, but Lightning knew she heard her.

She then dropped and flew very low above the ground. Agatha had reminded her several times before she had left Neverwinter that when she was looking for the demons, she had to either fly very high or very low to avoid trespassing God's Stone mines. It was also not advisable to change routes very often. Otherwise, once entering the God's Stone mines, nobody would be able to save her.

Lightning strictly followed Agatha's instruction. In this undulating mountain range, she could rely on nobody, so she must take good care of both herself and Maggie.

Since they had paid particular attention to possible shelters while she had been conducting the search, Lightning soon found a cave halfway up the mountain. A forest of stones stretched away below her, each stone the size of Neverwinter. Lightning suddenly had a strange feeling that these stones and mountains were sculpted by a giant visible hand.

Streams were interspersed between the mountains, which torrented down upon a heavy rain or flood. The weather varied significantly in this mountainous area. More often than not it was clear and sunny on one side and stormy and gloomy on the other. Inexperienced explorers would be very likely flushed away by an unexpected flood at night if they pitched their tents on the mountainside. Therefore, it was very important to pick a highpoint of the land to spend the night.

Lightning had witnessed several floods since her entry to the ridge of the continent.

Further, unlike other mountains that were usually comprised of sharp and steep precipices, the mountains here were mostly composed of boulders with many holes in them, as though these rocks were some solidified fluids.

Fortunately, round as they were, the stones were still robust enough to form a shelter.

The cave she discovered this time was pretty big, around 100 square meters, littered with twigs and weeds, which Lightning inferred were the remains of bird nests. After confirming there was no potential danger in the cave, Lightning informed Maggie of her location and started to tidy up the cave.

When the darkness became impenetrable, Maggie, in the form of a snowy owl, fluttered into the cave and restored its human shape. She held up a package aloft like offering a present and said, "Look what I've got, coo!"

Lightning took the package and found a chicken and four giant bird eggs in it , a very rare finding in the Impassable Mountain Range. Even Maggie, an experienced hunter, would not always return with such fruitful results.

"Good job!"

Lightning stroked Maggie's head who returned a triumphant smile, "Haha."

A bonfire soon sprang into life. Lightning built a stove with the mound of earth collected from the foot of mountain to shade the firelight, covered the chicken with mud and then tossed the whole creature into the fire along with the bird eggs.

Dinner was ready 30 minutes later.

They had cooked like this numerous times in the Misty Forest and were now quite good at it.

The rich flavor of the chicken immediately escaped as they broke the hardened mud.

A sheen of oil glazed off the chicken, and the aroma of the spices filled the entire cave. After removing the skin, they saw the tender chicken meat beneath. The chicken was not overcooked at all, its meat white and juicy.

The pair devoured the bird eggs and the chicken ravenously and even ate the chicken bones.

Maggie belched in satisfaction and said, "Nothing could be better than eating our own food, coo."

Lightning cast Maggie a glance. She still remembered Maggie's indignant protest against her "eating a bird" in the beginning.

Lightning shook her head in amusement and asked, "Any luck today? Except for food though."

"Well, no, coo... the landscapes are quite the same here. If there were demons, I would spot them immediately, coo."

It would be really hard to spot God's Stone mines buried deep down underneath the ground from above. Lightning wondered where the supporting God's Punishment Witches currently were. If they could point out a rough direction for her, it would make her life a lot easier.

She pointed at the cave and said, "Well, since you had no discovery, make me a bed then."

"OK, coo," Maggie replied as she paced to the designated location with her long white hair streaming behind her and then turned into a Devilbeast.

Lightning then extinguished the fire and lay down on Maggie's stomach. Compared to a sleeping bag, Maggie was a better shelter. Her stomach, as warm as a furnace, could shield her from cold winds and keep her warm during the night.

The only drawback of this method was that the skin of the Devilbeast was a little scruffy compared to Lorgar's soft fur.

"Are you not sleeping?" Maggie asked as she saw Lightning take out the Stone of Lighting.

"I need to make a journal entry to record our journey today. It won't be long. You sleep first."

"Alright," Maggie answered gruffly. After a long silence, she suddenly mumbled, "You're going to take me with you for the future exploration, right?"

Momentarily stunned, Lightning said in a gentle voice, "Yes, of course."

"I'll take care of you since Ashes is already gone," said Lightning within herself.

Maggie finally fell asleep after receiving an affirmative answer.

Lightning sat there for a long time before she took out her journal out of her bag.

It had been ten days since they had entered the mountainous area in the north of the Kingdom of Everwinter. They had covered a distance of 120 kilometers. The deeper they probed into the Impassable Mountain Range, the smaller she felt. This was an area never intruded by human beings, and it was in here she had seen a breathtaking view. The forest of stones as vast as the Fertile Plains, the icefall, which was a sheer drop from Heaven to the ocean in the northeast, the sea of clouds that spiraled up, as well as the great rapture in the center of the ridge of the continent... Lightning now came to the realization that the Impassable Mountain Range that separated the four kingdoms was simply a branch of this mountain range. Those incredible scenes, all hidden behind the crests of the mountains, were inaccessible unless she flew over the steep cliffs.

Lightning now understood why her father was addicted to exploration.

Human beings were too little and insignificant compared to this world. She could only become stronger by getting to know more about it.

To become an explorer was the best decision she had ever made in her life.

Of course, she could explore the whole world later. Lightning knew she was now on a mission. If she flew too far away from the Kingdom of Everwinter, she would not only hinder the exploration but also cause unnecessary trouble to the supporting team. The "Roland" should have now almost reached the port of the Kingdom of Everwinter.

Lightning cast a glance at her hand drawn map and rested her eyes on the great rapture.

It seemed to be a protruding plain in the middle of the stone forest, but it was hollow inside, so Lightning was not sure how deep it was.

She could discern the fault underneath the crust.

If she still could not find traces of God's Stone mines or the demons, she would probably return to the Kingdom of Everwinter and meet with the supporting team to discuss the next step.

Chapter 1205: A Dangerous Signal

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The next morning, Lightning disclosed her plan to Maggie. After a brief discussion, they decided to conduct another search in the stone forest and then head to the rapture as fast as they could.

They would have to return to the Snow Ridge in the Kingdom of Everwinter and complete the topographic map of this area before meeting the Taquila witches.

The sun broke over the horizon, the mountains were wrapped in rags of mist, and the rivers crisscrossed in the frost. There were traces left by the flood last night. As the roads began its winding ascent to the crests of the mountains, they saw a vast land of whiteness lay stretched before them. The distant rapture, completely covered by snow, resembled a giant porcelain bowl laid upside down.

It was estimated that the Kingdom of Everwinter was around 300 kilometers away, about the same size of the entire Southernmost Region. According to the map of the Land of Dawn drafted by the Union, the rapture was the offspring of various extinct volcanos.

Lightning had seen eruptions of active volcanos on the Searing Flame Islands, but they were nothing compared to the volcanos here.

Two hours later, the Exploration Group reached the rapture area.

They finally saw the whole landscape that lay out magnificently before them.

"It's so... so massive," Maggie exclaimed while flapping her wings. "I feel this hole could house an entire kingdom."

Lightning nodded in approval. The rapture was actually not a fault as she had thought but a huge scar that ripped the earth part. An immense invisible force underneath the ground had pushed the earth plates away from each other and formed cliffs on either side of the rapture.

If this "scar" was indeed the result of volcanic activities, what a huge eruption it would have been?

Lightning and Maggie dropped and landed at two to three kilometers from the rapture. As usual, Maggie approached the rapture first, for she could merge herself perfectly into the surrounding environment without raising any suspicions of lurking enemies.

"Listen," Lightning warned Maggie, "don't go too deep into the rapture. Just take a peep at the entrance and come back. If you find anything out of character, report to me. Never go in there on your own — "

"Got it. I'll report to the captain first before making the next move," Maggie cut across her. "I know. I know, coo. You told me a lot of times... You sound like His Majesty, coo!"

"Er, really? Ahem, anyway, it doesn't hurt to reiterate! I'll stay here and conduct a preliminary search in this area. I'll go no farther than one kilometer. Remember this particular spot, and we'll meet here in 30 minutes. Understood?" Lightning said while scratching the back of her head, a little embarrassed. She remembered that Roland used to always remind her not to act alone. Because of this, Lightning had complained to her group members a lot, and boasted that an excellent explorer was born to know how to make correct judgements, and that such warnings were completely unnecessary. Now, she realized how childish she had been.

"No problem, coo!"

"Good. Off you go," Lightning said while patting Maggie on the shoulder.

"Maggie, go!" Maggie yelled excitedly and flew toward the center of the rapture.

Lightning's eyes followed Maggie until the latter disappeared from her sight. She then started to survey the surroundings.

Snowy owls were a type of birds commonly seen in this area. They belonged to the owl family. They had an excellent eye sight and were thus active during the day and at night. As long as Maggie proceeded with caution, it was not likely that she would expose herself. This district was a bleak emptiness of icebergs, without the slightest trace of wild animals. Maggie would be able to spot a demon immediately, if there was one.

In consideration of these factors, the first place Maggie ought to look for should be hiding places. She had to think critically and solve problems herself.

However, within five minutes, Lightning heard something flutter above her head.

Lightning looked up with a start and saw Maggie plunge frantically and throw herself onto her.

"D-demons, coo!" Maggie shouted.

The words sent a faint shiver through Lightning's heart. Were there God's stone mines here? She thus asked, "What did you find?"

"A giant Eye Demon that is now lying on its stomach beneath the cliff, coo!" Maggie demonstrated with both her hands and feet. "I just passed the rapture and looked into its eyes!"

That meant the Eye Demon had also seen her.

Lightning was glad that she was not the one who had discovered the Eye Demon. A snowy owl would not catch the attention of the Eye Demon.

"Then? Did you cry out?" Lightning pursued.

"Of course not. I'm a seasoned bird, no, a seasoned explorer, coo!" Maggie swelled up. "I didn't even blink. I just pretended to be looking around. Then I averted my eyes, coo! I bet it had already put me out of its mind, coo!"

Then Lightning saw what had happened in her mind's eye.

A snowy owl stared at an Eye Demon and turned away...

"Oh, no!" Lightning snatched up Maggie and streaked toward one of the shelters they had previously found.

"Coo?" Maggie asked in bewilderment.

The shelter was an ice cave a few hundred meters away hidden behind rocks. The cave had not yet been filled with snow, so it was large enough to accommodate one person. Lightning rushed into the cave, poked half of her head out of the cave and looked up.

A moment later, a queer, shiny "door" suddenly appeared in midair.

Then a demon walked out from behind the door and stood suspended right above the rapture. Lightning felt her chest constrict involuntarily, as though she were facing Ursrook again.

The demon looked around cautiously before it dived. For a split second, Lightning felt all the blood within her freeze. It took her a great deal of efforts to suppress the urge to escape. However, she managed to stay put, as the demon was not aiming in her direction.

The demon plummeted to the ground covered in snow, exhaling clouds of white flurries. When it straightened up again, Lightning saw a snowy owl in its clawed hand.

Lightning swallowed hard, her hands involuntarily reaching for her own chest.

Fortunately, that snowy owl was not Maggie.

The demon gazed at the petrified snowy owl for a while and shook its head in disappointment before it released the bird. The owl screeched, soared into the sky, and disappeared from their sight.

The demon did not linger. It stretched out its hand and ripped open the strange "door" and vanished in front of the two witches.

Lightning heaved a deep sigh.

They were safe for now.

"Coo... what do we do next?" Maggie asked, a little crestfallen, for she had realized her mistake.

Lightning would have taken another route to sneak into the rapture in the past. The rapture was so massive that it was impossible for the Eye Demon to cover every inch of the area. As an explorer, Lightning would like to be the first person who made the discovery.

Nevertheless, she was now not only an explorer but also the captain of the Neverwinter Exploration Group, as well as the scout for the First Army.

Whatever was hidden underneath the rapture, the presence of the Eye Demon and the Senior Demon indicated potential danger!

She must return to Neverwinter as soon as possible to inform King Roland Wimbledon.

"Let's go to the Snow Ridge and meet up with the Taquila witches," Lightning said through clenched teeth. "This mountain range is no longer safe. Someone has clearly set foot in this area."

Chapter 1206: Just A Breath Away

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

"Have you found anything?"

An upgraded subordinate came up to Hackzord as it revealed from the Distortion Door.

"No..." Hackzord said while studying its hands attentively. "Probably the Eye Demon guard made a mistake."

"That does happen occasionally. You could take a rest at the Red Mist Pond, sir. I'll alert you if anything comes up." The subordinate paused for a second before it went on, "Sir Valkries always bathes in this pond. I think... you could also relax your muscles in there every now and then."

This was a pretty good idea. Hackzord did want to indulge in such a mundane pleasure and explore the beauty of the Realm of Mind. However, the king would not put blames on the Nightmare if anything went wrong with the plan for the Western Front. Instead, Hackzord was the one who would bear all the consequences.

After a moment of silence, Hackzord answered, "It would be too much for you to connect four Eye Demon guards at the same time. We've entered the most crucial stage of our plan, so I'd better monitor the situation myself. This is the last stronghold on the Western Front, and we mustn't fail the king."

The subordinate's manner instantly tightened into formality as it heard the king's name. It replied fervently, "You're right, sir! I shall not let the king down!"

Valkries was the one that let its guard down.

Hackzord thought to himself expressionlessly.

After Ursrook's tragic death at Taquila, this mountainous area became the focus of the Western Front plan. Hackzord exercised all its efforts to monitor this district. It had persuaded the front to spare four precious Eye Demon guards to monitor this area so that Hackzord could remain constant vigilance about lurking enemies.

Eye Demons, whose vision would not be restricted by distance, lighting conditions, or the size of objects, were the most astute observers. They could immediately sense enemies and inform the demons connected to them.

As the connection required a great deal of magic power, only upgraded ones were qualified to connect with Eye Demons. The world that Eye Demons saw were extremely complicated. They would not be able to mobilize themselves if they accepted all the information they received. Therefore, Eye Demons would normally conduct a preliminary screening and evaluate each creature they beheld in advance. Only those who posed a real threat or act strangely would be informed to the connected demons.

Hackzord had sensed unusual movements just a moment ago.

Like the subordinate had said, Eye Demons did make errors from time to time. This was because creatures tended to have their own unique ways to respond to nature, and not all of their behaviors were comprehensible. There was, for example, someone as inscrutable as the king, and also eccentrics like the Mask. Eye Demons, which lacked independent and critical thinking skills, sacrificed a lot for the thousands of eyes that encrusted their heads. As such, even though they possessed enormous magic power, not a single Eye Demon had upgraded to a Senior Lord over the past thousands of years.

Nevertheless, Eye Demons were still deemed as a rare species by the clan, whose birth rate was only a little higher than those of the Hatcher and the Mother of Soul.

Hackzord changed the subject. "How's the revival of the Birth Tower going?"

"It's almost done. Everything's going well."

"Very good. Take me there."

"Yes, my lord!"

Due to the impact of God's Stones, Hackzord could not go straight to the bottom of the valley and had to slowly make its descent through a flight of stairs.

As they went down, the surroundings gradually turned into a whirl of crimson. The air was impregnated with the Red Mist, and the towering precipices formed a giant vessel, a natural container chiseled out of rocks, where the Red Mist could easily accumulate. After more than half a year of accumulation, the lower part of the rapture was now permeated with the thick, dense Red Mist that could support thousands of lives.

However, Hackzord needed more than that.

Only when they erected the Birth Tower from the God's Stone mine could their kind truly survive on this land, without fearing a sudden disruption of the Red Mist supply.

The sunlight was completely replaced by a ghostly blue-purple light at the very bottom of the rapture. A stone tower stood magnificently before Hackzord among the God's Stone of Punishment Pillars.

A faint tremor of excitement smote upon Hackzord.

"No matter how many times I view it, it always awes me," the guard commented. "Before, we were only able to erect the tower when the Origin of Magic appeared."

"Yes, but it isn't the second Battle of Divine Will anymore," Hackzord said with a nod.

This particular Birth Tower was actually not supposed to be here because it did not grow out of the God's Stone mine but was an old one that had been set up a while ago. Although it currently relied on a huge base to support its weight, and its blotchy gray color signified a state of inactiveness, Hackzord knew this was just temporary. Soon, the tower would be reconnected to the God's Stone mine via the Mother of Soul.

This was the upgrade they had obtained from the legacy shards. Over the past 400 years, their understanding of magic power and magic stones had experienced various drastic changes. The most important change was that they slowly became less independent of the Red Mist.

Nonetheless, human beings also made remarkable progress.

Hackzord approached the tower base and gazed at the dormant Mother of Soul.

The Mother of Soul was the origin of everything, the most important individual out of the whole clan. It would only reach its maturity when magic power reached its peak and when the Divine Will emerged. By that time, the Mother of Soul would be fused with the raw God's Punishment Stone. Within a few years, the God's Stone mine would transform into a high tower that would further produce more Red Mist via magic power.

Yet their new technology had considerably shortened this lengthy process. A fast-growing Birth Tower meant much less time to prepare for the war. As they would soon have ample Red Mist, they could even use the Red Mist as a weapon and quickly convert the enemy's territory into their own.

There were nearly 100 Inferior Demons taking care of the Mother of Soul. They cleaned and fed her. In fact, the bottom of the great rapture was filled with thousands of such Inferior Demons. Through the window of the tower base, Hackzord saw those demons busy excavating the ground and transporting supplies. Some upgraded demons, on the other hand, were issuing commands on their Bogle Beasts. In the center of the rapture stood the symbotic demon newly created by the Mask. These powerful war machines would swarm toward their enemies upon an order. For a moment, Hackzord had an illusion that this place was the real front.

In fact, this rapture was, in a sense, a frontline. If they failed to stop human beings on this continent, their future would become dismally uncertain. They had to defeat the mankind here to save their civilization.

Therefore, they must win this battle for the king!

Chapter 1207: A New Idea

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

In Neverwinter, Graycastle.

Since the Longsong Cannons were not portable, the Artillery Battalion had become exceptionally unoccupied these days compared to the Gun Battalion that had set out for the Kingdom of Wolfheart and the Kingdom of Everwinter to execute Roland's immigration plan. Apart from the daily training and the harvest, off-duty soldiers all went back home to spend time with their families.

Van'er also chose to go home. As the battalion commander, he rarely had free time these days, so Van'er treasured this rare opportunity to unite with his families. He also took the advantage of this break calling on neighbors and old friends. Since alcohol was expressively forbidden in the army, the only time Van'er could indulge in relvery was when he was off duty.

After years of development, businesses in Neverwinter were currently far more dynamic and diverse than those in the old king's city. Under the influence of Roland's commercial district plan, the premises on either side of the street had now been in extremely high demand. Two-story premises were soon let out to shop owners and foreign merchants and were subsequently transformed into hotels, restaurants and taverns. Commodies from various parts of world were being constantly shipped to Neverwinter for sale. These shops supplemented the Convenience Market that mainly provided citizens with life necessities and staples.

Van'er was impressed with the king's foresight as he wandered about on the street while surveying peddling vendors. The city was busy but not congested. Everything was in a strict order: peddlers set up their booths in a designated area; pedestrians walked on the walkway paved with slabs; carriages ran in the middle of the road.

Van'er remembered that someone had raised questions as to why they needed to broaden up the road in the beginning the construction work. Many people questioned about the necessity to create two respective lanes for pedestrians and wagons. Now, it appeared that it was quite a wise decision. Van'er suspected that Roland might have foreseen the future beforehand.

After passing two main driveways, Van'er reached his destination, the tavern "Lucky Shell".

As soon as he entered the store, a person limped up to him from behind the bar and greeted him. "Sir, there you are!"

"Just Van'er. This isn't the army," Van'er said smilingly while pulling the bartender into a crushing hug. "How's your business going? It looks good, eh?"

This person was known as "Iron Crutch". Half a year ago during that fierce night battle against the demons at Tower Station No. 1, a spear had penetrated Iron Crutch's abdomen and leg when he had been charging at the demons to retrieve the artillery field. He lost his consciousness on the spot. Although Nana later saved him, he still lost his right leg and had to replace it with an iron stick. That was how he got his nickname.

Iron Crutch thus retired from the military service. He opened this "Lucky Shell" in the eastern city with the benefits received from the government and his salaries, and this tavern became where the First Army often met each other during their break.

"Since I'm a retired veteran, the rent is relatively low for me. I can manage," Iron Crutch said while messaging his hands in excitement. "If only you could come here a little more often."

Van'er replied, "Then you'll have to wait for my retirement or when I'm like you. By the way, Are Rhone brothers here?"

"They're both upstairs. Let me take you up there."

"No, that's fine. Don't worry about me. Come drink with us when you aren't so busy."

"Sounds good," Iron Crutch agreed pleasantly.

Van'er went up stairs and immediately saw his old friends sitting at a round table. Jop. Cat's Claw, Rodney and Nelson were all there. These people used to shudder at charging knights when the Artillery Battalion had first been founded. Now, they had all elevated themselves to military officers that the whole Artillery Battalion relied on. Because each of them had their own duties, they had not drunk together in the tavern for a while.

Van'er joined them. They exchanged opinions on various matters ardently. The most frequent topic of discussion was naturally the army and the upcoming Battle of Divine Will.

According to the king, this would be an unprecedentedly massive war that would involve the entire continent. They were not certain whether they could see each other again after the war ended.

"We're actually quite lucky. At least, we don't need to fight those monsters directly," Rodney drained his glass and sighed. "If the artillery is defeated, then we pretty much lose the battle."

"The problem is that we don't know what new tricks demons will play... Remember that unexpected night attack at Tower Station No.1?" Cat's Claw commented while shrugging. "I hope our soldiers could learn to cope with the demons themselves. They shouldn't wait for the Gun Battalion or the Special Unit of Strategies and Tactics to rescue them."

Everyone assented in earnest. "Exactly. If only we have powerful weapons as well. Revolving rifles could kill knights but not the demons."

"Drop it. I've heard that the army is going to use bolt rifles in the future. There'll be no revolvers anymore soon."

"Really? Commander, are you positive?"

Van'er confirmed with a nod in response to the others' inquiring look, "The First Unit and the Sixth Unit have already switched to the new weapons. It may take a while for all of us to have one due to limited production."

Jop said, frowning, "I tried the new gun once. It's powerful and accurate, but it's too slow for a close-range attack. Can't the Artillery Battalion keep using the old weapons?"

"I'm afraid not. The management team has made the decision," Van'er replied while pointing at the ceiling. "We use traditional black powder to operate revolvers. The bullet will be pretty much the same, so those who used to produce black powder could now help with the bullet production."

"Then... maybe we should ask Sir Iron Axe to persuade His Majesty to design a new weapon for us?"

"Forget it," Nelson snorted. "Brian will definitely butt in!"

"Yes, the Artillery Battalion only needs cannons," Cat's Claw said with a perfect imitation of Brian's tone. "Don't you often say that the barrels should be as large as possible? Leave those tiny ones to us Gun Battalion. Lads, drink on!"

The group of officers roared with laughter. Only Van'er remained silent. He gazed at his glass, apparently lost in thought.

"Commander?"

Van'er stroked his chin and said slowly, "What if we create a weapon on our own?"

"What weapon? A new flintlock?" Cat's Claw asked, his brows raised. "Commander, you're drunk, aren't you?"

"Shut up! I'm not sure if you have noticed it. Both the grapeshot guns used by the Special Unit of Strategies and Tactics and the Mark I type HMGs operated by the Gun Battalion are equipped with an air duct for steady firing," Van'er said meditatively. "I've seen many disposed weapons. Although their structures are not always the same, they have pretty much the same mechanism."

"Er... Really? How come I don't know?"

"That's why you aren't the commander," Rodney said sagely while twitching his lips. "Having said that, we would need manpower and supplies to create weapons. Sir Iron Axe doesn't charge the plant that manufactures weapons."

"No, we aren't making weapons from scratch but are simply upgrading the ones we currently have," Van'er said, feeling more confident about what he was saying. "It won't involve the plant or the Administrative Office. We just need a skillful worker."

Cat's Claw, Rodney and Nelson all rested their eyes on Jop.

Jop sighed deeply and raised his hands. "Fine. My brother is working in the industrial zone. His job is to process and assemble steam engines. I'll take you there tomorrow."

Chapter 1208: Van'er's Gun

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The next day at noon, they went to the Second Mechanic Plant in the industrial zone with Jop.

After hearing the purpose of their trip, Jop's brother, Lafite, showed great interest in Van'er's proposal. He took Van'er's rifle and fiddled the weapon affectionately before he asked, "Are we really allowed to do this? I was a miner, and what I'm now doing is simply some manual labor like sharpening and slicing. If I screw it up..."

"Brother!" Jop stopped him indignantly.

"One or two shouldn't be a problem. Guns break easily after all since we use them a lot during the training," Van'er said. "However, if you break a lot, then it means that my method doesn't work. I won't blame you."

"I see," Lafite said while nodding in excitement. "Then leave it to me! I'll do my best, as machine tools in the plant aren't always available."

"Your brother seems to like flintlocks very much," Cat's Claw whispered to Jop.

"That's nothing unusual," Rodney rejoined. "Who doesn't like powerful weapons? We used to flail swords and spears. Now we fire cannons and guns."

Van'er also thought the same way. After witnessing the true power of the 12-pound field artillery, he gradually fell in love with weapons. Van'er opened the leather bag his friends brought with them, took out a disabled HMG and then handed a metal tube to Lafite. Van'er said, "Let's begin."

...

The barrel of the rifle was soon fixed to a drilling machine.

Lafite turned on the machine, aligned the drill with the mark on the barrel, and slowly moved the drill downwards. When the drill touched the barrel, the metal tube splintered into numerous tiny chips.

It was a new experience for Van'er. Although he knew that both the steam engine and the Longsong Cannons were made of metal ingots, it was his first time witnessing the actual production. He was amazed when seeing the robust iron gradually melt and dissolve into various shapes.

According to Lafite, the machine tools in the Second Mechanic Plant were all in their third generation powered by Dawn I. Compared to the old machine tools driven by steam engines, the new ones were much more steady and quiet. In addition, they could start working anytime. Some skillful workers could even carve intricate patterns on a tiny iron rod the size of a fingernail.

Yet Van'er did not require such exquisite skills. After reflecting upon his proposal for a night, he redrafted his plan. The principle was to use the least resources to attain his goal. The transformation of the gun should be simple and must not interfere with the daily operation of the plant. As such, he brought the air duct of Mark I, in a hope of simplifying the procedure and saving time.

With a sample air duct, they could then easily ignite gunpowder. The problem, nonetheless, was how to keep up a steady fire.

Van'er had developed a great interest in the HMGs used by the Gun Battalion a long time ago. During the war of the North Slope, he had played with those machine guns many times. One thing that Van'er was certain was that Mark I was much larger than rifles because it had a much more complicated recoil system. Further, the loading systems of the two weapons were also quite different. Machine guns required a cartridge, whereas rifles were only equipped with a clip. Therefore, it was impossible to copy the whole model.

Even if his method worked, Iron Axe and Brian would not allow the artillery to use heavy machine gun parts.

The best way to upgrade rifles was to just upgrade the barrel.

"That's pretty much it..." Lafite said as he cleansed the drill and compared the air duct and the rifle against the sunlight. "These two barrels should be about the same length once we cut off the excessive part."

"Don't connect them as yet," Van'er stopped Lafite as he produced a piece of paper from his pocket and spread it out. "I want you to help me to make this spare part as well."

There was a crude diagram on the paper. The part was in the shape of an arc, about one finger long and two fingers wide, with a groove in the middle.

"What's that?" the other officers asked curiously. "It doesn't look like a gun part."

Van'er was not sure if this part would really work. It was simply one of his wild ideas that had yet been verified. However, he must not retract, so he said, "Ahem... if everything goes well, I believe this new part will replace our hands."

...

Five days later, many soldiers from the Artillery Battalion gathered at the First Army's shooting range.

They had learned from their superiors that a new flintlock that would enable the artillery to keep up a steady fire was currently under test. Unlike all the other weapons widely used by the army, this weapon was invented by Commander Van'er instead of His Majesty. Many soldiers were intrigued by the news and came to see what this new weapon looked like during their break.

To their dismay, the weapon under test could indeed fire steadily, although it did, from time to time, got jammed. As long as the user continuously pulled the trigger, the gun could eject multiple bullets at a time.

Unlike the revolving rifles that could only fire five bullets, this upgraded one could fire 20, which would almost rival an HMG if multiple such upgraded guns fired at the same time.

"I can't believe that you really made it," Cat's Claw remarked impressively. "Now I know why Sir Iron Axe chose you to be the commander."

"His Majesty taught me all this. Doesn't he always say that we need to apply what we learn from books to actual work? I simply did what His Majesty told us to," Van'er said triumphantly. He had not expected that his plan would work so well. Within just five days, he had created a new weapon. Next, they would only need to make a few adjustments and the Artillery Battalion would be able to increase the power of their guns significantly at a minimal cost.

"Are you Commander Van'er?" someone asked suddenly.

"Yes, you are..." Van'er said as he turned around.

"I'm Danny, a member of the sniper team," the man said with a smile. "I saw a lot of people here, so I came to see what's going on. I'm on duty today... Can I try out your new weapon?"

"The sniper team?" Jop echoed, a little surprised, and then cast a glance at Van'er, "Chief — "

Van'er knew that every single member of the sniper team was an elite picked by Brian from the Gun Battalion. The sniper team made its fame through the battle against the church at the Coldwind Ridge. They received a medal from His Majesty for their outstanding performance. They were the best among the best and were also highly respected among the soldiers. If this new weapon caught the attention of the sniper team, wouldn't there be a possibility that the Artillery Battalion could finally overpower the Gun Battalion?

In response to Jop and Cat's Claw's eager look, Van'er replied with a faint smile, "Of course. Please go ahead."

Chapter 1209: Testing Result

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Danny took the gun and instantly noticed that the center of the gravity had changed. The gun was, overall, heavier than a regular rifle. Apart from the second tube installed to the barrel, this new gun looked no different than an ordinary bolt rifle used by most of the soldiers in the Gun Battalion, although it was not as well-made as his own high-precision rifle. The biggest change was that this additional metal tube ran all the way to the bottom of the barrel and was connected to the bolt.

This must be the reason that the gun could keep up a steady fire.

Danny took the aim and pulled the triggered. However, instead of locking his eyes on the muzzle, he gazed at the iron tube on one side of the barrel.

As the gun trembled when the bullet escaped from the muzzle, something extraordinary happened. It was just a split second, but Danny noticed the change in the bolt. The rod in the iron tube was pushed forward and then retracted along with the metal shard attached to its end.

This metal shard was normally fixed to the bolt. If someone tried to forcibly pull it, it would get jammed and break the rod. However, the groove in the middle of the shard enabled the bolt to retract and thereby unlock it.

Then, the whole process reversed. The rod retracted to the tube and the bolt returned to its original spot. The metal shard slid back to the bottom and locked the bore again.

This was such an ingenious design!

This additional part was quite self-explanatory. Even a lay man like Danny could immediately understand the mechanism behind it. Basically, the rod in the second iron tube replaced manual labor. What was clever about this design was that the rod completed four steps at a time, namely, pushing, pulling, lifting and pressing. Without any external force, the gun was automatically restored.

Danny fired all the bullets, mesmerized by the pungent smell of gunpowder and that familiar voice that always visited him on the battlefield.

"You missed one shot out of 20," Malt said. "Not used to the new weapon?"

"I haven't got used to it yet. See if I miss any in the next round."

"See what?" a surprised voice said to him.

Danny pulled himself back to the present. He suddenly realized that this was not a battlefield, and a group of onlookers were watching him in the shooting range. Danny looked toward the confused Artillery Battalion commander as he rose and said while shaking his head, "No... I'm just mumbling."

"You're really an excellent sniper. 19 out of 20. That's really something, and you're still not satisfied," Van'er said while patting Danny on the shoulder. He then asked hopefully, "So... what do you think of this gun?"

Danny knew about the competition between the Artillery Battalion and the Gun Battalion. Nevertheless, both of the two battalions served the king. He thus said honestly, "It's perfect, except it's a little unstable and heavy. I wish the sniper team could also have an upgraded weapon like this, if possible."

If truth be told, the gun was as accurate as regular rifles when shooting targets were at 50 and 100 meters. Although it was a lot heavier than a rifle, the sniper team and the Artillery Battalion were not required to fire on standby or carry the weapon on the go."

The greatest strength of this upgraded gun was that it enabled soldiers to keep up a steady fire. Since the current gun could not fire steadily, soldiers had to readjust their position and took the aim again after they missed their target. The repositioning normally took a few seconds, and more often than not, they lost track of the target. Therefore, they fired less frequently than ordinary soldiers. However, the upgraded gun minimized the readjustment and enabled soldiers to fire again immediately. This weapon would thus be very helpful for a massive warfare.

Van'er was pleased to hear that his work received some kind of acknowledgment. He grinned, "It's just a preliminary design. If you could help us further improve the weapon, I would feel more comfortable when I talk to Sir Iron Axe."

Van'er believed if the sniper team used the gun designed by the Artillery Battalion, then surely he outperformed Brian.

Danny, on the other hand, agreed to help Van'er purely out of his person affection toward firearms that could efficiently kill demons, the smell of gunpowder, and the voice of his ghost friend, Malt. Danny thus said, "I'm happy to be of service, Mr. Commander."

The two of them smiled at each other and reached an agreement.

...

Roland learned about this new weapon a few days later.

As an increasing number of soldiers from the Artillery Battalion visited the Second Mechanic Plant, the superintendent of the plant reported the incident to the Administrative Office, who later forwarded the news to the Minister of Engineering, Anna.

Roland was greatly amused by the duplicate sample created by Anna. The design was crude. Although the gun could fire steadily, it would easily break down since the additional metal tube was exposed in the air. The gun thus required extensive maintenance.

Having said that, the artillery, after all, did not need to fire very frequently.

"What do you think?" Anna asked smilingly.

"Well... there's a lot that can be done, but it's a good sign," Roland said casually. "At least, it shows that soldiers start to think independently and know what kind of weapon they really need. The strengths of this gun are also very obvious, which are minimal costs and simple alteration."

There would certainly be a huge increase in the consumption of bullets if the whole army started to use this new weapon. Fortunately, frontline soldiers who mainly relied on HMGs did not necessarily need to fire successively.

Well, in that case, let's help them," Anna said, nodding.

The design of the weapon was soon finalized with Anna's assistance. The bolt and piston were replaced by a more flexible latch structure. Its joint was encased in a shell to stablize the weapon, so the gun would not get easily jammed. After a part of the air duct was cut off, the weapon was officially upgraded. Roland advised that the new rifle should be named after Van'er.

Soon after the news was announced, the Ministry of Engineering suddenly received tons of recommendations and feedback.

Roland was pleased with the turn of the event.

He finally saw the result of universal education.

The success of his education plan excited Roland even more than the new weapon itself.

Also, there was another piece of good news.

Celine told him that there was a breakthrough in the research of the Magic Ceremony Cube.

She found a way to significantly reduce the consumption of uranium when she was making the sixth batch of cube replicates.

Chapter 1210: A Cube-Powered Vehicle

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

In the underground laboratory in the Third Border City

Roland immediately took Anna to the laboratory. Through the thick protection glass, he saw two activated Magic Ceremony Cubes at the center of the laboratory. The wall of the laboratory was plastered with lead plates. One of the Cubes looked quite normal while the other ejected much shorter red laser beams.

"Is the one that ejects shorter red light the new replicate?" Anna asked perceptively.

"That's right. Actually, it was purely an accident," Celine replied brightly. "Normally, Slimwrist carves the patterns on the parts. If the materials are damaged, then it won't be easy to duplicate the patterns, so we normally dispose those damaged stones. However, a week ago when Slimwrist was carving Part No. 236, we found the stone crack, which means this specific part is defective."

Roland asked meditatively, "But you didn't throw No. 236 away?" As all the materials used to create duplicates were collected from the Southernmost Region, and since those tablets had been buried underground for 1,000 years, it was normal to have damage here and there.

Celine tapped her main tentacle and said, "I thought it would be a waste to throw it away, so I kept it just in case. Then I installed it on the Magic Cube previously made to see whether it would function properly."

Roland looked at Celine incredulously. That was a nuclear torture device!

"Don't worry, Your Majesty," Celine said as if seeing the thought in Roland's mind. She raised her blobbed head and continued, "I conducted the test in the Impassable Mountain Range. Nothing would happen to Neverwinter even if something went terribly wrong. This is a principle followed by the members of the Quest Society. You don't need to feel sad for me in the event I'm killed. For the sake of truth, I really can't care less about my personal safety..."

Looking at eloquent Celine, Roland realized his concern was unnecessary. He thus said, "Now, your finding!"

"Ahem, sorry," Celine said while clearing her throat. "Anyway, just as what you've seen, the Magic Cube could still be activated, although the range of the red beam shortened by 90%. However, the tri-tank magic power unit could still transmit energies. I conducted a heating test to see whether the shortened red beam affected heat transmission. It took me two to three days to complete the test. When I examined the uranium chip, I was amazed to find that it did not change much. Also, it appears that much less magic power was consumed when the range of the red beam shortened."

Anna asked thoughtfully, "So, most of the magic power was used to maintain the red beam?"

"I now understand why you became a Senior Witch even faster than Agatha," Celine praised. "It took me quite a while to reach the same conclusion. If that beam is comprised of numerous tiny particles, it'll be hard to direct them all to the same spot. The experiment indicated that the heat transmission on the front, left and right sides wouldn't be affected as long as you didn't touch the red beam. Therefore, I conclude that the decrease in the laser range did save a lot of power."

"Hang on," Roland interrupted suddenly. "This means that Part No. 236 determines the radiation range?"

This was definitely a major discovery even more important than the sustainability of the power system. There were around more than 300 parts in one Magic Ceremony Cube. Nobody knew how magic power worked through those patterned stones. Now, there seemed to be a solution to analyze the power within the cube.

"Yes," Celine assented, a twinge of excitement in her voice. "Perhaps the patterns on each part have a specific function. If we could decipher those patterns, we could probably understand how magic power worked within the Magic Ceremony Cube."

"Each part functions differently. It looks like the radiation clan shared the same mindset with us," Anna said with a smile. "Aren't we lucky?"

"Of course," Roland confirmed with a nod. He knew what Anna meant. Civilizations varied drastically in terms of language, mindset and appearance. It was almost impossible to find a similar one to learn from. The underground civilization, for example, could only operate the core device after transferring the soul to a carrier. Celine had spent hundreds of years trying to understand its mechanism, but the research was fruitless.

Therefore, each civilization, in a way, was lonely.

Although Roland had promised earlier that human beings could still learn from lost civilizations without the legacy shards, it was actually not easy to do so, especially when there was no guidance or assistance available. How could one learn about the other when they had different mindsets?

If Celine was right, then the radiation clan, which was the first civilization that shared some similarity with the human race, might enlighten them on the research of magic power.

"By the way," Anna said as she suddenly grinned at Roland. "Since the magic power unit has been finalized and we have also solved the sustainability problem, isn't it time for you to fulfill your promise?"

Gazing at Anna's bright, blue eyes, Roland found it hard to turn down her request.

"Yes, yes... Your Highness," he said while smiling back. "I'll start working on it once I'm back to the castle."

...

The dawn broke with loud noises.

Soraya sat up from her bed in a daze.

She yawned dramatically and fumbled for her clothes. These were the noises produced by steam engines that she heard every morning. They marked the beginning of another busy day.

But she noticed it was particularly early today. Soraya cast a glance at Echo who was still deep in her sleep, and put on her clothes quietly. She wondered who else in the castle got up earlier than her.

Then Soraya suddenly realized that this was not the industrial zone. Why were there noises of steam engines. It was weekend today, and most of the witches slept in. The castle would be empty until it was time for lunch. Was she dreaming?

The roar started again outside the window, and Soraya heard someone talk and laugh sprightly.

"This is so interesting!"

"Your Majesty, let me try it."

"Me too, me too!"

"What happened?" Echo asked blearily as she rose.

"I don't know. It's probably Mystery Moon..." Soraya said as she stretched and pulled back the thick curtains. Sunlight spilled across the room through the window. It was actually not early anymore.

After she became more comfortable with the sudden brightness, she peered down from her window and was surprised at what she saw.

Many witches were congregated at the castle gate, staring at something at the center of the yard, looking excited.

Soraya then saw Anna sitting in a peculiar four-wheeled carriage. There were no horses, but the vehicle ran on its own. Anna's face split into a big smile.

Immediately, Soraya's eyes were glued to the strange vehicle.

Chapter 1211: A Farming Tractor

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

"Your Majesty, Your Majesty, what's Lady Anna driving?"

Roland turned around and saw Echo and Soraya rush toward him.

"It's a car, a Magic Cube-powered car!" Mysterious Moon supplied the answer fervently. "If you want to drive it, go line up."

"A... car?" Soraya echoed, "A car powered by a steam engine?"

"Yup, but the boiler of the steam engine has been replaced by the relic of the radiation clan, so that's why it's so small," Mystery Moon boasted. "It's still a lot larger than an electric motor though. I wish it could be powered by Dawn I. That'll be perfect... No, then we should call it a magnet-driven car!"

'You can barely manage to work with dozens of copper rods," Lily retorted while twitching her lips. "And now you want to power a car?"

"Er..." Mystery Moon faltered. "I, I just came of age, so obviously I'm not that powerful. Perhaps I could manufacture tons of Dawn I after I upgrade."

"I would rather put my hope in Miss Doris," Lily said scathingly.

"Shut up, or I'll take away all your Chaos Drinks!"

"I dare you — "

"Haha..." Phyllis burst into a laughter. "Actually, no matter it's powered by steam or electricity, we still call it a 'car'."

"Really?" All the other witches said together while looking toward her.

"Yes, in the Dream World, it's called a car," Phyllis replied triumphantly. "The cars in the Dream World are much better than this one Her Highness is now driving. They could not only shelter us from rain and wind, but they're also equipped with an advanced heating and air-conditioning system. It's pretty much like a mobile house, and it's a lot faster than horses!"

"Have you... driven a car before?" Mystery Moon asked, her eyes widening in curiosity.

"Of course," Phyllis bragged. "I once drove His Majesty's vehicle on an endless highway. The vehicle literally trembled when I drove at the maximum speed. I could only hear wind howling around me, and I felt I could conquer the whole world!"

Roland mopped his forehead, amazed that Phyllis could drive his battered mini van in the same manner as she drove a luxurious sports car. The truth was that his vehicle had poor noise insulation and it always wobbled violently on highways.

Nevertheless, even the old mini van functioned better than this cube-powered vehicle.

It had taken Roland only four days to complete the production. The vehicle was comprised of a steam engine at the front, a heating system at the rear, a power unit attached to the automobile frame, and a couch in the middle. Apart from a steering wheel, a clutch and a brake, the vehicle had no gearbox but only a valve next to the seat to adjust the speed.

Once the Magic Ceremony Cube heated up the water and set the steam engine in motion, the vehicle would start to move. As the air pressure in the conduits increased, the vehicle accelerated. Then the driver could switch the valve on to release some steam so that the steam engine would not overload. In this way, the driver adjusted the speed of the vehicle.

In other words, the driver simply needed to press on the brake and the clutch to slow down and release the brake to accelerate. Due to the high air pressure, the spinning cogwheel might sustain some extent of damage. Therefore, once the vehicle came to a complete stop, the driver must open the valve to release the steam and reduce the air pressure in the steam engine.

Despite the cubersome power unit, the primitive automobile frame, and the crude steering device, Anna was over the moon. Like a little girl who had just received the best present in the world, she drove around the yard with the slightest intention of taking a rest.

In addition to Anna, the other witches were also aroused by the vehicle. They exchanged excited murmurs. It was the first time they laughed so heartily after the battle of Taquila.

Roland wished Tilly could share this happiness.

Nightingale told him that Tilly invested most of her time in training aerial knights, so she rarely came to the castle lately. Perhaps, for Tilly, the happiest thing was to defeat the demons.

When Anna finally alighted from the vehicle and asked who would like to try out, all the witches pressed forward to take the share.

Sylvie, who was the first to arrive at the scene and spot the car, got the opportunity to drive.

"How do you like it," Roland asked Anna.

"It's more fun than I thought," Anna replied with a smile. "Thank you, Roland. I'm so glad that you taught me how to drive."

Roland dazed for a second as he saw Anna's face split into a dazzling smile. He quickly averted his eyes, a little embarrassed, as though he had suddenly traveled back to the time when they had first met. Roland said, "Well, I'm glad you like it."

Anna blinked and said, "By the way, Celine found a way to stabilize the Magic Ceremony Cube. Does it mean that we could use the Cube in the Battle of Divine Will?"

"Technically, we could," Roland replied on a cough and pulled himself together. "We just need to keep supplying water to make sure that the cube-powered steam engine works. Time will tell how much this new steam engine could help with the logistics."

"Can we use the steam engine to create an armored war machine with a Longsong Cannon anchored to the top?" Phyllis cut in. "If you could make such a weapon, then we don't have to be afraid of the Spider Demons anymore."

It was true that a competent power unit would make an armored unit possible. With a powerful tank, they could instantly dominate the war. Even the crudest tank could easily repulse Mad Demons and block spears and bone needles ejected by Spidery Monstrous Beasts. It was a weapon as well as a defense.

Nevertheless, extensive research was required to create such an advanced weapon. Not only did they have to improve technologies, but they have to also educate workers. Anna could not manufacture the biplanes and the armored weapons at the same time, it was also unrealistic to directly create a tank. In short, considering the limited technologies and resources, most of the work had to be completed by plant workers.

The first project that came to Roland's mind, however, was not a tank or an infantry fighting vehicle but a transportation tool for civil services.

This transportation tool could considerably increase farming efficiency while saving a lot of manpower. As the principle and technologies applied to this transportation tool were quite similar to those related to armored vehicles, Roland could also, at the same time, provide soldiers with some training. Meanwhile, workers in the plant could also immediately start to produce armored weapons, if necessary.

This transportation tool was — a tractor.

Chapter 1212: Rainbow Stone

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

"Ahhh! Help! I can't steer it around. Someone help me!"

A piercing shiek interrupted Roland's train of thought. Roland looked up and saw the vehicle dash toward the flower bed at the center of the yard. In the vehicle sat Mystery Moon.

"You, you idiot!" Lily said through clenched teeth. "Hit the brake!"

"I did... but it doesn't work, ahhhh!" Mystery Moon screamed in terror.

The car ran wild. It bounced off the flower bed and streaked toward the castle gate.

"Your Majesty, watch out!" Wendy shouted.

There was instantly a great commotion.

"Holy crap," Roland said within himself, gaping at Mystery Moon who steered the vehicle frantically with her eyes clamp shut. He was astonished that a car without gas could go so wrong. What a monstrous driver Mystery Moon was!

Much to Roland's consternation, the crowd was not dispersed. All the witches, on the contrary, stopped in front of the car. In a second, all the witches applied their various abilities. Anna summoned a Blackfire wall; Lotus created a ditch to separate Roland from the yard; Iffy summoned her Magic Cage, and Andrea was about to shoot her Light Arrow; Nightingale grabbed Roland by the arm, ready to drag him into the mist anytime.

In the end, Phyllis and Lorgar stopped the vehicle by force.

They grasped the bumper of the vehicle and lifted the car off the ground.

Then Anna turned down the Magic Ceremony Cube with her Blackfire.

The steam engine was immediately silenced.

"Ahhhhh! Run, guys!" Mystery Moon yelled hysterically, her hand still on the steering wheel.

"You BIG THICKHEAD!" Lily strode across the ditch and slammed her hand on the back of Mystery Moon's head. Her scream instantly perished into a grumble.

Mystery Moon opened her eyes, her hands on her head, looking perfectly innocent.

"Mystery Moon!"

Seeing Wendy and Scroll dart in her direction in a hot rage, Mystery Moon realized that she had made a big mistake. She pleaded, "I'm sorry. I'm so sorry —" But it was too late. She had been dragged out of the vehicle and into the castle before she could justify her behavior.

"You always cause trouble!"

"No time off for you this week!"

"I order you to copy the rules of the Witch Union 100 times!"

"And you also have to complete five sets of homework before dinner!"

Mystery Moon's cry reverberated across the whole yard. All the witches shuddered at the long murmur of echoes, except Anna.

"I examined the vehicle. There's nothing wrong with the steering wheel or the brake," Anna said to Roland. "There's only one reason why Mystery Moon lost control."

"What's that?"

"She's not strong enough to maneuver the car," Anna said with a magnificently forgiving air.

Roland laughed at such an amusing truth. It appeared those who were weaker than Mystery Moon probably could not drive the car unless he installed an assisting mechanism to the steering wheel and the brake.

Lotus and Anna soon fixed the yard. Looking at a group of witch who was not able to disguise their eagerness, Roland said while shaking his head, "If you still want to go on a ride, then talk to Anna. As long as she agrees, I don't have any objections. Just make sure that you don't destroy the castle. Right, another thing. Don't forget to come back for lunch."

"Yes, Your Majesty!"

"Please let me have a go first!"

"Hey, I came here before you!"

The yard was again alive with laughters.

...

"Sir, it's here."

A carriage staggered to a halt in front of a tavern. Victor Lothar alighted from the wagon and tossed two silver royals at the coachman before he got in.

"Mr. Victor!" a pretty young lady in a white robe greeted him at a trot. She took the luggage from Victor and said ardently, "We keep the room for you. Please, this way."

Victor's room was the largest one on the top floor. Everything was just as the same as when he had departed last time, including incenses, grape wines and his personal maid, Tinkle.

Victor nodded in satisfaction. This was the power of money. Although it could not bring the dead to life, it could freeze time.

"It has been a while since last time you were here," Tinkle said as she pulled back the curtains, opened the window and poured him a cup of tea. "My boss thought you encountered bandits or died in a shipwreck. He asked the accountant to check the gold royals you left here every day to see how long we can keep the room for you. He wants to let out this room to someone else but at the same time doesn't want to break Neverwinter contract law. It's really amusing to see that he was caught in such a disgusting dilemma."

Victor felt his fatigue gradually dissipated as he listened to his maid babbling. He asked, "Aren't you afraid that he'll know that you badmouth him behind his back?"

Tinkle stuck out her tongue and said, "Unless you tell him. By the way, where have you been? Was it a great undertaking?"

"Well, sort of," Victor said while sipping the tea. "I spent most of my time in the Southern Territory in the past half a year."

"The Southern Territory?" Tinkle echoed in confusion, her head lopsided. "That area isn't famous for gemstones, is it?"

"There are gemstones everywhere, provided that you know where to find them," Victor said, shrugging. "For example, in the south, gemstones grow on trees."

"Sir, you must be making fun of me," the maid said a little indignantly.

Victor smiled. He knew Tinkle would not believe him. In fact, he could not believe it either before he actually saw it. The cotton field was, to his surprise, even more beautiful than gemstones. The plants cultivated by Leaf were incredible. The cotton was large and soft like snow, completely different from the one he used to see.

Victor had been busy in the past few months. He summoned all the tailors in his native town, built a plant at the Port of Clearwater, and hired staff to work for him. Once the harvest season was over, he started to sell the cotton to the public. His business was better than he had initially anticipated. As this new cotton was affordable and high-quality, they soon outstripped their competitors. All his products were fairly popular, from cotton blankets all the way to cotton winter jackets.

Nevertheless, Victor knew that competition always existed. He knew when other merchants also started to purchase cotton seeds from Leaf, his market would inevitably shrink a little bit. Therefore, apart from common cotton fabrics, he also produced high-end commodities, which were mainly clothes tailored to wealthy customers. All the clothes were carefully designed and made, with a tiny logo of a colorful gemstone at sleeves and collars that marked the uniqueness of his products.

Those clothes were soon acknowledged by a certain group of people and were subsequently called "Rainbow Stone".

Victor thus also granted the same logo to his low-end products such as blankets and robes, only that the logo is monochrome.

Victor predicted that even if other merchants sold their products at a lower price than his, people would still tend to buy his products because of the Rainbow Stone logo. Just like jewelry, nobles always preferred to purchase those processed by masters over the ones that were not.

"How long are you going to stay here this time," Tinkle asked after a long silence.

"Probably three or four days. I have a lot to do in the Southern Territory," Victor replied.

"That soon?" the maid asked in a low voice.

Victor understood that Tinkle would have to serve other customers if he decided to surrender the tenancy. She preferred to clean a vacant room than serving customers. Victor did not really care about the possible change, but he did like Tinkle to serve him.

He had not got tired of her yet.

"Don't worry. I'll pay a good amount of gold royals before I return to Neverwinter."

"Really?" Tinkle said, her facing lighting up.

"That isn't much, really," Victor said while straightening up and tossed a gold royal at Tinkle. "This is your pay. I need to pay a visit to the Administrative Office. Lead the way."

Chapter 1213: The Beginning of an Enterprise

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Over the past six months, although Victor Lothar had stayed in the Southern Territory, he had paid close attention to Neverwinter, for he believed that this city would undoubtedly become the central city of the world in the future. The impact of this future capital would extend to not only Graycastle but also the other three kingdoms and the Fjords. Therefore, Victor asked his men to purchase Graycastle Weekly and send a copy to the Port of Clearwater every day.

He returned to Neverwinter because of two major events that had caught his attention. One was the sale of the Miracle Building and the other was the release of a new magic movie, "The Dust of History".

Victor did not understand why the King of Graycastle insisted that Neverwinter people had to show their identification cards to purchase the apartment. As a Neverwinter resident, he could still travel to the Port of Clearwater and the City of Glow. Victor did not know what the point of having a Neverwinter Identification Card. He was a merchant and basically traveled the world all the year around.

Nevertheless, nobody would miss the opportunity to become a resident of the tallest apartment building on this continent situated at the center of the new king's city. It was a perfect marketing strategy to further promote his brand, "Rainbow Stone".

However, even if Victor failed to obtain a room in the Miracle Building, he would not feel too regretted about it. As the designated distributor of the new cotton seeds appointed by King Roland, Victor was confident that he could outperform all other merchants. For him, he was interested more in the magic movie than the real estate transaction.

He would never forget the first magic movie he had seen.

It was mind-blowing.

The moment the curtains had been pulled back, Victor had felt his physical body melt into nothingness, his soul wandering in the darkness. He had watched "The Wolf Princess" many times, and would have watched over and over again had he not decided to grow cotton in the Southern Territory.

Victor had the faintest clue as to the content of the new magic movie "The Dust of History". However, he was particularly intrigued by the movie because of two reasons. One was that all the actors in the movie were from the Star Flower Troupe, and the other was that the screenwriter this time was famous Kajen Fels.

According to the introduction of the movie, it was based on a true story, and King Roland had even provided assistance with the background research. It was rumored that the king had disclosed a book that had been kept as a secret by the royal family for generations. Victor knew he should not take these rumors circulated among the public too seriously. The best way to confirm the validity of the information was to watch the magic movie himself. How could he miss it?

This was actually the main reason Victor came back to Neverwinter.

As soon as Victor reached the Administrative Office, Tinkle went to line up to purchase the tickets. Each ticket cost 50 gold royals, which was 10 gold royals more than the ticket for "The Wolf Princess". However, Victor immediately gave Tinkle 100 gold royals and asked her to buy two tickets.

Tinkle felt a surge of pride. Many people eyed her as she bought two tickets at a time. The price for the premiere was so daunting that even foreign merchants would hesitate for a while before making the decision. In fact, the ticket would be a lot cheaper the next day, and the price would further drop to 10 silver royals for civilians a week later.

The transaction of the apartment was much more complicated. After Victor submitted the application, he and Tinkle were led into a small cabin.

"I can't believe that you have a Neverwinter Identification Card!" Tinkle said in a hushed voice. "But you aren't a Graycastle man, and certainly aren't a resident of Border Town either."

Victor said, shrugging, "You've forgotten that one could become a Neverwinter resident as soon as he purchases a property here."

"Of course I know!" Tinkle defended herself. "But you always live in the tavern..."

"That doesn't prevent me from having a real estate property here," Victor said airily. "I prefer a tavern to a residential area, but I can still buy a property just in case."

"..." Tinkle was speechless, her eyes wide open.

Victor thought that was the beauty of a country girl. If Tinkle were a lady, she would have probably viewed him as an idiot.

Just then, a young lady in a uniform came in. "Hello, thanks for waiting. My name is Betty. I'm a clerk at the Administrative Office, and I'll be responsible for registration."

"I'm..."

"Victor Lothar. I reviewed your application, and you're eligible to make a purchase." Betty said quickly, "I have to admit that you have a really good taste. Out of all the residential buildings, you picked the Miracle Building. This is the landmark of Neverwinter. You can have a birdview of the whole city. Although the price is a little high, it's definitely worth it!"

Mildly taken aback, Victor suddenly had a strange feeling that not many people were buying. He thus cleared his throat and asked, "So, how much is it?"

"Here it is, Mr. Victor," Betty said as she handed him a piece of paper.

Victor spread it open, a muscle twitching around his lips. The prices of all the floors of the Miracle Building were listed. The first five floors were under 100 gold royals. From the fifth floor onward, the price doubled by each floor. The 14th Floor was listed as 2,000 gold royals.

Tinkle clapped his hand over his mouth.

"The 15th floor is not for sale?" Victor asked as he noticed the floor was not priced.

"The Astrology Association and the Alchemist Workshop have jointly bought the 15th floor. I've heard they're planning to found a Society of Sage and make it as the headquarters — "

"I'll take the 14th floor!" Victor cut across Betty, who looked as aghasted as Tinkle. He then added, "I'll take two."

4,000 gold royals was a large sum of money even for Victor. He had been hesitating at first, but after hearing the news of the Society of Sage, he immediately made up his mind.

If Neverwinter was the central city of the future, then this so-called headquarters would definitely influence the entire kingdom. If he could associate his business to these two eminent organizations, it would be very helpful to further promote his products, even though what he did was simply sharing the same building with the two societies.

"A wise choice, Mr. Victor!" Betty said while holding Victor's hand in excitement. "I'll bring the contract right away. Once you sign, the two rooms will be yours."

Watching Betty rush out of the room, Victor heaved a deep sigh and said, "I somehow feel that she is the buyer not me..."

"It probably has something to do with her sales target," Twinkle mumbled.

"What's that?"

"I heard about it from customers coming to the tavern. It appears that every official and clerk in the Administrative Office is subject to periodical evaluations. I don't know about the details, but the evaluation determines whether they could get a raise or get promoted."

"I see... Now I see why everyone here works so hard," Victor muttered. This was something new he could learn from.

Perhaps, he could also implement a similar system in his textile mill.

"By the way..." Tinkle said hesitantly. "You aren't leaving the rooms vacant, are you? You spent so much money on them. So, are you still living in the tavern?"

"I'll continue to live there," Victor said smilingly. "But the rooms I bought with 4,000 gold royals won't be vacant either."

"But you can't live in two places at the same time."

"It doesn't mean I'm going to use it as a residence. I'm planning to make it as the new headquarters of Lorthar Corporation, the headquarters for 'Rainbow Stone'." In the beginning, Victor had only planned to purchase one room and hang a banner outside to advertise "Rainbow Stone", but Betty's words inspired him. He could use the room for something else.

Chapter 1214: The Second Magic Movie

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Two days later, Victor went to the movie theatre.

The premiere of the movie "The Dust of History" was at 3:00 PM. He arrived at the theatre pretty early and waited to check in. The movie theatre had expanded a great deal since his last visit a year ago. There were not only several new movie halls but also a yard and a waiting area for customers. Although Victor came here half an hour early, the hall had been packed when he got here.

"Are you Mr. Gammon from the Chamber of Commerce of the Crescent Moon Bay? Nice to meet you."

"Nice to meet you too. I didn't expect to meet such a successful businessman from the Kingdom of Dawn like you."

"Are they actors from Kajen's troupe? I wonder if I could meet Kajen himself."

"Please present me to him if you ever get a chance."

"Sure thing."

The audience started to make conversations. As Victor had expected, those who could afford the premiere were all prominent figures. This was also one of the benefits to attend the premiere.

"Hey, aren't you Mr. Victor? I've heard that you're no longer in the jewelry trade, are you?" someone said to him abruptly.

"I'm still doing my old trade, but the business isn't good at the moment."

"I like your blankets. More customers come to my hotel after I use your products. I would like to order 100 more."

"I'm glad to hear that. We could have a chat after the magic movie."

"Sounds good."

Tinkle's eyes were wide open as she listened to their conversation. To her, it was unimaginable to suddenly have such a big order over a casual chat. When Victor was finally alone, she tugged his sleeve and asked, "Sir, are these people coming here for the movie or business? I notice many of them don't really know you. Aren't you afraid that they're frauds?"

"Don't worry. It's very common among enterpreneurs. Just get used to it," Victor said smilingly. Only successful businessmen were financially capable of attending this grand premiere. To some extent, this premiere told more about their financial status than any jewelry they were wearing, because the theatre experience was, essentially, an intangible service that would not give audience any monetary benefits.

While Victor was explaining to Tinkle, someone bumped into him.

"Ah... sorry," Victor apologized. However, he was rooted to the ground after he saw the woman.

It was a lifeless face, although quite pretty. Perhaps, the lady would have been even prettier than Tinkle had she put on some makeup. Nevertheless, her pale skin and absent look abhorred him. The sullen expression that the woman was wearing formed a glaring contrast with the animated atmosphere in the hall.

The woman did not say anything but simply cast him an indifferent glance before she drifted off.

"What a weird person..." Victor mumbled.

"Sir, the magic movie is starting in a minute. Let's get in," Tinkle, who apparently had not noticed anything, urged while grasping Victor's hand.

"Right... yes," Victor said. He soon put the lady out of his mind and followed Tinkle into the hall.

...

"What happened just now?" Joe asked Farrina a little apprehensively.

"Nothing," Farrina answered in a low voice. "Someone bumped into me. Let's go. Since you brought me here, let's just get in."

"R-right," Joe stammered, not sure whether he should hold Farrina's hand, and finally decided not to do so. "Remember that you shall stay with me, no matter what happens."

Farrina remained silent. This was the best she could do to come here with him.

After staying in Neverwinter for nearly half a year, Farrina gradually came to the realization that the ancient witch who claimed to have been living for 400 years did not lie to her. Her wounds slowly healed up. Although the whip and brand marks persisted, she could at least walk on her own. Farrina found herself have nothing to complain about. Had she fallen into any pure witches' hands, she would have suffered more tortures. Neverwinter witches did treat her fairly well.

However, the trial Farrina had been waiting for did not come. She had not even got a chance to meet the King of Graycastle. Farrina was simply questioned by dozens of people. She had even lied, in an attempt to provoke the interrogators, but they simply gave her a searching look with an air of derision.

After Farrina was released from the prison, Joe bought a house to settle her down. Unlike her, Joe, as a former noble, soon found a job at the Administrative Office and quickly adapted to the new environment. If truth be told, Joe should not have been a church member in the first place. However, the life in Neverwinter tormented Farrina. The longer Farrina lived in Neverwinter, the more she realized how wrong the church had been. The witches were not the representation of evil. Apart from magic power, they were no different from ordinary people. Roland Wimbledon did not turn the city into hell with the power of witches but instead made people's life even better.

Farrina was torn between her belief that she had been indebted for half of her life and the glaring reality. Perhaps, this was the trial. Sometimes, it could be more brutal than tortures. She would have ended her own life had Joe not needed her.

Farrina didn't know how long she could live like that. Dimly, she knew the two tickets sent from the Star Flower Troupe would be her last straw. Kajen Fels created this movie on King Roland's request. The sole purpose of this movie was to disclose the truth about the church and thus further secure the dominant position of the Wimbledon Family.

Farrina could imagine that the church would become what everyone loathed after this movie. The sacrifice of Pope Tucker Thor and numerous Judgement Warriors killed in action would then become nothing but a joke.

Farrina did not want this to happen, but she still agreed to come with Joe.

Just as she had not refused the request of the church executives and agreed to stay behind to fight for Hermes.

Because Joe needed her.

Yet this was probably the last thing she could do.

Light gradually faded out.

Darkness fell on the hall, and the magic movie began.

...

The story started on the Hermes Plateau 300 years ago when the New Holy City was simply boulders and rocks. A sheer drop of cliffs, the vast bleakness of the land covered in snow, and the great rapture down the Impassable Mountain Range swarmed into his view.

Although Victor had watched magic movies many times, he was still quite shocked as the whole continent dwarfed beneath him.

Across the great rapture, many church members were building their new city, as though this was really what had happened 300 years ago.

A moment later, the audience saw a huge hole in the ground. Victor heard the name "Prival Council", which was the most secretive organization of the church. A murmur, at this point, swept over the hall. Victor knew everybody was as surprised and intrigued as him and believed that this was probably the hidden history once only known to the royal family. Soon, the story caught Victor's attention.

It was rumored that a disastrous war broke out every 400 years. When the war started, a bloody moon would appear in the sky, and many enemies would creep out of hell and crush the mankind. For the sake of the human race, witches offered their blood to warriors and obtained incredible power. This was the truth of the God's Punishment Warriors.

To make sure this plan was successful, witches established the church and started to select potential warriors. The main character of this movie was a witch, and she was also the succeeder of the current pope. Another main character was the pope's guardian, the commander of the Judgement Army.

Like the majority of plays, the two main characters, after overcoming the initial prejudice and hostility against each other, finally fell in love. The witch and the guardian promised to each other than once there was a succeeder to take over the pope position, they would attend the incarnation ceremony for the God's Punishment Army and never part again.

It was such an ingenious stroke that Kajen Fels told this beautiful love story in such an emotional, unobtrusive manner. The excellent performance of the actors from the Star Flower Troupe further moved the audience. Tinkle even wept when she saw the couple make vows.

However, the situation suddenly turned for the worse. The guardian's father, having a strong desire for power, framed the pope and usurped the throne. The witch, as a candidate for the next pope, naturally became the first obstacle he was going to remove. He thus asked his son to kill the girl, but the guardian refused his request with inflexible determination.

It was a scheme that the usurper had conspired for a long time. When the couple discovered the consipiration, it was too late to change the situation. The couple thus decided to flee Hermes and inform the king situated at the foot of the plateau of this incident. However, the guardian's father sent soldiers to catch them. Apparently, he was determined to kill the young man and the woman.

The movie reached its climax when a battle broke out at the Coldwind Ridge in Graycastle.

A unit of the Judgement Army soon caught up with the witch and the guardian. it seemed that the two unfortunate lovers were doomed.

When the tension between the two parties became almost unbearable, something incredible happened.

"Please, help us! Please!" the guardian yelled, panting, and suddenly turned around. He grasped Victor frantically. Victor felt a coldness steal through him, and he shuddered uncontrollably.

It took him all his efforts not to cry out loud!

"They're there! Get them!"

"Anyone who resists us will be viewed as their accomplices. We're going to kill all of you!" the soldiers shouted, their arms aloft in the air.

"I, I'm not..." Victor said with great difficulties, his throat dry. Words failed him, and the Judgement Warriors had already pulled the trigger.

An arrow brushed past his cheek!

At the same time, Victor felt a sting.

His hand rubbed on his cheek tremulously and he peered down at this fingers.

There was a faint hint of crimson on them.

Chapter 1215: The Reoccurence of the Legend

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Farrina, surprisingly, found that her last straw had not fallen upon her yet.

It was hanging by a thin thread only a few feet above her.

The story portrayed by the magic movie was very similar to the "truth" disclosed by the ancient witch, only that it did not repudiate the church totally. When Farrina saw the main characters make all their efforts to save the church and shoulder the responsibilities of fighting against the enemies from hell, she felt a warmth long since forgotten wash over her.

Her hand balled into a fist when she saw more than half of the executives conspire against the pope, and had a sudden urge to beat them into the ground.

These people forgot the initial purpose of establishing the church and turned the church into a hideous monster.

What she loathed the most was that these executives kept the existence of demons from the public and people who were dedicated to saving the world like Tucker Thor. These faithful warriors did not die for a noble cause as they had believed. Instead, their death merely became a tool that those obnoxious leaders used to keep a firm grip on power.

Farrina should not have put her faith in a church like that.

She did not understand why the King of Graycastle did not reveal the dark side of the church. Wasn't it a perfect opportunity to further criticize the church and wipe it off people's memories?

Or was it because he had never taken the church seriously?

While Farrina was dealing with a multitude of thoughts in her mind, the soldiers from Hermes caught her attention.

For a person who had completely lost hopes, nothing could really perturb her mind. However, now, Farrina was touched, and her power slowly came back to her.

As one of the best soldiers in the Judgement Army, Farrina could sense even the slightest change in the surroundings.

She felt the ground underneath began to quaver.

The ground shook as the Judgement Army drew near.

Farrina had lived in Hermes for five to six years, so she was familiar with the pattering of horse hooves against the ground. She could instantly tell the number of the soldiers and how far they were without even looking at them.

There were 16 horses, two units of troops.

But she knew her feeling was not real. The magic movie was just an illusional image. Even though it felt so real, it was still not reality. As she was totally merged into the surroundings, all her senses had sharpened.

Farrina realized something had changed!

Then she could again feel her body.

"What happened?"

But something more incredible occurred.

She saw other people who were watching the magic movie rise in front of her.

Including Joe.

"Farrina, what the..." Joe asked blankly as he turned around.

Suddenly, a sense of evil foreboding possessed her. Farrina made an abrupt snatch in the air but caught nothing. The chair underneath her had disappeared.

"Please, help us! Please!" the guardian and the witch pleaded hysterically. They had now noticed the audience and started to run toward them.

"The traitors are here! Get them!"

"Anyone who resists us will be viewed as their accomplices. We're going to kill all of you!"

A few more arrows cracked through the air, and people at the front fell.

Most viewers were board members of Chambers of Commerce or members of a prominent family who had never experienced a war. For a second, they were all framed to the spot.

"Damn it!" Farrina swore. What were those witches doing? Was she hallucinating? Farrina would have shouted "This is a nasty snare set up by the witches. Everyone, follow me" in the past to calm down the audience. However, she fought down the urge, pushed Joe aside and rushed up to the front before all the audience. She yelled, "Stop! I'm the commander of the Vanguard Battalion of the Judgement Army, Farrina! Who are you?"

The soldiers reined their horses and asked, "The Vanguard Battalion? How come I've never heard of it?"

"Oi, what's your commander's name?"

"The Great Priest of the Prival Council, Sir Tayfun," Farrina lied. In the meantime, she put her hand at her back and gestured the couple to hand her a weapon.

"What?" Hearing Farrina's answer, the leader of the unit hesitated.

The guard wavered as he heard the name "Prival Council". Apparently, this secretive organization had quite a deep influence on church members. Yet Farrina knew it would not completely stop them. The Priest was obviously not as influential as the new throned pope.

She must fight before the other party did!

Unfortunately, the guardian did not really understand her gesture. He simply shuffled toward her with a sword in his hand.

"Why aren't you wearing the armor of the Judgement Army?" the soldier asked as he got off his horse and motioned his men to come with him.

"Because we're on a special mission," Farrina said placidly.

"I'm sorry. I must bring the traitors back to Hermes. This is the pope's order. Also, I must take you as well. I'm sure Sir Tayfun would understand it."

"Is there no alternative?"

"No," the soldier said resolutely while placing his hand on the hilt.

"Alright, I'll come with you," Farrina sighed. "As for Sir Tayfun..."

"What's the matter with him?"

"He's dead — only 300 years later." At these words, Farrina quickly drew out the guardian's sword and thrust it through the unit leader's helmet.

Blood spilled all over her.

"C-captain!"

"Kill them!"

Farrina grabbed the unit leader's weapon and fought fiercely against the other soldiers. The guardian finally realized what was happening and also joined her.

"This woman is — so difficult to deal with!"

"Darn it! Where's my bow? Shoot her!"

"Don't let the witch go!"

It was total chaos. Many people fell to the ground, and the audience goggled at the screen, flabberghasted.

Farrina knew there was no chance of winning since she was not wearing an armor. They had 16 people whereas there were only two of them. It was a matter of time that she got injured.

Soon she was wounded, but the pain searing through her did not slow her down. On the contrary, she fought even more ferociously.

For the first time since she had waken up, Farrina felt contented.

"How dare you defy the church!" the soldiers bellowed.

"The church? No... you don't deserve calling that name!" Farrina said while glaring at them. "It shouldn't have been like that. You destroyed it. You failed us!"

She would soon end up dying here, but somehow, Farrina was satisfied with this ending. In that split second, she had finally become the type of person she wanted to be.

However, death did not come.

A few gun shots cracked through the air over the clatter of swords. Farrina turned around and saw the men in black who had been guarding the yard suddenly appear in the magic movie. Their situation immediately changed. The enemies seemed to be frightened by those reinforcements. They got on their horses and soon disappeared in the mountain range, leaving the bodies of their fellow companions behind.

"Thank you..." said the wounded guardian and the witch as they limped to Farrina. "I thought my father has completely controlled the church, but I didn't expect that there were still loyal warriors like you."

"I thought there was no hope, but God hasn't abandoned us," the witch said while raising her tear-glazed face and smiled at Farrina. "You not only saved us but also the entire human race."

"I..." Farrina opened her mouth but did not know what to say.

"We're going to Graycastle next and tell their king about the coup that occurred on the Hermes Plateau. We hope it's not too late," the guardian said solemnly. "Run! Never come back to the Holy City again. We'll meet again once the church's mistake is rectified. Take care, my friend!"

Light gradually faded out as the couple disappeared from her view.

When the light was on again, Farrina found herself still sitting in the hall on her chair.

Even her wounds as a result of the battle had disappeared.

Was she really hallucinating?

"Good Lord... this is amazing!" The hall exploded into a tidal wave of applause as the audience came back to the present.

"Good heavens! I feel I'm changing the history..."

"What a brilliant masterpiece. I would be willing to pay 100 gold royals to watch it one more time, let alone 50!"

"You scared the hell out of me when you rushed to the front," Joe said while patting his chest. "It's so amazing to conceive such a story and make it so lifelike..."

Farrina did not answer, but she noticed the men in black looked around nervously with guns in their hands, as though something out of their expectation had happened. Two other theatre staff members dashed to the backstage, looking equally flustered.

This did not look like a great success at all.

Farrina held her breath, trying to figure out what was going on based on the few signs she had discovered. Suddenly, she heard distant explosions and people cry and execrate, but these voices were overpowered by the heated discussion in the hall.

This did not look right.

Farrina realized that something was wrong here.

She rose to her feet abruptly. Under the surprised gaze of Joe, Farrina passed the audience at the back and ran out of the room.

"Stop! You... hold on!" the men in black yelled, attempting to stop her, but it was too late.

Farrina ran across the yard and reached the street outside.

Neverwinter was in a state of chaos. Many people were running and shouting. Several residential areas had caught a fire. She heard more explosions in the industrial zone, and the whole city seemed to be out of control.

What scared her most was something above.

Darkness pressed in, and the sun had vanished into the thin air. A huge crimson moon appeared in the sky like a giant eye that snapped open.

Chapter 1216: A Chain Reaction

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Not only Neverwinter citizens saw the Bloody Moon.

Margaret was standing at the bow of the "Snow Wind" early this morning while gazing at the distant ocean. It had been 66 days since they had crossed the Sealine. Ocean waves rushed toward them, high at one time and low at another. Their movements were almost the same as the waves at the Shadow Waters thousands of miles away as if the two types of waves shared the same origin.

If the Swirling Sea did have a source, it must be the greatest discovery in the history of time.

Margaret was confident that the ocean waves would lead her to her final destination, and she also put great faith in the "Snow Wind".

The "Snow wind" did not require a sail to proceed against gusts of wind and rushes of rain. Since the ship was colossal, they could put plenty of food and water on it. Thanks to this robust and sturdy iron ship, not a single ship fell behind in this expedition.

She believed that Thunder would definitely make some spectacular discovery during this journey.

"Any luck?" a familiar voice said to her from behind.

Margaret turned around and said smilingly, "If I did find something, I would have informed the lookouts perched on the mast. So, you should have asked them first."

The person who was speaking to her was none other than the captain of the fleet, Thunder.

"I don't think so," he said brightly. "Perhaps they've found something already but are too shocked to say anything."

Magaret stifled her laughter. She knew Thunder was referring to what had happened when they had crossed the Sealine. When the horizon became vertical, even the most experienced sailor had failed to react promptly. Everyone had fallen off the watchtower as the world had turned upside down, their legs too shaky to support them.

Seasoned sailors would normally cling to cables and masts in the event of a storm to prevent themselves from falling off the ship. However, the Sealine rendered all the common senses they had useless.

Thunder said while shrugging, "According to my intelligence, the Chambers of Commerce would later change their lookouts. They'll have the boldest person on their ship to serve as a lookout. Shame on them."

"Really?" Margaret said while shaking her head. "But I believe after the experience at the Sealine, nothing could really perturb them anymore."

"Who knows?" Thunder said while patting Margaret on the shoulder. His voice suddenly lowered. "Don't worry. Joan will be fine."

Margaret's smile faltered. She nodded resolutely and said, "Yes, she was born to live in the ocean. I'm sure we'll meet her again somewhere soon."

Being optimistic was an important ability for explorers. Margaret knew worrying would not help with anything. What she should do was to pull herself together and move on.

"By the way, the meeting is about to start," Thunder said after a moment of silence. "The other captains are already there. Come to the cabin with me."

"Okay, got it."

All the captains gathered to discuss the route, the status of their ships, and resources. They held this meeting every three or four days to make sure the whole fleet was on the right track.

Just at that time, Thunder and Margaret noticed that the seawater was suddenly awash with a sheet of a strange red color.

The sailors on the deck were all frozen to the spot, gaping at the far distance as if seeing something incredible.

A little farther on, several people fell off the mast and to the deck, as though they had seen the Sealine again. It really surprised Magaret.

Weren't they the boldest people on the ship?

Margaret turned around slowly, and the next moment, all her blood froze.

A gigantic, crimson round celestial object hung low over the horizon, far larger than the sun. It just came out of nowhere!

"In the name of Three God," Margaret mumbled. "Is this what His Majesty called the Bloody Moon?"

But Thunder did not speak. It was such a terrifying scene that even Thunder failed to formulate a proper answer.

A long whistle pierced the air.

It was the "Snow Wind".

The shriek of the ship shattered the dead silence and jerked everyone out of the trance.

The whistle indicated there were enemies!

Margaret and Thunder exchanged dark looks and ran toward the bridge.

"What happened?" Thunder yelled as he darted into the command room.

"There are... ships," his first mate stammered, "coming from the southeast... toward us...

"What?" Thunder said. He quickly snatched the telescope from the first mate and looked in the direction the latter had pointed out.

Margaret's heart sank to the bottom. They were now thousands of miles away from the Shadow Waters. They hardly saw any birds around this area, let alone ships.

This was a new sea never intruded by human beings!

She thus got a pair of telescope from another sailor and looked in the same direction.

"Jesus..."

Margaret gasped. Two shadows were floating on the surface of the water. They had no sail but were proceeding against the water. What was more horrific was that the seawater around them was boiling, as though numerous fishes were coming with them.

However, Margaret soon noticed that what seemed to be fishes were actually the last thing explorers wanted to see.

They were sea ghosts.

Their fins slid in and out of their views. Sometimes, they leaped out of the water, throwing a splatter of water that reflected off the sinister red sheen of the Bloody Moon, which reminded Margaret of a pack of sharks vying for food.

"On my order, all the ships turn about!" Thunder yelled. "Full sail! Advance in full sail! Everyone, ready for the war!"

"Yes, sir!"

"We've got trouble..." the captain of the "Tuna" swallowed hard.

"May the God of Ocean bless us," the other captains all prayed.

Fjords people knew that no ship could outstrip a sea ghost, which meant their enemies would soon catch up with them.

Their situation worsened every minute.

As the two shadows got closer, Margaret saw what they looked like. They were half in the shape of a ship and half a skeleton of a monster, something that would have only appeared in one's nightmare. Their ribs exhaled clouds of dark green objects, and they were now only a dozen miles away from them!

When the dark green object fell into the water, the ocean stirred. Apparently, nobody wanted to be hit by such an ominous thing.

Thunder remained unflappable and issued another order. "Abandon all the food and supplies. Keep half of the drinking water only... No, just keep 30% of them and accelerate!"

Astonished, Margaret said, "Then we won't be able to explore."

"And it's probably not going to be enough for us to return to Neverwinter..." the first mate said hesitantly.

"We could fish and collect rain." Thunder took a sharp intake of breath and said, "However, if we could not outrun those sea ghosts and monsters, we'll all end up dying here. The exploration is over. Now, our goal is... to survive!"

Chapter 1217: The Doomsday (I)

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

In the Snow Reflection Castle in the Kingdom of Everwinter.

"Your, your lordship... the Army of Graycastle retreated!" When a guard rushed into the castle hall and reported the news, all the nobles rested their eyes on him.

"Are you sure?" Earl Marwayne asked as he stood bolt upright.

"I'm positive. More than one scout has confirmed that," guard said while nodding vigorously. "Some people saw them empty their campsite overnight and also abandon a lot of food."

"They're... finally gone!" exclaimed the earl who burst into a roar of laughter. His heart instantly lightened. A month ago, Graycastle men had suddenly appeared in the Kingdom of Everwinter and soon taken over many port cities. They accepted neither their surrender nor presents but started to evacuate the cities immediately. Their barbarous behavior was even more outrageous than the church's. At least, the church would provide them with an opportunity to negotiate.

The reason provided by the Graycastle men was also quite ludicrous. They claimed that the Bloody Moon would bring swift destruction to the kingdom. Therefore, everyone must leave as soon as possible. This was the land passed down by generations, and the earl would not allow anyone to take it away from him. Neither the church nor Graycastle could do that!

"Your lordship," a withered, ancient scholar said oily, "the so-called full moon, sickle moon, dark moon and Bloody Moon are simply astronomical phenomena. They appear every now and then. If they believe that it omens ill, then let them do so. As long as your lordship holds onto this land, they can't do anything about it."

"That's right, the treacherous precipices around the Snow Reflection Castle will protect you from any invasion."

"We won't yield even if the Graycastle men are willing to negotiate."

"The church threatened you first as well, but in the end, they had no choice but to promote you to bishop."

His other henchmen all rejoined.

Earl Marwayne became more and more confident. As he gazed at the sinister Bloody Moon that had emerged three days ago through the window, his fear gradually dissolved into gratitude. Had the Bloody Moon not appeared just in time, the Graycastle men would have continued to advance, and he would have definitely lost his precious Snow Reflection Castle.

Although the earl had heard that those barbarians rarely attack or interfere with a city ruled by a noble, taking away his people was intolerable.

If all the surrounding cities were evacuated, who could he rely on during the Months of Demons?

Like his henchmen had said, this city was his asset. It was to the north of the king's city, situated among precipices. The gaps between the city and the precipes were around a few miles to hundreds of meters wide, connected by suspension bridges. These gaps were actually wide enough to house a few castles.

His ancestors picked this isolated land to build their castle because this area was well fortified. In fact, the Snow Reflection Castle had never fallen. Even though the Church of Hermes had conquered the entire Kingdom of Everwinter in a very short period of time, they had never managed to drive their army into the Snow Reflection Castle. Instead, they had sent ambassadors to negotiate with the lord and promised him that he could continue to rule this land as long as he pledged fealty to the church. This was what a normal person would do.

That was why the earl maintained his silence for such a long time, hoping to sell the city at the best price.

However, he could not accept Wimbledon's conditions.

Earl Marwayne did not think that the demons referred to by the Graycastle men would invade his castle. The towering cliffs were natural defense. However, he needed surrounding towns and cities to provide him with resources. Without people, his current stockpile would be exhausted eventually.

Fortunately, these Graycastle men all fled when they saw the Bloody Moon.

"Mr. Zac, what should I do next?" Marwayne asked the old scholar.

"Haha, of course we should launch an attack at them," Zac replied while stroking his long beard.

The earl stiffened. Attacking was a completely different story. He would have never defied the King of Graycastle had he not had this geographical advantage.

"Rest assured. I'm not asking you to attack the Graycastle men directly. However, you could seize the territories they looted. Look, the scouts said the Graycastle soldiers are scattered around. Each unit only contains around 100 soldiers. How many resources and supplies could they take away with so few of them?"

Marwayne's eyes glistened with excitement. He said, "You mean..."

The scholar nodded smilingly and said, "Those people who left with the Graycastle soldiers must have left a lot of their possessions behind. If we trace them down, we could probably retrieve some resources."

For example, food that was not easy to carry along.

Marwayne thus summoned his Chief Knight in excitement. While he was about to issue an order, a guard suddenly burst in and yelled, "Your, your lordship... there's a demon... outside the castle!"

"What demon?" the earl asked while scoffing at him. "You believe the nonsense those Graycastle men said?"

"P-pray forgive me, your lordship, but it..." the guard stammered in a hollow sort of voice. "But it isn't human indeed!"

Not human?

Everyone looked one another in bewilderment.

Marwayne's heart leaped to his throat. However, as the lord of the Snow Reflection Castle, he must maintain his composure.

The earl thus put up a straight face and said, "Well, take me there. Let's see what it actually is. I'm very curious about what the creatures living in hell look like."

...

With that being said, Marwayne still put on his best armor and took the largest God's Stone of Retaliation with him before he ascended the city wall. A dozen guards erected "a wall of shields" in front of him.

He felt hugely relieved when he saw the demon. The demon was, as his guard had suggested, alone.

It was standing on a protruding rock instead of the city wall. The rock was a little taller than the wall, right in front of which was the fathomless abyss. The patrolling knights had already ordered their squires to set up catapults and were ready to shoot their arrows.

After studying the demon for a while, Marwayne noticed that it was indeed not remotely human. The demon had hands and feet, but it had a much larger build than an ordinary man, its skin blue, with protruding veins running underneath. The biggest difference lay in the tentacles that sprouted from its cheeks, chin and elbows. Marwayne was disgusted about those wriggling tentacles.

To his surprise, the demon's eyes were shut as if it was sleeping. Marwayne did not feel it threatening at all.

Marwayne wondered if the demon's visit was really the result of the Bloody Moon, but he soon convinced himself that this was a pretext the Graycastle men used to persuade ignorant villagers to leave the country. This monster definitely had nothing to do with the rumored doomsday. He just needed to ask his soldiers to shoot arrows, and then the demon would be dead.

At this thought, Marwayne took a deep breath and yelled, "Listen, you filthy, revolting monster! I'm the lord of the Snow Reflection Castle, Marwayne Caso. You illegally entered my territory. If you want to live, on your knees and surrender. This is your only choice. Otherwise, the icy abyss beneath will be the place you find your perpetual peace!"

Marwayne did not think the demon understood him. His hot statement was more like a demonstration of his own bravery than a warning to the demon.

If he scared away this demon that the Graycastle men were afraid of, then he would definitely rise to fame.

"My patience is limited. I'll count to five — five, four!"

In the meantime, Marwayne motioned his soldiers to get ready to shoot.

"Three..."

The demon's eyes snapped open. It bellowed, "Enough!"

Its voice pierced the air like thunders and rang off the precipes. Numerous icicles fell off as the cliffs shook. Marwayne felt the ground was about to shatter. There was a ringing silence, and he took a few steps backward in terror and fell to the ground.

Chapter 1218: Doomsday (II)

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

This monster... could speak human language!

The earl was reddened to temples when the guard helped him up. He had intended to exhibit his authority and valor in front of the demon to impress the other nobles. He had not expected, however, that the demon would uncover his carefully disguised gallantry with just one single word. What was more mortifying was that the demon was alone.

"Damn it. I must kill this monster!"

Marwayne raised his hand while gritting his teeth. He was about to order the soldiers to shoot when the old scholar suddenly stopped him and blinked. His lips took shape of a silent "stay put".

It took the earl a few seconds to realize that he should not lose his composure at the moment. Since the demon could talk, there was a possibility of negotiation and communication. Considering the situation was uncertain at this point, it was unwise to resort to force. The earl realized that the rumor circulated by the Graycastle men did cloud his judgement, for he had also, for a split second, viewed the demon as his enemy.

Perhaps, the demon came here alone as an ambassador.

Why did he take no action in the first place but stood upon the city wall while doing nothing?

If the demon was ferocious like what Graycastle men had said, it should have raided the surrounding villages unprotected by the city wall a long time ago.

The more Marwayne contemplated the matter, the more convinced he was. Had he killed the ambassador, he would have bred enmity with the demon, which was exactly what the Graycastle men wanted.

However, the earl found it hard to change his hostile attitude so quickly and sit down to talk in an amicable manner, for just a moment ago, he had commanded the demon to kneel down.

Fortunately, the old scholar understood the earl's dilemma. He stepped forward and said, "Impertinent! If you can speak our language, why didn't you tell us the purpose of your trip? Our lord kindly gives you another chance to speak. What's your intention of coming here?"

Marwayne praised the old scholar internally. He had paid 10 gold royals for the service of this former butler at the king's city.

"Before I answer you, I have a question for you," the demon said placidly. "What's your relationship... with the human beings on the Fertile Plains."

The Fertile Plains? Where was it? They exchanged confused looks, utterly bemused.

But Marwayne was now very sure that this monster was an ambassador.

"I don't know where the Fertile Plains is," the old scholar replied again. "One place may have different names in different parts of the kingdom. We are of different races, and we may have very different ways to call a city. Bring a map, and I may tell you where it is."

"No, you humans came up with this name, and I'm just borrowing it." The demon then shook his head and said, "I see... I can't believe you're still like hundreds of years ago where each lord circled out their own territories without knowing anything about this world. I was expecting to see you yield to your fate in disbelief, terror and despair, but it seems that I was wrong."

What did it mean? What monstrous absurdity it was talking about. The earl frowned. For a moment, he seemed to capture a faint hint of disappointment in its horrific countenance.

"Are you referring to... the Graycastle men?" the Chief Knight suddenly asked.

"Yes?" the demon said while looking toward him.

"They've been saying that demons will creep out of hell when the Bloody Moon appears. They're gone now," the knight said contemptuously. "If you go after them now, you may be able to catch a glimpse of them at the port in the east."

"Really?" the demon said as it gazed upon the east, and then turned around again. "I'll go, but not now. Since you know nothing about the Fertile Plains, then I'll cut the crap."

"I'm the Sky Lord, the commander of the Western Front Army. Thousands of years ago, your race and my race made an agreement to fight against the witches and their underlings. Your ancestors agreed to serve us. I granted them land, power and wealth. This contract has yet been terminated. It won't terminate until the war ends. You, as the descendants of your ancestors, should continue to serve us," the demon proclaimed in a booming voice. "Now, I command you to offer this city in accordance with the terms set out in this contract and serve me!"

Earl Marwayne gaped. This demon was crazy! Who cared about a contract signed 1,000 years ago? He would not even take a contract after a lapse of two years seriously. What kind of stupid commander of the Western Front Army was! What kind of commander would come in person alone? This monster was out of its mind!

"What if I disagree?" the earl said defiantly. His patience was exhausted.

"Death will let you yield," the demon who called himself the Sky Lord said. "Look, this is your fate."

The earl looked up and saw the distant mountains had been enveloped by a thin mist. It was not the mist he normally saw in the Impassable Mountain Range but a horrendous, crimson one. The earl was not sure if it was because of the Bloody Moon or it was the color of the mist itself.

Another peculiar phenomenon he noticed was that the red mist did not float in the air but slowly flowed down the mountains, forming a hazy "waterfall".

Was the demon waiting for this moment?

Marwayne felt a jolt of uneasiness at the pit of his stomach. He cast a glance at his equally disturbed knights and squires and knew he must take action now.

"With you alone?" the earl said through clenched teeth and gestured his soldiers. "I've given you a chance. Kill it!"

The knights and guards finally pulled themselves together. They immediately released the arrows, which whistled in the air and streaked toward the demon.

However, not a single arrow hit it.

Everyone goggled incredulously. The demon dived into a black hole and vanished from their sight.

"Damn it. It has magic power," the Chief Knight said in a low voice. "Then how's it different from the witches?"

"No worries. We're all wearing a God's Stone of Retaliation. Magic power won't hurt us!" Marwayne yelled as he clutched the pendant in front of his chest. "Find and kill it!"

"The d-demon is there!" a guard shouted.

Within a second, the demon had flown over the abyss and landed silently on the street behind the city wall.

The earl was alarmed when he saw that the demon could instantly pass the precipes. Now, he was more certain that this dangerous monster, whether it was an ambassador or not, must be exterminated. After all, it was alone. "Shoot the God Stone arrows. Treat it as a witch! 100 Gold Royals for anyone who could kill it!"

As all the knights and guards charged at the demon, the demon slowly raised its arms.

The next moment, a "black screen" around hundreds of meters wide appeared abruptly behind the demon and blocked the street and houses like a wall.

What was it playing at? Was it planning to hide?

However, the earl soon found the answer.

Thick Red Mist suddenly flooded all over the black screen! Then a group of monster he had never beheld rushed out of the screen and clashed with the knights who dashed forward. The God's Stone did not help at all. The knights were thrown into the air by the howling monsters before they landed heavily a few meters away. The knights coughed out blood, their chests sinking. Apparently, there was no chance for them to survive.

Nevertheless, this was just the beginning of the nightmare.

More monsters came out of the black screen, bowed to the Sky Lord, and joined the battle. Every monster was far stronger and larger than an ordinary man. Soon, they gained the top of the city of wall and began to slaughter the soldiers. The soldiers were torn into pieces, their blood and broken limbs flying in all directions.

Within seven or eight minutes, the city had been filled with painful groans. Many people were heading to the city gate, in an attempt to escape but they were stopped by the icy abyss.

Marwayne felt his legs give away. He staggered and fell to the ground. This time, nobody came to help him up.

His guard had been ripped apart by the demons.

His precious Snow Reflection Castle, the land passed down by generations that he took pride in, fell.

The air was heavy with pungent Red Mist, and this city had completely become a living hell.

Through the Mist, the Bloody Moon appeared to be even more gruesome.

The earl now understood what a doomsday looked like.

The end of Volume II: The Battle of Doomsday

Chapter 1219: The Investigation of the Abnormal Phenomenon

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

In Neverwinter, Graycastle.

The Police Department was stirred. Everyone was busy issuing orders and making reports. The appearance of the Bloody Moon became the latest topic of discussion, and the whole organization went on a sort of "rampage".

The Police Department kept close watch on the new king's city of Graycastle where Roland lived. They make records of every single trivial matter that occurred in the king's city, and certainly a major event like a fire or an explosion would be big news.

Carter Lannis had not slept for two days. After calming down his frightened wife, he immediately devoted himself to work. As the Chief Knight, he was obligated to protect the king and eliminate anyone who attempted to stir up trouble. Usually, multiple incidents implied an active underground criminal group. Therefore, he sent for the Neverwinter Detective Group at once to assist with the investigation. Carter believed that he would soon get to the bottom of it and find out the culprit.

However, after he submitted a number of reports, the king founded a Joint Investigation Team comprised of the Witch Union, the Security Bureau of Kingdom, and the Administrative Office to investigate the new magic movie instead of the crimes in the city.

"Sir, we brought the witnesses," a knight whispered to Carter. "Would you like to start the interrogation now?"

Carter drained his teacup and said with a firm nod, "Yes, let's get started. Send everyone in."

"Yes, sir."

Since they were making an inquiry to witnesses rather than prisoners, the interrogation took place in an office so that the witnesses would feel more comfortable to come forward with information. Apart from Carter himself who joined the Joint Investigation Team, Ms. Agatha and the assistant director of the Security Bureau, Vader, also took part in the investigation.

The first witness was a 21-year-old maid working in a hotel. She was not an official Neverwinter resident and had no criminal records.

She looked pretty nervous, for she kept rubbing her hands against the chair.

Carter cast a glance at the materials he had regarding this maid and asked sternly, "You're Miss Tinkle, right? I'm curious. The ticket price for the premiere of the movie 'The Dust of History' is 50 gold royals. How are you able to afford it?"

"Sir, I didn't steal or rob!" Tinkle explained hotly. "My customer, Mr. Victor, has a lot of money and he paid for me. There were many people in the hall that day, and I swear I'm not lying!"

Carter had conducted a background check before this interrogation. He reiterated the question simply to pressure the witness to tell the truth, as Miss Nightingale was not here to help him detect lies. Carter thus said, "Victor, right? I'll question him later. Now, let's talk about what you saw after the movie."

"Yes, sir..." the maid answered tremulously. "I didn't know what had happened at that time. Everything seemed so unreal."

15 minutes later, Tinkle finished her story. "Fortunately, the police repelled the soldiers. Otherwise, I couldn't imagine what would have happened to these two people."

Carter frowned. He had also watched the magic movie. "The Wolf Princess" was quite impressive but it was definitely not something so strange like that.

"Are you sure that the soldiers' weapons hurt the audience?"

"I... No, I'm not sure, but Mr. Victor did bleed, and I heard other people scream. I don't think they were faking this up."

"Do you remember when this happened?"

"About 10 minutes before the ending? Possibly even earlier than that... Sorry, I was too scared at that time to watch the movie, so Mr. Victor held me in his arms."

"Do you have anything else to ask?" Carter asked the other two investigators.

Agatha said thoughtfully, "If I remember correctly, the characters in the magic movie talked to you, right?" She then held up a picture and asked, "Is he this person?"

It was an actor from the Star Flower Troupe, who played the guardian of the witch in the movie.

"Yes, it's him. I remember very clearly that he thanked us!"

Carter felt a chill run down his spine. He knew that once the filming was completed, nobody could modify the contents of the movie. It was impossible for the characters to communicate with the audience.

Seeing that neither Agatha nor Vader have other questions, Carter waved his hand and said, "Bring in the next witness."

The statements of the other witnesses were pretty much identical. In short, the magic movie had suddenly become alive. Although they later confirmed that the incident was just a part of the movie, it did occur in real life. As multiple people gave the same story, Carter judged that this was not a hallucination.

Carter had been focused on the fire and explosion before, so he had not paid much attention to the incident in the movie theater. Now, he somehow understood why the king wanted to investigate this matter.

"The next witness is a police officer who was guarding the yard when the incident happened. He's the captain of Team No. 2."

"Let him in."

The captain was apparently more composed than the other witnesses. He quickly related the story. "I first heard someone cry for help outside. When I was about to get into the theater, I saw a red moon in the sky. To be honest, I was a little hesitant at that moment, as I didn't know whether I should remain in my post or help those people. Just at that time, a witch ran out of the theater and asked me to bring my men and protect the audience."

"And then you shot the soldiers in the magic movie?"

"It sounds very strange but that's what I did. They're probably just actors, but at that time, they did pose a real threat to the audience. I didn't think I was hallucinating, so I immediately fired."

The second last witness was the witch who broadcasted the movie on that day, Nightfall.

"What could I do? I was desperate. Normally, whoever has excess magic power would activate the Sigil of Recording. How do I know that this would happen?" Nightfall ranted. "Everything went well at first. Then, suddenly, the Sigil pushed me out. I should have immediately cut off the magic power but it didn't stop. I wanted to wake up the audience, but they were in a trance. Anyway, I did all I could. At last, I had no choice but to seek the police for help."

Agatha twitched her lips and asked, "The Sigil... pushed you out?"

"Pretty much like that. I felt a great force repelling me. The more magic power I put in, the greater this repulsive force was. Then, everything went back to normal."

"Alright. Next."

Carter was momentarily stunned when the last witness came in. The witness was none other than the screenwriter of the movie, Kajen Fels.

His hand clenched in a fist as soon as he sat down.

"In the name of God, this is definitely the most brilliant play I've ever watched in my life!"

"You were in the theater at that time?" Carter said while knitting his brows. As Kajen had once argued with Carter's wife, Carter did not like this famous screenwriter very much. "I looked at the list of customers. You were not on there."

"He was at the backstage. There are special seats for staff members. In fact, the members of the Star Flower Troupe didn't need to buy tickets to watch the show. Didn't your wife tell you that?" Agatha supplied the answer. "Actually, Kajen reported the incident to me and that's why His Majesty asked the Witch Union to investigate the matter."

"I apologize, but this is a personal habit of mine," Kajen said while placing his hand on his chest. "I like to watch my own play secretively so that I would know how my audience like the show. Ms. May knows it so she didn't tell you." Kajen's voice was again alive with excitement. "I have to admit that this is a miracle in the history of magic movie, because the audience changed the ending!"

"What did you say?" Carter asked in surprise.

"You heard it right, Mr. Knight. This wasn't my story!" Kajen Fels said eloquently while flailing his arms. "The original story has a sad ending. The guardian acts as a decoy to protect the witch. He then falls off the cliff. However, the audience saved them both. Is there anything better than that?"

The Chief Knight goggled at Kajen.

"I didn't write those lines. The audience created this spectacular ending. Like the characters in the movie said, the audience saved them and altered their fate!" Kajen gradually raised his voice. "This is the ultimate play that I've been trying to create for my whole life. If you find out the reason why, please tell me, please!"

Chapter 1220: The Origin of the Story

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Roland had the most hectic week since his ascendence to the throne.

There had been various subtle indications that the Bloody Moon would arrive a lot earlier than usual, and he had been preparing for that day for a long time. However, unlike what the church had predicted that it would appear in 10 years or as the Taquila witches had anticipated in two to three years, the Bloody Moon emerged above the Western Region right after the implementation of the immigration policy, so suddenly that its appearance had caught everyone offguard.

And that was not the end of it.

A week ago, various urgent reports had been sent from numerous cities to Roland informing him of the abnormal astronomical phenomenon. It seemed that nobody had seen the Bloody Moon approach the city. The Bloody Moon appeared to have always been there, being invisible to people until very recently.

Roland found that he had developed this "Bloody Moon Complex". Whatever he was doing, he always had a tendency to turn to the window and daze at the Bloody Moon outside. The moon was enveloped by a red haze but was not completely obscured. Roland sometimes had an illusion that the Bloody Moon was also gazing back at him.

According to the Union, the emergence of the Bloody Moon meant the beginning of the Battle of Divine Will, which Roland had been preparing for over the past few years. However, when it was actually time to fight, he felt everything become somewhat surreal. No news came from the Fertile Plains, and he had not heard anything from the scouts in the north either. Neverwinter appeared to be the only city affected by the incident. The Administrative Office sent in a report every half an hour, but none of them was relevant to the demons.

"Your Majesty?" Nightingale's voice jerked Roland out of the trance. "You're staring at the sky again."

Roland blinked and was suddenly back to the present. "Ah... sorry. I couldn't help — "

Nightingale fed him a piece of dried fish and cut across him, "Don't apologize. There's nothing wrong with staring at the moon. You've been exhausted lately. I'm happy that you take a break every now and then. Do you want my company? Since the Bloody Moon has something to do with the Divine Will, let's study it together."

Amused, Roland took the dried fish and shook his head. Nightingale always had ways to justify her eccentric behavior. He replied, "I have a lot to do. Keep an eye on me. You mustn't let me slack off. Understood?"

Nightingale twitched her lips and went back to her couch.

Roland took a deep breath and returned to the stack of reports on his desk.

The Bloody Moon seemed to have caused more trouble than the demons. According to the statistics from the Administrative Office and the Security Bureau, there had been four fires and 16 crimes in Neverwinter in the past one week. Anna had also reported 21 deaths in the plants caused by malfunction of machinery. More than 500 people were injured, and 90% of injuries had occurred within 24 hours of the appearance of the Bloody Moon. This was the most chaotic moment in Neverwinter in the history of time.

At first, Roland had thought the Bloody Moon induced panic to the masses. However, after he analyzed the patterns of all these incidents, he found it was not that simple. Therefore, he asked the Joint Investigation Team to further investigate the matter, and the result was quite surprising. Those incidents were actually caused by the fluctuation of magic power brought about by the Bloody Moon.

The reports submitted by Agatha detailed the chain of events.

The Bloody Moon had appeared at around 5:35 PM. All the devices driven by magic power in Neverwinter were, more or less, affected. For example, the ending of the magic movie "The Dust of History" had suddenly changed, and the audience had failed to distinguish illusions from reality. The electric circuits in the industrial zone were overloaded, and some machine tools powered by Dawn I stopped working. The most serious accident took place in Machinery Plant 1. One old boiler suddenly exploded, and hot steam burned the workers. Subsequent investigation showed that due to the outdated technologies, the boiler had been posing potential safety hazards for a long time, although Candle had, at one point, remoulded some of its important parts, including its valve.

Testimonies from multiple witnesses proved that order had been re-established in 10 minutes. The various accidents further created chaos and made many people believe that the demons were invading Neverwinter. Although the plant workers had all received emergency training, the evacuation did not go very well. The death toll would have probably continued to increase had Neverwinter not established an advanced public health system. Meanwhile, Nana's contribution to reducing the death was also phenomenal.

Roland had thought the Union had known that such things would happen upon the emergence of the Bloody Moon, but the truth was that none of the Taquila witches had heard about it. It appeared that the previous two appearances of the Bloody Moon did not bring such a huge impact on people's daily life, as magic power had not been widely used among the public back then.

Considering that people still suffered from the aftermath of the incidents, and nobody knew whether there would be a second round of magic power fluctuation, workers in the plants conducted a thorough inspection and removed all the outdated machines. The Administrative Office also prepared a new contingency plan, which included how to stay calm upon emergencies. The term "magic-caused accident" was used in official documents for the first time.

As for the magic movie, it was broadcasted again in the theatre after a brief suspension that had lasted for three days. The public went crazy for the movie, and the theater was packed with people who had heard about what had happened during the premiere. Practically everyone came for the movie, in a hope of "changing the history". Even though the magic movie now followed its original storyline, the masses were still quite frenzied.

This was probably one of the very few pieces of good news in the past one week.

Nonetheless, the multiple accidents deterred Roland from using the Cube-powered steam engine right away. He wanted to first figure out whether the fluctuation of magic power occurred only upon the appearance of the Bloody Moon, or it actually caused continuous events during the whole period of the Battle of Divine Will.

If it only occurred when the Bloody Moon appeared, he was totally fine with that. Roland wanted to defeat the demons, and both Dawn I and the Magic Cube were the key to the victory. They also played an important role in the industrialization of Graycastle. Once the public benefited from these two types of machines, they would soon get addicted to them. However, if the fluctuation would continue to exist until the end of the war, Roland would have to take the potential risks into consideration.

Just then, the telephone rang. It was from the Administrative Office.

Normally, only the director, Barov, would use this line.

Roland heaved a sigh and picked up the phone. "What's the matter now?"

"No, Your Majesty..." Barov said hesitantly. "Astrologer of Dispersion Star just burst into my office and told me that he made a major discovery about the Bloody Moon. He hopes... No, you must come to the observatory and see it for yourself."

Chapter 1221: The Non-existing Bloody Moon

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

As far as Roland knew, the Chief Astrologer was a man of honor and responsibility. Although he had not made any particularly extraordinary contributions to the astronomical research, he had founded the Arithmetic Academy and trained many students. He also assisted with the statistical analysis. In a sense, he extended the influence of the Astrology Association and expanded this old organization into one that could rival the Society of Alchemists.

Dispersion Star had come to apologize multiple times for his negligence and failure to predict the premature appearance of the Bloody Moon. However, as Roland had been too busy with various events lately, he had dismissed him. Nobody ever anticipated that the Bloody Moon would appear so early, and Roland had never intended to rely on the Astrology Association to predict the Bloody Moon. He used their service simply because these scholars knew arithmetics.

The word "must" alarmed Roland. Disperson Star would have never used such an almost impertinent word had this not been an emergency. Therefore, Roland immediately headed to the Arithmetic Academy in the south of the city after he hung up.

The so-called observatory was only an attic of the Arithmetic Academy. The astrologers used this little attic as their temporary observatory before they moved to the top floor of the Miracle Building. Since the construction of the Miracle Building had taken longer than planned, Roland had made them a large telescope and transformed the attic into a revolving observatory so that they could continue with their astrological work.

Dispersion Star and the other astrologers had been waiting for Roland for a while. They soon went to their knee as they saw Roland come in. "Your Majesty," they chorused.

"Please rise," Roland said as he waved his hand casually. "Let's jump into the business. What did you find?"

"Your Majesty, please follow me," Dispersion Star said solemny as he led Roland to the attic at the top.

Roland immediately saw that the floor was littered with drafts and drawings. He believed they were the calculations of the orbits of various stars. In fact, Roland only knew very little about astronomy. After having obtained basic knowledge of physics and mathematics through two years of studying, these astrologers had now surpassed him.

Dispersion Star followed Roland into the attic, leaving the other astrologers outside. The moment the door was shut, Roland noticed that the old Chief Astrologer was wearing an extremely grave expression as if he were about to make his last will.

"Roland..." Nightingale muttered as she tugged his sleeve.

Roland nodded in comprehension. He knew Nightingale would protect him if he was in danger, but he was curious as to why the discovery alerted the astrologers so much.

"Your Majesty, we've been observing the movement of the Bloody Moon these days, as well as its change," Dispersion Star finally spoke after a moment of silence. "Since we failed to predict its appearance, we would like to make amends for our previous faults. We wanted to calculate its size and where its star district is. That's the duty of the Astrologers Association. However, the discovery horrified us."

Horrified? Roland's brows contracted. This was not the word he expected to hear. "What do you mean? Get to the point."

"Yes, Your Majesty," Dispersion Star obeyed in a low voice. "The Star of Extinction is probably a hoax. The Bloody Moon... doesn't exist."

Roland was stunned. He turned around and looked through the window involuntarily. The crimson sphere was still aloft in the air, as sinister as ever.

"Are you saying that the thing over there... doesn't exist?"

"I couldn't believe it either when I made the conclusion. On the contrary, I found it quite amusing. However, gradually, we started to take it seriously," Dispersion Star said after a sigh, and his voice became more confident. "Yes, Your Majesty, it doesn't exist. According to the materials passed down to us and your books, we're positive that the giant star over there doesn't affect other stars."

"When we drew the star chart and calculated the orbits of the other stars in the star district where the Bloody Moon is situated, we found not a single star deviate from its course, which means that the Bloody Moon doesn't affect those stars at all, nor does it affect us."

"In addition, there's no change in its own movement either. Before, the Bloody Moon was stationary in the sky, which indicates that it was moving at the same rate as us. But now, it's still stationary, despite that it's so close. That doesn't make sense."

Roland immediately understood what the old scholar meant. "If we remove it from the sky..."

"Then it'll explain everything," Dispersion Star replied while nodding. "Only when it isn't there will everything on the earth looks normal. In other words, wherever the Bloody Moon is, it won't make a difference to our world."

Roland fell silent.

Now, he understood why the Chief Astrologer had been hesitant. The legend of the Bloody Moon and its relationship with the Battle of Divine Will were solely hearsay stories from the ancient Taquila witches without any solid proof. As the headmaster of the Arithmetic Academy, Dispersion Star had also heard about those witches. If it turned out that the witches were all lying, the discovery would probably jeopardize the healthy relationship between the witches and the king.

But Roland completely trusted the witches. He enjoyed helping Celine conduct research and taking the God's Punishment Witches to the Dream World. Even if they lied, Roland would still like to be with them.

At least, the demons did exist.

"Are you positive?"

"Your Majesty, I wasn't until I received a letter from one of my friends in the old king's city this morning," Dispersion Star said as he produced a piece of paper from his pocket and spread it open. There was a drawing of the Bloody Moon. "As he observed the moon from a different location, the calculation might be a little different. My friend used to be a noble, but he's very interested in astronomy. Therefore, I asked him to calculate the star district from another location. His calculation is very different from ours. It isn't even a minor error. That means that the Bloody Moon is stationary everywhere. It's not only stationary in relation to this area but to the whole continent!"

Roland's heart skipped a beat.

"Your Majesty, it isn't possible that a physical object remains stationary in relation to everything!" Dispersion Star proclaimed slowly.

Roland suddenly remembered the red speck in the Dream World. It was always the same no matter how he viewed it.

In the Dream World, it had a different name.

Erosion.

Chapter 1222: The Promise of the Divine Will

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

"Your Majesty, Your Majesty... Your Majesty?" Dispersion Star's voice startled Roland.

"Er..." Roland rubbed his forehead and said, "Does anyone else know about it?"

"Only astrologers named after a star know it. The students in the Arithmetic Academy don't know," the old scholar said as he knelt down.

Roland now understood why the astrologers were all wearing a stern expression as though they were facing a death sentence. Apparently, they believed that Roland would kill them to prevent their betrayal of the horrific truth about the Bloody Moon, for the real purpose of founding this Astrology Association was to explore the Star of Extinction, which was a secret that only the royals were entitled to.

These astrologers were expert in political games, so they naturally knew the consequence of their discovery. Roland was impressed with their caution and loyalty. He shook his head and said, "You did a great job. Don't tell anyone about it. Keep up with the good work. Continue to manage the Arithmetic Academy and forget about astrology. Compared to something that doesn't exist, helping with Neverwinter is apparently more important."

With these words, Roland left the attic, leaving the stunned scholar behind.

"Let's head back to the castle," Roland said in a low voice.

He walked in a even more brisque manner than when he had come and almost broke into a trot.

"Do you think the astrologers are telling the truth?" Nightingale asked as she revealed herself.

"I don't know... I just have a hunch," Roland said. "It doesn't mean that the Bloody Moon doesn't exist. Perhaps, it's something else..."

"Something... else?"

"For example, a pit."

Roland had never given much thought about the Bloody Moon. It was giant because it was close to the earth. For example, the Jupiter observed on io took up two thirds of the sky. People here called this object a moon simply because it was round with a soft glow.

If this was an Erosion, then it could be a square or a polygon.

Nightingale asked in confusion, "Are you saying that the sky is cracking?"

"It may be even worse than that, but I have to find it out first."

"How?"

Roland cast her a glance and answered, "By dreaming."

...

Although it was not yet his typical sleeping hour, nobody had forbidden Roland to enter the Dream World during the day. This time, he did not inform any of the God's Punishment Witches but only asked Nightingale to guard him.

"We'll meet upon the appearance of the Divine Will."

Roland had had no idea what the Divine Will was. Now, he suddenly came to the realization that the messenger was not referring to the time in the Dream World but that in the real world.

It was incredible that the messenger knew the true nature of the Dream World and even had knowledge of the real world. The messenger could probably even sense the change in both worlds. All Roland's suspicions seemed to have been confirmed when Dispersion Star had said "the Bloody Moon doesn't exist". Both the "Battle of Divine Will" described by the executives in the Prism City and the anonymous book led Roland to the same conclusion.

"What are you going to eat for breakfast?" Zero asked him, with a toothbrush between her teeth as she stood in front of the sink.

"I'm not having breakfast today. You can eat alone!" Roland shouted without looking back. He pulled on his coat briskly and rushed out on his slippers.

The alley below the apartment was alive with people. The breakfast booths where deep-fried doughs and buns were sold were surrounded by students and young professionals. The residential area was teeming with the raucous voices of yelling vendors and the sizzling sounds of the deep-fried doughs.

The only place that seemed to immune to all these noises was the Rose Café.

The coffeeshop was like a loner slinking outside the mainstream community. When Roland took out the key and opened the door, he could see the vendor across the street cast him a pitiful and scornful look that people typically afforded to an idiot.

Roland took a deep breath and went straight to Room 302. The shop was on the ground floor, but Roland insisted the room number to be 302. It was a a little strange, but he did not care about it.

Since Roland had been busy dealing with the incidents in Neverwinter, he had kind of forgotten about the Dream World for a while. Therefore, when he pushed open the door, he felt, surprisingly, a little nervous.

Roland did not care about whether the messenger would be able to get into the closed shop. As the messenger could send a message to him through the champagne glass, he certainly possessed some extraordinary power. Perhaps, the messenger would pop up somewhere out of nowhere abruptly.

Roland took a deep breath and put his hand on the doorknob.

The shop was empty.

Apart from a table and four chairs, there was no further furniture. Certainly, there was no hiding spot either.

A little disappointed, Roland slowly walked to the table and sat down.

Was he wrong?

Then he realized that the messenger was not an apparition after all, who could travel from one place to another in a split second. Perhaps, he should wait for while.

But Roland became more and more uncertain.

Could the messenger really find this place that had just opened a month ago? What if he was waiting at another place?

Could the note be a hoax that had nothing to do with the Divine Will in the real world?

Roland had not a shred of evidence to his theory.

Apparently, it would not be that easy to solve the problem.

When Roland was about to leave the shop, suddenly, the bell rang.

Clink and clang.

"Welcome to — " Roland's words rested on the tip of his tongue. The God's Punishment Witches did not come with him this time, and Garcia would not visit his store very often either. No customer should come here considering the absurd prices listed outside. When Roland opened the door, he saw a familiar figure outside the shop.

Roland had seen her twice.

He had met her during the orientation for new martialists in the Prism City.

He had also met her in the Reflection Church in the old Holy City of Hermes.

Roland remembered this face.

"I didn't expect that you would open a coffeeshop here and name it 'Rose Cafe'. I thought you didn't find that note."

Lan said.

Chapter 1223: Lan

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Roland was a little surprised to see Lan, although he had somehow predicted that she would come. He asked, "Who are you exactly?"

"A person who needs help," Lan said while looking around. "I understand you have a lot of questions for me. We can sit down and have a chat. Let's sit over there by the window."

"Don't we need to go to Room 302?" Roland asked as he watched Lan take the seat.

"The reason I asked you to meet me here is to avoid curious ears. Since nobody's here, just take a seat you like," Lan said casually. "By the way, as this is a coffeeshop, can I have an ice coffee?"

"I thought you were disclosing a big secret to me, so I've been very cautious, making sure that nobody will overhear us."

"A secret will only become a secret when the eavesdropper recognizes its value. I monitor the Erosion underground every day and do need to take a break from time to time," Lan said gracefully. "One ice coffee, please."

Roland gazed at her for a second and then grumbled, "I only have instant coffee here."

"That's fine."

Roland was a little frustrated to see Lan act as if she were the owner of the shop. He added some milk to the coffee and put two ice cubes in it. His eyes were glued to Lan during the whole process.

"Rest assured. I won't disappear," Lan said while shrugging.

"I don't know about that," Roland said, his eyes fixed on Lan resolutely. "I once asked Garcia to contact you and went to the Prism City twice, but you vanished. Why didn't you talk to me? Why did you just leave me a note?"

Lan lapsed into a short silence before she answered on a sigh, "Because we weren't ready yet at that time, child."

Weren't ready? A little astonished, Roland pursued, "You mean you've been waiting for me to find out about the Bloody Moon, well, the Erosion myself?"

"You're quite smart. I now expect more from you."

"Expect what from me?" Roland grunted. "You don't look like a person who needs help."

"Then what should I do to convince you? Do I have to beg and cry for your help? Or you want a reward from me?" Lan said while shaking her head. "No, I don't think you'd trust me even I did so. That'll only push you away."

Roland wanted to joke around, saying "You never know", but somehow the words abandoned him. Lan was much older than Garcia. She was the Chief Disciple of the Defendender of the Martialist Association, the senior of his senior. If she was really the person in the Reflection Church, she was probably 700 to 800 years old, a historical figure, so to speak. At this thought, Roland put up a more serious look.

"Alright..." Roland said as he sat down across the table, and went over the questions he had in his head. "Were you a member of the Union?"

"I have nothing to do with your world," Lan replied. "I was born here and will also die here, although it's won't happen until many many years later."

"But I saw your portrait in the Reflection Church — "

"That's nothing," Lan interrupted Roland. "It's just a historical record that doesn't really say anything."

"But what are the odds that you and the person in the picture look exactly the same!" Roland argued while knitting his brows.

"If you think further, there are many coincidences in the history. Compared to dwelling on something in the past, you'd better focus on the present."

Roland knew Lan might be pretending. Without Nightingale, he could not tell whether she was telling the truth or not. There was no point in keeping arguing with her, so he immediately changed his question.

"So, what's magic power exactly?"

Lan's lips curled into a smile. She said, "You probably have already known it. Nothing in this world could explain it because it doesn't belong here. Low lives don't have the capability to understand higher animals. What we know now is that we can use it. Therefore, you could view it as 'a power we obtain by accident'."

From Lan's words, Roland judged that magic was like the Force of Nature, or perhaps simply another form of the Force of Nature. Because of magic power, the Dream World became the way it was. Roland thus asked, "So the book, 'Raison d'être', you mentioned in your speech during the orientation in the Prism City, and your deduction were all true?"

The most two pressing questions Roland had now were the nature and origin of the Erosion and the reason for the endless Battle of Divine Will.

"Not really, but you could think that way," Lan said quickly.

"I want to know the truth."

"It's beyond the scope of your understanding, and it's impossible to describe it in your language," Lan said after sipping the coffee. "Plus, everything I do is under God's watch. If I give away any information that'll potentially endanger Him, both of the two worlds will be destroyed. Hence, please remember that the truth is what you understand."

Roland twitched his lips in amusement. Lan could have directly told him that she would rather lie than tell the truth.

"He can destroy the two worlds?"

"That's why we call Him God. It's the closest word to describe Him in your language."

"What does He want?"

"To keep the Battle of Divine Will going."

"What's your relationship with God?"

Lan fell silent and then replied hesitantly, "I betrayed Him."

"Betrayed?"

"Yes. The war will continue, and I don't want to be stuck here forever. A new cycle means another round of loss. God will eventually exhaust His power. By that time, both worlds will be devastated."

Roland stared directly into Lan's eyes before he asked, "So, why did you come to seek me?"

"I need your help, child," Lan said and gazed at Roland. "I want you to stop the Battle of Divine Will and put this cycle to an end."

"You mean to win the war?"

"No, that'll start a new cycle," Lan said while shaking her head. "I want you to stop everything and replace God!"

Roland was astounded. He had never anticipated that.

He took a deep breath and said, "Sorry, I'm afraid I can't help you."

"Why?" Lan asked. Her expression finally changed.

"I don't know whether you're telling the truth. You admit that you could only give me some evasive answers to avoid raising God's suspicion. Sometimes, one single word could mislead a person. What if you lie to me? You betrayed God once, and you can certainly betray me," Roland said while spreading out his hands. "I'm not good at taking risks. So, look for someone else to replace God."

"If you could help me — "

"Don't," Roland interrupted. "You said there was no reward. You told me a reward would make things worse."

Lan fixed her eyes onto Roland for about 10 minutes before she conceded, "No, I changed my mind."

"I'm determined," Roland said as he rose and poured himself a coffee. "An empty promise doesn't mean anything, although it sounds pretty nice."

"You should at least let me finish."

"I've told you — "

"I can bring Ashes back to life."

"Crash!"

Roland was aghasted. The glass in his hand slipped through his fingers, fell on the floor and broke into pieces.

Chapter 1224: The Remedy

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

"How do you know her?"

Lan said placidly, "Although I was born here, it doesn't mean I know nothing about your world. Have you heard of the 'Realm of Mind' or the Origin of Magic?"

Roland immediately thought of Kabradhabi's statement. His hand that was going to reach out to the broken cup on the floor paused in the air for a second. Then he suddenly threw himself over the table and asked Lan in a low voice, "Is she in the Realm of Mind?"

"Of course not, but she left a mark in the Realm of Mind. Anyone who has sufficient power will leave a mark in the Realm of Mind." Lan paused for a second before she resumed, "I know what you want to ask about. You want to know how to bring her back to life and then do it yourself. You also want to know how to stop the Battle of Divine Will. However, I have to tell you that we don't have much time."

"What do you mean?"

"People will eventually fade out of the Realm of Mind. This process is irreversable. Even if you know the method, you probably won't have enough time to suit the action to the plan, and this isn't the worst scenario yet."

"What's the worst scenario?"

"The Dream World has intruded God's mind, and He won't let things keep going like this. "In other words, when God believes that nothing could put things back on track, He'll destroy the two worlds. The situation is even more pressing than you think, and that's why I made up my mind to persuade you," Lan said slowly. "Child, help me, and you'll be also helping yourself."

"Sounds quite convincing," Roland commented sarcastically. "But you just said that the truth was what I understand. In other words, you can be lying to me right now, including the part about bringing Ashes back to life."

Lan heaved a deep sigh and leaned against the chair. "You can think that way as well, as I don't want to give you false hopes. I did so because I do want you to trust me."

Roland fell silent.

For Roland, it was a tough choice to make.

Lan's argument was quite solid. Roland had indeed heard a lot about the threat to the Dream World from the magic creature. He was certain that these magic creatures aimed to destroy this world. After hearing Lan's explanation, Roland believed that those creatures were actually God's "underlings".

However, he could not trust Lan completely without confirming the validity of the information himself. All the information that Lan had just related to him regarding the potential harm to God was just her version of the story. It might be totally wrong, and Roland could not jump to the conclusion based on false information.

However, he had not enough time to verify himself.

Under such circumstances, the only way was to take risks.

Roland closed his eyes and remembered that Tilly had cried her eyes out that night. He had noticed that the painful loss had dimmed the light in her eyes, as though a gemstone once dazzling was now incubated in a light sheet of dust. Some people maintained that such a change marked spiritual maturity. Only when one truly lost something would he began to cherish what he used to have. Roland dismissed such an absurd theory. A mature person would never allow himself to lose what he cherished and certainly would not let himself wallow in pain.

If he could bring Ashes back to life, he would do everything he could to attain his end.

Roland suppressed his excitement and put up a perturbed look as he sat down again across the table.

"I can't trust you just yet. I need to hear how you're going to bring her back to life?"

"It doesn't conflict with what I want you to help me with. In fact, they're actually the same thing," Lan said slowly. "First of all, you have to get into the Realm of Mind in both worlds simultaneously. Otherwise, we won't be able to proceed."

Roland asked in surprise, "Two worlds? Hang on, are you saying that the so-called Origin of Magic does exist?"

"That's right. It's not something intangible but a physical entity. It's entirely different from the hollow created by the Erosion," Lan replied while nodding. "In fact, it's at the north end of the Land of Dawn, and we call it the Bottomless Land."

Roland's heart skipped a beat. He had heard this word somewhere else.

"But the demons have taken over the north. You know demons, right? They're my enemy in this Battle of Divine Will."

"I can't help you with anything regarding the other world. God forbids me to interfere with the Battle of Divine Will. You must find a way out yourself," Lan said flatly. "Beat them and get to the Bottomless Land. If you fail, then it'll be over."

That was why Lan said even if he knew the method, he wouldn't have much time to achieve his goal.

Roland pondered for a while and then said, "Alright. I'm going to wipe the demons off the face of the Land of Dawn anyway. Then how to get to the Realm of Mind in the Dream World? It's not a real world after all, so it won't be that hard, right?"

"Before I answer you, I want to ask you something," Lan said as she looked through the window. "Do you really think that this world is a fake one?"

Roland stiffened for a second and also rested his eyes on the people outside. There were fewer people now on the street after the rush hour. Many vendors were taking a rest, and some were ready to head back home in contentment. Others were reading newspaper while smoking cigarettes.

Now, the students and young professionals were all gone. The elders started to come out and head to grocery stores. When they passed the Rose Café, they cast contemptuous glances at the shop and exchanged murmurs with a derisive air.

Roland knew that if he went out there and argued with them, these elder people might retort fiercely. The verbal altercation might also attract many curious, gloating onlookers. Roland certainly did not want to become the center of an improvised show.

He found it hard to admit that this world was real.

"How to define reality?" Lan murmured absent-mindedly. "Must a living being have a physical body? If this entity has consciousness and emotions, isn't it enough to be alive, even though it's in the form of energy?"

"Well, I think it is."

Lan turned around and said, "Then protect this world. Once it's destroyed, everything here will disappear. It'll be a greater loss than anything in the other world. If you lose this Dream World, then you'll be shut out from the Realm of Mind forever."

"Is the entrance to the Realm of Mind in this city?"

"Actually, you're in the Realm of Mind right now," Lan corrected him. "This is the Realm of Mind."

Roland's eyes were wide open.

In other words, his body was still in Neverwinter, whereas his mind was at the Bottomless Land in the north of the continent thousands of miles away?

Chapter 1225: The Remedy (II)

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

"Is this also the result of magic power?"

"Yes. There are so many types of magic power that I just can't explain every single one of them. It's a power that transcends the four fundamental forces, the ultimate solution to the great unification, if that makes sense to you," Lan explained mildly. "Nevertheless, it doesn't mean that you can enter God's territory and interfere with the Battle of Divine Will. This world is an independent one. It's protected by a thick membrane. That's why I can sit here and talk to you."

For some reason, Lan's explanation reminded Roland of bubble blowing. Among those floating bubbles, one of them housed the Dream World. He then asked, "Then how do I penetrate it?"

"The same way the magic power enters our world — through the Erosion."

"Er... could you tell me more about it?"

"You should have already noticed that this world has changed a lot," Lan resumed, and Roland could feel his heart beat frantically in his chest. "At first, it was just a reflection of your mind, but there are now many things you've never seen before. The change started when you began to collect the Forces of Nature."

"You even know that?" Roland exclaimed in surprise.

"I've been wandering about in the Realm of Mind since I was born, so I can sense even the most subtle change." Lan continued, "Listen, child. Both the Dream World and God's territory are driven by magic power. We call it the Force of Nature. When you continue to collect them, this world will expand and overlap with God's territory. That's the reason why Erosions appear."

Roland had heard about this theory during the orientation. He thus said, "As far as I know, the Martialist Association has collected many cores of the fallen Force of Nature. If you want to collect as many of them as you can, why not just support the the Fallens?"

To Roland's surprise, Lan did not object his proposal but simply summoned a bitter smile. "Unfortunately, I'm just the Defender's student. I can't take you to the central hub in the Prism City."

"You don't mind turning against the Association?"

"If it could stop the Battle of Divine Will, I won't. Once the Battle of Divine Will ends, there'll be no Erosion in the Dream World, so in a way, I'm still helping the Association. But that child... She'll be very disappointed, for she has put so much faith in you."

Lan suddenly put up a very regretted look as she said these words.

Was she referring to Garcia?

Roland was a little surprised that Lan had such a deep affection toward Garcia. As a God's servant, she should have lived hundreds of years, and nothing should have been able to perturb her mind.

Was she acting or was she actually too involved in her role?

"Well, this isn't the only way." Roland wanted to get some coffee to ease up the tension in the air when he suddenly realized that the cup was already broken. He thus withdrew his hand and said, "You also said that I have to enter the Realm of Mind in the two worlds simultaneously, right? Perhaps, by that time, we would have had enough cores. The only problem is that how I am supposed to know that the Dream World has already overlapped with God's territory? We can't really enter God's territory from the Erosion in the Prism City, can we?"

"Of course not. The hollow created by the Erosion there is the area of nothingness in the Realm of Mind. It's completely a different thing," Lan said while nodding. "As for when the Erosion will affect God's territory, you'll know when that day comes. However, this will also mark the beginning of the destruction of the two worlds. Therefore, you must find a way to the Bottomless Land before that."

"And then?"

Lan shook her head.

It appeared that Lan could not disclose any more than that, otherwise she would bring harm to God. Nevertheless, there was also a possibility that Lan chose to hold the information back intentionally. Roland had now a basic understanding of what he should do. In fact, he had planned to drive the demons out of the Land of Dawn and earn some extra income by killing the Fallen Evils a long time ago, so Lan's information did not really change much of what he was doing. The only change was that he now probably had to fight both the demons and the Fallen Evils at the same time.

Roland was not certain what he would encounter at the Bottomless Land. Lan did not say anything about that. If this was a trap, the only part where Lan might lie to him was when she asked him to replace God.

Roland did not think God would surrender after he penetrated the Realm of Mind. Since everything sounded so vague to him, he had to proceed with extra caution.

Another question that bothered Roland was that why she chose him.

As far as Roland could see, Lan could totally pick someone else to help her. Although Lan looked like human, Roland was certain she was not any ordinary woman. Human beings had been defeated once. Given that, she could completely pick a demon or someone in the Sky-sea Realm to achieve her goal.

According to Lan, the north of the Land of Dawn where the Bottomless Land was situated had been taken over by the demons. Kabradhabi had also confirmed that the enemy in the Sky-sea Realm was quite overpowering. The demons apparently had a hard time keeping their land. These two races were obviously far more powerful than the mankind. In a sense, they were almost halfway through the mission.

Roland was not yet that arrogant as to believe that he was the only person who could leave a mark in the Realm of Mind.

At least, Zero had that power too. Dimly, Roland had a feeling that the Battlefield of Soul was a demonstration of the power struggle in the Realm of Mind.

The Dream World originated from there.

He thus asked, "I bet... that I'm not the first person you sought help."

Lan replied immediately, "Yes, I turned to someone else for help as well over the past thousand years."

Roland felt his chest constrict. He pursued, "Also including demons?"

"I don't know much about the other world. After I left the Divine Land, I lost my power of connecting with other servants, but I can tell you that I'm not the only traitor."

"Who's the last person you talked to regarding this matter? Zero?"

"The Dream Courier, Alfina. She lived 869 years ago."

The name was unfamiliar to him. Roland asked, "None of my preceders succeeded?"

Lan sighed, "You probably think it's pretty easy for us to talk face to face like this, but the fact was that they didn't even manage the first step, which was to stablize themselves in the Realm of Mind and establish effective comunication. Also, I had to phrase the matter in a way that made sense to them. In other words, they had to understand what I was saying. Only in that way would the message be successfully delivered. The more they understood, the better reply they could formulate. This rule applied to both you and the demons."

"Like you have to share the same mindset?"

"Exactly. In fact, you're the first person with whom I can effectively communicate. Although I don't know where you obtained so much knowledge, far more than what this era actually needs, I'm glad I found you."

"Well..." Roland said hesitantly. "What if I fail?"

Lan said after a moment of silence, "I'll continue to wait until the next person appears. I'll wait until someone frees me, or until... God kills me."

Chapter 1226: The Prison of the Heart

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“What will the world look like when God is gone,” Roland asked tentatively. “What will you gain from this? Are you able to leave the Realm of Mind and become a physical entity?”

“To be honest, I don’t know,” Lan said with a smile. “But anyhow, it’s better than being imprisoned here forever. At least, there are hopes.”

Roland gazed at her for a while. There was not the faintest hint of uneasiness on Lan’s countenance. She acted as if just making a very simple decision.

It appeared that he could not get anything more out of her, unless he brought Nightingale into the Dream World. Their subsequent conversation did not go anywhere either. Every time Roland asked about God, Lan kept her mouth clamp shut and reiterated that she could not help him with the Battle of Divine Will.

Lan told Roland that she could do nothing more than living here as a martialist and delivering him messages. According to Lan, there were various rules that governed the Realm of Mind. Even God might not be able to change those rules at His will. Because of such restrictions, Lan had finally found a chance to look for the person who could terminate the Battle of Divine Will.

Nevertheless, she would not be able to gain total freedom until the war was stopped. All the rules and restrictions still applied to her, and her work could be subotaged anytime.

When Roland walked Lan out, he asked one last question.

“By the way, you said you didn’t expect me to open a coffeeshop here. Is there another Rose Café somewhere in this city?”

“Yes,” Lan said while smiling faintly. “It’s in the Prism City.”

“But I’ve asked Garcia…”

“The coffeeshop is in the central part of the city. It’s only accessible to the executives of the Martialist Association. At that time, I already knew that the Association would license you, so you would be able to get there via your hunting license. However, you don’t have the slightest interest in the Association, which really surprised me. You’ve never been to the Prism City since you got your license.” Lan paused for a second before she resumed, “Also, for your information, the central hub where we store the cores of the Fallen Evils is located at the bottom level of the city. Normally, only the Defenders and their seniors have access to it.”

Now, Roland finally understood why he could not find the Rose Café. It was actually a coffeeshop exclusive to the executives of the Association.

“So where shall we meet again next time? I mean if we plan to meet again, which coffeeshop? Now there are two Rose Cafés.”

“This one would be better,” Lan said as she looked up at the towering apartment building. “Garcia should be living here, right? It’s not a bad idea to visit her every now and then. I would probably… like it here a lot.”

“Probably? She doesn’t know her likings?” Roland thought to himself, his brows raised, but he remained silent.

Then they parted, and Roland saw Lan gradually disappear from his sight.

Roland leaned against the shop door while revisiting their conversation.

Both the Dream World and the real world seemed to be more understandable now. Words like magic power, Divine Will, the Realm of Mind, the Land of Dawn, and the Fathomless Abyss all became more concrete and made more sense to him.

While Roland was lost in thought, suddenly, he felt a queer quaver steal through him!

Roland looked up abruptly and saw a distorted, transparent wave sweep over the entire alley and soon ripple across the whole area.

What had happened?

He was surprised that the residents in this community seemed to be unconscious of the change, for they were still talking and laughing as if nothing had happened.

Roland almost thought that he was hallucinating.

But he knew, based on his past experience, that this was a change only visible to him. It was a fluctuation of power that he sensed when he collected the cores of the magic creatures. Roland clenched his fists. It was quite a pleasant sensation, but he somehow felt a little unsettled this time.

Did something impact the Dream World?

Lan was gone, and he had not obtained a phone exclusive to Association members from the Prism City. Otherwise, he could have asked her about it.

Roland thus closed the coffeeshop and returned to the apartment.

He had planned to disconnect the dream and go back to reality. However, when he entered Room 0825, he saw Zero’s sneakers at the doorstep.

Roland wondered why Zero had not gone to school yet. He had been with Lan in the coffeeshop for over an hour.

To his dismay, he found the little girl lie on the floor. There were two broken glasses not far away.

“You gotta be kidding me…”

Roland strode over to the little girl and clasped her wrist.

He felt the pulse.

Then he noticed that Zero looked feverish, her eyes shut and her brows contracted, as though she was suffering a great pain.

Roland’s hand reached onto Zero’s forehead. It was burning.

Did she have a fever?

From where she fell, Roland judged that Zero probably had lost her balance when she was trying to clean the coffee table.

“Damn it. She was alright this morning.”

But Roland was relieved that there was no Fallen Evils involved. The moment he had seen Zero fall on the floor, he had thought that God had come to seek revenge.

Roland thus held Zero in his arms, sped down a flight of stairs, and climbed into the mini van.

At this moment, Zero gained her consciousness. She opened her eyes and muttered, “I… broke the glasses… on the table.”

“I saw it.”

“S-sorry, I’ll… pay you. I don’t… want to go back to the countryside.”

“Is she so sick that she’s out of her mind?”

Roland put Zero in the passenger seat and fastened the seatbelt. “Stop talking,” he said.

Then Zero suddenly stretched out her hand and spoke again when Roland was about to turn on the engine, “Don’t go…”

Roland had never seen Zero, who always spoke to him in a defiant and almost trenchant manner, look so fragile and helpless. He somehow thought of what she had written in her diary. Perhaps, the fever brought about the most tender part of her personality. Roland did not know how her families used to treat her. At these thoughts, Roland heaved a sigh and said, “Don’t worry, you still owe me rents. I won’t let you go.”

After receiving the confirmation, Zero closed her eyes, but she did not relinquish her grip.

It was already afternoon when Zero was hospitalized. Although the cause of the fever remained unknown, Zero looked a little better.

The doctor did not come until late evening.

“Are you really a martialist?

“Yes, what’s the matter?” Roland asked.

“This isn’t funny,” the doctor grunted. “The girl isn’t sick at all. She’s simply awakened. Some people will indeed feel not very well when they’re awakened, although it’s not very common. Didn’t the Martialist Association tell you about that?”

“What?”

“Awakened! What a mess. If there weren’t a martialist in the hospital, I would have thought it’s some rare disease,” the doctor said dismissively. “You can go now. Take her home.”

…

So Roland brought Zero back to the apartment building.

He let out a deep sigh as he stared at the white-haired girl curling up in his arms. As a former Pure Witch, it appeared that she was destined to have magic power. Fortunately, Zero was now living in the Dream World, so she would probably not make the same mistake as she had done in her previous life.

Darkness had now pressed in. The long corridor outside was bathing in a soft, warm glow. A few bugs flew toward the light source. When Roland approached Room 0825, he found, surprisingly, a familiar figure. It was Garcia. She was sitting at the doorstep while leaning against the door.

“What’s going on today?” Roland wondered. “Everyone seems to come look for me.” He had told Nightingale that he would only have a short nap. Now it was probably time for dinner in the other world.

“Hey,” Roland greeted Garcia as he crouched down. “What brought you here? Did you lose your key and want to stay over?”

However, Garcia neither responded nor sneered as she usually did, and Roland realized that something was wrong.

All the words rested on the tip of his tongue when he saw Garcia’s face.

It was glazed with tears.

“A large number of Fallen Evils attacked the Prism City. Someone who escaped told me that my master… my master stayed behind to protect others and was killed by the Fallen Evils…”

Chapter 1227: The Fall of Prism City

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Roland was stunned.

If he remembered correctly, Garcia’s master was called Lan.

Which meant that the lady who had met him in the Rose Café this morning was… dead?

How could it be possible?

Even though Lan was bound by the rules in the Dream World, she was, after all, the Defender’s student and should have the capability to deal with Fallen Evils.

The Prism City used to be a mine, so the main part of it was built underground. It was constantly guarded by the Awakened. How could the Fallen Evils breach the city so easily?

There were so many things that Roland failed to understand, but he managed to calm Garcia down. “Get in first.”

Garcia rose feebly as if all her strength was gone.

Roland put Zero in her bedroom and gave Garcia a glass of water. The latter gradually regained her composure, although her eyes were still kind of out of focus, but she, at least, stopped crying.

Roland then noticed that there were six unread messages and a dozen phone calls. He scrolled down and realized that they were mostly from Garcia.

“Oh, sorry… Zero suddenly got a fever, so I had to go to hospital and left my phone here,” Roland said in embarrassment. “What happened in the Prism City? How did you know that your master was killed.”

It took a long time for Garcia to find her voice. After what seemed to be an eternal silence, Garcia finally broke out inarticulately, “I received an urgent message from C02 around noon, saying that something happened to the headquarters. He requested support from martialists from all over the world.”

Roland remembered that C02 was the liaison officer for that joint mission he had attended a while ago. Now, he understood why Garcia had called him so many times, so he asked, “But nobody went there?”

Garcia should have immediately gone to the Prism City.

“Nobody was able to, because the Erosion in the middle part of the building suddenly expanded,” she muttered. “Nobody knew how it happened, and the video camera didn’t catch it either. C02 told me that by the time the Association realized it, the Erosion had already slashed the Prism City in half, and all the connection between the upper and lower floors were disrupted.”

“The Erosion expanded?” Roland’s heart pounded against his ribs like a frantic bird. If the Bloody Moon was actually the hollow created by the Erosion, it should have been able to appear anywhere, including the underground area. If the emergence of the Bloody Moon marked the beginning of the Battle of Divine Will, then could the expansion of the Erosion be another form of Bloody Moon?

“When did it occur? Do you know?”

Garcia nodded slightly and said, “Around 9:00 in the morning.”

That was almost the same time he had seen that wave!

Was it a warning from the Dream World that the Erosion had begun?

“Then what about the Fallen Evils?”

“They… they came out from underground…”

Half an hour later, Roland finally had a full picture of the incident.

Noticing that the Erosion had reached the middle part of the building, the Martialist Association immediately decided to send reinforcements. The Prism City wedged into the ground like a giant awl. Although it was well fortified, there were also several drawbacks in its architectural structure. For example, they must constantly maintain the ventilation system to make sure that people on the lower floors could breathe easily. Apart from that, all the life essentials, such as water and food, had to be transported from the upper level to the bottom. Therefore, when the supplies were cut off by the Erosion, the staff at the bottom level might be in peril.

The most pressing task for the Association now was to find out how large the Erosion was and then reconnect the upper and lower level. The archtects who had built the Prism City had indeed also thought about the possible disconnection and thus equipped the building with a few evacuation exits so that people could quickly escape the building in an orderly manner upon an emergency.

Since the Martialist Association figured out that the disruption was caused by the Erosion rather than an enemy attack, they soon withdrew the reinforcement request. At that time, the Defender and his students were all there in the building, and what the Association actually needed was the engineering team and paramedics, so the martialists did not come to rescue at once but waited for further instructions.

However, something out of expection had happened.

While everyone was going down through the evaucation exists, Lan and her team at Exit No. 04 were suddenly attacked by the Fallen Evils.

Later, somebody noticed that many Fallen Evils used to be their colleagues on the lower level.

It was quite shocking and incredible news. Nobody knew what had happened at the lower part of the building a few hours after the disruption. What they saw was a group of monsters with fallen cores transformed from ordinary staff members and martialists.

Most people at the lower part of the Prism City were elites of the Association. What had made them betray the Association within half a day remained as a mystery. However, the moment they had chosen to merge with the fallen cores, they were no longer human. Even Roland was astonished at the turn of the event, let alone the rescue team at the scene.

That was why Lan’s team had been caught offguard.

It was a miracle that a few people managed to escape when the whole team was outnumbered and overpowered. However, the team leader Lan did not make it. Some Fallen Evils attacked her when she was trying to close a door.

At these words, Garcia started to sob again.

Roland handed her another glass of milk. After a moment of hesitation, he asked what concerned him most. He knew it was not a good time to ask a question like this, but he must know the answer.

Roland took a deep breath and said, “These are all what the survivers reported to the headquarters, right? Did anyone actually see it when your master was killed?”

Garcia would have retorted ferociously had she not been so perturbed and devastated. She croaked, “My master… my master blocked the switch that controls the door… Then she was torn to pieces by the Fallen Evils… Many people in her team saw it…” Her voice again perished into a suppressed sob.

“… I’m sorry,” Roland sighed.

He did not know what would happen to a dead person in the Dream World. Would she return to the Realm of Mind or completely disappear? If God did control almost everything in the Realm of Mind, neither would be a happy ending. Without the protection of the Dream World, Lan, as a traitor, would definitely be punished severely.

Roland had a very good reason to suspect God, for this attack seemed to be targetting Lan.

And Lan was not the only person God intended to eliminate.

He wanted to tear down the whole Dream World.

“If you lose this Dream World, then you’ll be shut out from the Realm of Mind forever,” Lan’s voice reverberated across his head.

It appeared that there was going to be a Battle of Divine Will in the Dream World as well.

His enemy, however, was neither the demons nor those in the Sky-sea Realm.

He would be confronting God directly.

…

“Hold on…”

She heard loud noises. Sometimes the noises were so far away, but sometimes they were suddenly so close.

What had happened?

She felt excruciating pain. It seemed that her leg was broken. She had never suffered so severe injuries before, not even at the upgrade ceremony.

For a split second, she thought of death.

“Ah, right, I’m dying,” she thought. She felt that her body gradually turn cold, her mind drifting off. She felt hard to concentrate.

“Hold on…”

The voice drew nearer.

Was there somebody out there?

Strange… she had heard this voice somewhere before.

“Someone’s still alive here. Can anybody help me remove this stupid stone?”

“She’s hurt badly. Quick, move!”

“One, two, three!”

Suddenly, the weight on her was lifted, and she was transferred to a soft bed.

“Hold on. You’ll be OK,” someone talked to her from above. “The Association has sent for the best doctor and medical equipment. You’ll be fine once you get to the hospital!”

“The Erosion expanded?”

“By the way, you came from Cargarde Peninsula, right? What’s your name?”

“My… my name?”

“Yes, do you still remember it?”

She used all her strength to reply.

“… Valkries.”

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

At the entrance to the Prism City.

The whole square was lit up, and the roar of machines rented the air. The rescue had lasted for nearly 16 hours, and the Defender, Rock, was waiting in the temporary tent for the latest news with a steely look on his face.

It was rumored that nothing could unsettle him. However, this was a mistake. Lan’s death actually shocked him a great deal, and he blamed himself for not fighting the Fallen Evils. Yet he knew it was not advisable to lament the loss now. The first thing he needed to do at present was to find out what was going on at the bottom level of the building.

After Exit No. 4 was under attack, Exits 01 and 05 were also surrounded by the Fallen Evils. Fortunately, the rescue team there learned Lan’s lesson and eradicated the enemies at a minimal cost, but the casualty rate was still astonishing. Like what had happened at Exit 04, all the Fallen Evils were transformed from the staff members at the bottom level. The death toll had reached 320, which was almost the total number of the staff members on duty.

Clearly, it would not be long before the Fallen Evils took over the entire bottom floor.

Rock did not know why those people would merge with the fallen cores within just a few hours of the breach. The Prism City was equipped with the most advanced emergency system. Even if the bottom floor was completely cut off, they could still sustain themselves for a while. They should have known that the Association would never abandon its members. As long as the exits were not blocked, they would soon be able to escape.

However, Rock currently had no time to give it much thought. He was only concerned about the status of the central hub. There were more than 3,000 fallen cores stored in the central hub. If those cores were released to the public, the consequence would be disastrous. There would be far more than 300 Fallen Evils as they were facing now.

“Mr. Rock.” Just at that moment, a man in a suit came into the temporary headquarters and whispered to him.

“Are we really so unlucky?” Rock’s face clouded over. The rescue team had just told him that the Erosion had suddenly expanded. There were two groups of touring martialists from Cargarde Peninsula currently in the Prism City. Since the Erosion had destroyed the middle part of the building, the floor closest to the Erosion slid into a hollow, and the two touring groups thus fell.

Based on the current situation, these tourists might not be able to survive.

“What should we do?” the man in the suit consulted. “Some celebrated martialists from Cargarde are among them. If we fail to handle this crisis properly, we may be caught in some diplomatic problem.”

“Try to find them and save as many as we can. How do I know what we should do? It’s something beyond our control.”

“But the Defender from the peninsula may not listen to you…”

Rock lapsed into a short silence and said, “I see. Just hush this thing down. I’ll ask the director of the Sky City to assist us.”

As soon as the suit man left, a liaison officer came up to Rock.

“We’ve heard something from Exit 01! They’ve opened up a passage and are now going down!”

“Connect them to the main screen,” Rock said in a low voice.

“Got it!”

After a brief noise screen, Rock saw what was going on at the front. From the shooting angle, he judged that the video footage was transmitted from the head-mounted camera that the team leader was wearing. The lighting down there appeared to be quite good, although a few lights were flickering. The emergency electric motor seemed to be working, so the elevator was still functioning. This could indeed save the rescue team a lot of time.

However, nobody cheered up at the scene. Everyone rested their eyes on a peculiar “red spot”. The red spot was in an irregular shape, but it was perfectly embedded in the concrete like a piece of asymmetric artwork.

Rock knew this was definitely not a coincidence. Everything contaminated by the Erosion would disappear, including the Force of Nature.

It was this red spot that separated the Prism City into two parts.

“Forget about the headquarters,” Rock instructed. “Go down to the bottom level and make sure that the central hub is intact.”

The rescue team, after receiving the order, immediately went down. Fortunately, they did not encounter any Fallen Evils on their way. Rock did not see a lot of traces of fight either. The building was dead quiet. Everything was in a perfect order, as though the building was simply abandoned.

When the rescue team reached the central hub, everyone in the temporary headquarters gasped.

Rock clenched his teeth.

Another Defender named Furious Flames was slashed in half, its upper body clinging to the steel gate around 10 centimeters thick, all his clothes reduced to ashes. In the center of the steel gate was a huge, irregularly shaped hole, which seemed to be drilled out under high heat.

Apparently, Furious Flames had attempted to stop the invaders from entering the central hub but had failed.

This was definitely not the work of Fallen Evils.

It took the rescue team a while to open the gate. All the cores were gone.

There was a dread silence in the headquarters. Everyone dazed at the screen, horror-struck.

Rock clenched his fist even tighter. He knew that the staff at the bottom would not take the fallen cores for no reason. He ordered solemnly, “Get the surveillance footage. I want to see what kind of monster it was!”

His sonorous voice jerked the audience out of the trance. Since they had immediately switched over to the contingency power, the surveillance system still worked well. Despite a few broken cameras, most of the video footages was still there. The technical support soon inserted the spare hardware, and the video was transmitted to the big screen. All the executives in the headquarters was taken aback by what they saw.

The moment the Erosion had expanded, several blood clots had escaped from the red hollow and hit the floor. These clumps of blood wriggled and gradually transformed into human-shaped monsters. One of them had the ability to melt everything down. It instantly penetrated the floor and reached the bottom level. Another monster was even more terrifying. It immediately impaled a few martialists and turned them into puppets, making them look like inferior Fallen Evils controlled by the Force of Nature.

Within half an hour, the bottom level was breached. People who were alive all merged with the fallen cores in a daze and became their enemies’ puppets. After that, the monsters “devoured” the rest of the fallen cores and created a passage in the central hub before they vanished from the camera.

It was Rock’s first time witnessing such an incredible power. The fact that the Erosion generated new Fallen Evils horrified him.

He somehow thought of the joint mission last time, where the survivors had told him about the monster coming from the “man-made Erosion”.

It appeared that the Erosion, which they used to believe could engulf everything, had changed.

Also, he sensed the blatant animosity from the Erosion from the way those monsters attacked the central hub and the people.

But Rock believed that as long as all the martialists worked together, they would eventually find a solution to eliminate these enemies, no matter how powerful they appeared to be. The most important task now was to raise the morale and not let the fear conquer them.

“Everyone, just as you’ve seen, this isn’t an accident. The Erosion is invading this city!” Rock announced as he straightened up. “It sounds quite strange but that’s the truth. Let me make it clear. This is a war! They aim to take this world! I’ll contact all the other Martialist Associations immediately, and we should unite together and exterminate the enemies!”

At these words, Rock paused for a second and then said, “Like my student Lan said, the Battle of Divine Will has begun.”

Chapter 1229: The Red Mist

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

At around 4:00 in the morning, Garcia finally fell asleep.

She had talked more than what all she had said to Roland in the past few months altogether since their first encounter. It was more like a monologue than a constructive conversation. Most of her rambling was about how she had met her master after she had cut ties with her family.

The only thing Roland could do was to refill her glass and be a good listener.

Roland also discovered that Garcia’s dedication to protecting this world was mostly a product of Lan’s education. Although Lan had been very strict with her, Garcia had always looked up to her and viewed Lan as her goal and role model.

From what Roland saw, Lan must have liked the Dream World.

But he was not sure whether her method would work.

There were only two bedrooms in Room 0825, one of which was Zero’s. Roland pondered for a while and decided to put Garcia in the master bedroom and spent the night in the living room himself. He did not think it a good idea to rummage Garcia’s pocket for the key to her own apartment while she was asleep, for he had the slightest intention of creating any unncessary misunderstanding.

Roland was certain that based on his past experience, this was the best way to handle this kind of situation.

In the meantime, he also realized that he had to return to the real world now.

Roland looked through the window after he settled Garcia down and gazed upon the city night. He could spie glitters of lights dazzle in the distance. The flickers were even brighter than stars in the sky. It seemed to be a very peaceful, sweet night, but Roland knew that this world, like the other one, was full of danger. The “Bloody Moon” that represented the Erosion had revealed its horrendous nature. The only difference was that the one in the real world hung in the sky while the one here lurked underground.

Roland shut the curtains and departed from the Dream World.

He dazed for a while before opening his eyes. However, instead of the ceiling, he gazed into two sparkling eyes.

The two stared at each other for a while until Roland heard someone scream above him. Then the person peering down at him immediately disappeared, as though everything was just his imagination

“Ahem, well, I was just checking whether you had waken up or not, as you’ve been sleeping for quite a while, and I was a bit worried,” Nightingale said as she revealed herself from the desk. “Plus, why did you suddenly open your eyes. You scared me!”

Roland was speechless. How could he give her a headsup telling her that he was about to wake up?

“Anyway, you’re awake now, so I’m going to bed,” Nightingale said as she yawned dramatically. “By the way, Anna came to see you at 10:00 today, but she left when she saw you were still asleep. She asked me to tell you not to force yourself.”

“Hang on, what’s the time now?”

“Just a little over 12:00,” Nightingale replied as she walked toward the door. “Well, good night.”

As soon as Nightingale withdrew, Roland felt sleep creep over him. He had been roaming the two worlds for the last two days, and now he really needed a rest.

Roland stretched himself and was about to go to bed when he suddenly caught a glimpse of something unusual.

He slowly raised his head and almost shrieked at what he saw!

Two pale faces hung down from the window. As they were tightly pressed onto the glass, the faces were a little distorted. Roland saw four large eyes gazing into his. He jumped with a start!

Then he noticed that the two faces looked quite familiar to him.

Hang on, why did they look so familiar?

Roland’s heart did a kind of drum drolling in his chest. He squinted at them for a while and suddenly realized that they were Lightning and Maggie!

Why did they come here at this hour?

It was midnight.

Realizing they were exposed, the two girls drifted down from the roof.

“When did you get here?” Roland asked after Lightning and Maggie got in. He put up a straight face and said, “Why didn’t you notify me first?”

It wasn’t until then that Roland noticed that both of them were unkempt and muddy as if they had not taken a shower for half a year. They had indeed come back from a long journey.

“Your Majesty, we arrived here around an hour ago, coo,” Maggie replied, but Lightning soon stopped her.

“No, we just got here, and we didn’t see anything.” With these words, she glared at Maggie and added, “Did we?”

Maggie nodded fervently and said, “Coo… yes, I got it wrong.”

Roland twitched his lips, amused by their poor acting. Even Nana would not believe their words. He did not actually mind them watching him sleep, so he asked, “Did you travel at night? Why not use the Animal Messenger? Did —”

He suddenly had a bad feeling.

“Yes, Your Majesty,” Lightning said solemnly. “About half a month ago, we found traces of demons at the ridge of the continent!”

Roland was now completely awake. He pursued, “Then? Did you see any outposts there?”

“Not for now,” Lightning denied as she shook her head, produced a rumpled map from her pocket, and laid it open on the desk. “We couldn’t go really far in there, so we met up with the Taquila witches at the Snow Ridge. It took them a while to set up the magic core, and we were finally able to confirm something.” Lightning then pointed at the rapture marked in the center of the map and said, “There are God’s Stone mines there, and they’re almost as big as the one in the Holy City of Taquila!”

It was pretty clear what the demons were up to.

Roland knitted his brows. Edith was right. The demons did have a plan B. Even if Taquila fell, they could still invade the Four Kingdoms from another location. Although the Impassable Mountain Range was treacherous, it would be better to invade from there than waiting for another 400 years.

Fortunately, human beings discovered the demons’ intention in advance. According to Agatha’s intelligence, the demons would need some time to grow the Obelisk. They would only be able to produce a small amount of Red Mist before the Obelisk grew up.

“We also obtained another piece of news when we left the Snow Ridge,” Lightning resumed hesitantly. “At that time, Maggie and I had already passed the Kingdom of Everwinter, so we couldn’t hear it very clearly over the Sigil of Listening.”

“What did you hear?”

Maggie clapped his hands over her ears as if holding a telephone receiver.

“The liaison witch told us that they found Red Mist in the north of the mountain range, coo!”

Chapter 1230: An Emergency Meeting

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Barov was waken up by his servant.

During the wartime, the staff of the Administrative Office stood vigil in turns so that they could notify Barov immediately in case anything out of ordinary happened.

Edith no longer worked in the Administrative Office, but she still had certain influences on Roland. Barov always tended to seek counsels of the General Staff before making a plan. The presence of such a genius rival constantly reminded Barov to work hard.

Nevertheless, this was not the only reason Barov was so dedicated to his work.

In fact, he enjoyed being busy, as being busy represented power. It meant that Neverwinter needed him. Also, His Majesty would trust him even more if he succeeded in his undertaking.

Barov slid off the bed and pulled on his clothes. “Speak up. What’s the matter now?”

“Sir, this is an order from the king. He calls a meeting at the boardroom in the castle. All the ministers should be there at once.”

“Right now?” Barov asked in surprise as he looked out of the window. Without a doubt, it was in the dead of night.

“Yes. The telephone operator didn’s say much. Do you want to send someone to the castle first to make sure…”

“No, that’s fine,” Barov said quickly. The call was from the Administrative office, so it was not likely miscommunication. Since he was the only person who had installed a telephone at home, he must inform the other ministers verbally. “Ask the servants to notify the other ministers. Remember that everyone needs to be informed. If you ever miss one, it’s on you!”

Barov would have hesitated for a while had the order been issued by the old Prince Roland. However, now, Prince Roland had become a competent king. If he decided to call a meeting at this deadly hour, it must be about something of extreme urgency.

“Yes… yes, sir,” the servant said in the earnest. “Are you going to the castle alone?”

“No, I’m going with the Pearl of the Northern Region,” Barov returned. “I’ll notify Edith Kant myself.”

…

“Your Majesty, almost everyone is here,” Nightingale said as she put on a coat for Roland. “Do you need a cup of tea?”

“Yes, please,” Roland said while nodding. “Sorry to wake you up…”

“That’s nothing,” Nightingale said while smiling. “I’m not tired at all. I was just pretending.”

“Pretending?”

“No, no,” she denied quickly, a little flustered. “I mean I did yawn, but it was because my eyes were dry. I’m not tired at all. By the way, is Anna coming?”

“Let her rest,” Roland said while shaking his head. “She doesn’t need to worry about such things. Plus, she’s been working so hard lately.”

To further improve the Cube-powered motor, Anna had been working in the laboratory at the North Slope day and night. At the same time, she also had to work on the biplanes.

“You’re working hard as well,” Nightingale said as she handed the tea to Roland. “You didn’t sleep at all in the Dream World, did you?”

“Don’t worry. I’m used to staying up late…” Roland said smilingly. It was common to sleep at irregular hours in his previous world. This was actually not the worst. He simply needed to take a rest later to make up the hours he had lost. “I won’t be able to sleep well if I don’t finish my work.”

Roland thus drained the cup and sighed, “Let’s go.”

…

The boardroom lapsed into a dread silence after Lightning told them what she had discovered during her journey. Everybody was completely awake and wearing an extremely grave expression.

Agatha looked toward Roland apprehensively and said, “Your Majesty, we…”

“This isn’t your fault,” Roland comforted. “The rapid increase in the number of Senior Demons and Spider Demons has already indicated that our enemy is now very different from the one 400 years ago. Apparently, they also progressed.”

There was no point in blaming the Taquila witches for providing inaccurate intelligence, as the event was unforeseen. Indeed, the soldiers in Neverwinter and the Taquila witches had reached a mutual understanding on the strength of the demons in the third Battle of Divine Will.

“Although the Exploration Group is not 100% sure about the ‘presence of the Red Mist’, the Red Mist did reach the crest of the Impassable Mountain Range. I believe that we’ll hear from the front within a week. Now, the problem is that what we should do in the event that the demons do have the ability to activate the Obelisk in a short period of time. Before we discuss this matter, I want to make sure how much Red Mist an activated Obelisk could produce.”

Agatha said hesitantly, “After the Union discovered the special demon at the bottom of the mine, we speculated that the Obelisk is probably a type of giant Magic Stone. If the small Magic Stone embedded in the demons is transformed from a Chaos Beast, then the Obelisk would be from raw ores. The Obelisk does have unique properties, but its size also depends on the mine where it’s growing from. However…”

Roland knew why Agatha was hesitating, but he urged, “That’s OK. Speak up. It’s better than nothing. Plus, everything is subject to change during a war. If our prediction is a little different from the reality, then we can make adjustments accordingly.”

“Alright…” the Ice Witch said while nodding in great relief. “Based on the Union’s experience and Lightning’s information about the location of the mine, the Red Mist produced by an Obelisk transformed from a God’s Stone mine the same size of Taquila could probably reach here…”

She then conjured an icicle and pointed it at the map.

“This is… the Archduke Island?” Edith asked thoughtfully.

“That’s right. If we move the great rapture to the Taquila area, then the borderline would be around the Impassable Mountain Range area,” Agatha explained. “Of course, the Red Mist won’t reach there all of a sudden. It needs time to permeate the surrounding area, and the whole process may take a few days. The farther it goes, the slower it’ll travel. Therefore, it’ll be another few months before the Red Mist covered the area within a radius of 100 kilometers.”

It appeared that they had done a good thing to seize Taquila in advance. Had they failed or been a little slower, say, they had just completed the railway construction now, the Red Mist would have not only invaded the Four Kingdoms from the Impassable Mountain Range but it would have also hindered the operation of the First Army. The Red Mist was fatal to the witches. Even though the army had advanced weapons, they would not be able to carry out military operations effectively while being interfered with by the Red Mist.

“With that being the case, we must hurry up,” Roland said as he looked toward Edith. “Does the General Staff have any plan?”

“Of course we do,” Edith said confidently. She was the first person to see through the demons’ intention. “Although the demons are faster than we thought, from the perspective of military strategy, erecting the Obelisk at the ridge of the continent was actually their last resort. The ridge of the continent is a good hiding place, but the demons could not launch an attack effectively from there. This affords us time to remedy the situation. The General Staff believes that if the demons do appear in the Kingdom of Everwinter, our defensive line will definitely not in Graycastle but here.”

She tapped the map.

It was the Cage Mountain in the Kingdom of Dawn.

Chapter 1231: Hope

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“The reason is fairly simple,” Edith resumed before anyone could raise a question. “The Cage Mountain is not only a branch of the Impassable Mountain Range in the horizontal direction but also the highest point of the Kingdom of Dawn. The artillery of the First Army could have a broader view if they fire from there. Also, the demons will have restricted mobility, considering that there are fewer flying Devilbeasts than inferior Mad Demons.”

“Secondly, the Red Mist tends to move toward the lowlands, and it becomes thinner as it stretches farther. Therefore, the witches shall build the defensive line at the highpoint of the land. I’ve heard that the front has already done so ahead of time.”

“The last is His Majesty’s Radiation Project.” She surveyed the room at these words and continued, “We know that this project relies on the ores at the Cage Mountain. Before we find an alternative resource, we can’t abandon the Cage Mountain.”

Nobody questioned Edith’s decision.

Nobody saw the final product of the Radiation Project, and they could not possibly imagine how much energy those tiny little spheres could produce, but all of them viewed the project as one of the most important missions, simply because Roland said so. Roland swelled up with pride at this thought.

This was probably the biggest achievement an engineering student could ever attain.

“But we can’t desert the Kingdom of Everwinter or the Kingdom of Wolfheart completely either,” Roland said as he cast a glance at Edith. “We need people to win the war.”

“Yes. Therefore, while the Red Mist is spreading, the First Army should focus on bringing in immigrants and stopping the demons from advancing. I don’t think the demons will set up outposts after the Red Mist spreads out. They’ll build them right now, which was exactly what they did 400 years ago.”

Edith paused for a second and said, “To be honest, the sudden appearance of the Bloody Moon helped the First Army. When people in the Kingdom of Everwinter and the Kingdom of Wolfheart see what kind of enemy they’re dealing with, they’ll automatically side with us. By that time, they’ll beg Graycastle for help even if Iron Axe wants to shut them out.”

At these words, Edith’s lips curled up into a faint, inscrutable smile.

In that case, a lot of people would die.

Roland heaved a sigh.

Roland understood why Edith gloated over the misfortune of the refugees. He remembered a piece of news in his previous world saying that some residents opposed to build a cell tower and therefore lost cellphone reception. However, in a war that would determine the fate of the human race, Roland could not stand by watching those people suffer, even though it was because of their own stupidity.

“We harvested tons of Golden Twos this year,” Roland said as he turned to Barov. “Draft a proposal and send some food to the Kingdom of Dawn. Make sure those refugees who left their native towns are fed.”

“Your Majesty, if my understanding is correct, once we confirm the Red Mist would spread out, the First Army will immediately set off for the Cage Mountain. This will create a lot of pressure on the logistics,” Barov replied hesitantly. “I can’t guarantee we can provide food to the refugees while at the same time supplying our army. We won’t have enough ships even if we borrow all the ships from the Chambers of Commerce at the Fjords.”

This was a real problem. Even the largest sailboat in the Fjords would not meet the needs of the war. All the fleets were now filled with immigrants.

“Unless… we build a railway leading directly to the neighbor…” Barov said with great difficulties. He knew such a large project would cost tons of money. His heart ached every time money went out from the treasury.

“We probably don’t have much time,” Roland said while shaking his head. “The railway construction on the Fertile Plain has cost too many resources. If we build another railway, we won’t be able to support the other projects.”

The railway, which stretched away from the Misty Forest all the way to the ruins of Taquila, cost a great amount of steel. Its construction took a year and a half, not to mention that Leaf had amended the first half of the railway and that the second half was built on a flat plain. The road condition between Neverwinter and the Cage Mountain was more complicated than the Fertile Plains, so it would be hard to say how long it would take to build this new railway.

“I totally agree with you, Your Majesty…” Barov rejoined, apparently much relieved.

“Let’s make a plan based on the current situation. Don’t try to save money. Use the money well,” Roland said. “As for the logistics, I’ll see what I can do.”

“Yes, Your Majesty.”

Roland then looked toward Edith and said, “The General Staff should also draft a proposal based on the presumption that the farthest the Red Mist could go is the Cage Mountain. Then we’ll discuss further in detail.”

Smart as the Pearl of the Northern Region was, she had no problem in making a plan. Even if Roland did not remind her, she would understand the urgency of the matter.

“Leave it to me,” Edith said while placing her hand on her chest.

Roland rose to his feet and surveyed the boardroom. “I told you before that the third Battle of Divine Will will determine the fate of the mankind. Now, it’s coming.” The victory of the Taquila war has proved to us that we could win, despite the miserable defeat 400 years ago. I hope we all do our best and devote ourselves to this war. I’m sure today will be remembered!” Roland proclaimed. “Listen, no matter who our enemy is, I only have one request, that is, we must win the battle!”

“As you wish, Your Majesty!” everyone shouted together.

It was going to be a busy night.

After everyone filed out of the boardroom, Roland held Tilly back.

“I want to have a private word with you.”

…

After Roland returned to his office, he dismissed Nightingale and shut the door.

Tilly raised her brows and asked, “Something that you don’t even want Nightingale to hear? It seems you’re not planning to inquire about the training of the Aerial Knights.”

Roland did not answer but poured a glass of minty Chaos Drink for both of them. It did not taste particularly good, but it was pretty calming.

Seeing Roland remain silent, Tilly did not pursue but simply sipped the drink, waiting for him to break the silence.

Roland had a complex feeling toward his “sister”. Tilly was not his real sister. Compared to the Princess Tilly he used to know, the current Tilly Wimbledon had become more like a leader. However, he preferred the little girl who used to curl herself up beside Anna in winter, with her feet sticking out from underneath the blanket, and think about what kind of tough questions she could ask the other witches.

Although Roland knew that people would change, Tilly’s change was too drastic. Within a few days after Ashes’ death, she had grown up. He could see the virulent rancor against the demons in Tilly’s eyes. She seldom revealed such hatred, but Roland was very disturbed by her “only request” of seeking revenge from the demons.

She had made up her mind.

The world had suddenly become meaningless to her.

Roland learned from Lan that Ashes could be brought back to life. He should have verified the information before telling Tilly so that he would not give her a false hope. However, Roland realized that as Ashes’ death had sunk Tilly into the lowest dejection, Tilly might not survive the Battle of Divine Will in the end.

If he told her about the prospective good news now, she might probably elevate herself from such despondency.

Yet there was a risk he had to take. If Ashes did not come back to life in the end, Tilly would be devastated.

That was why Roland did not say anything for quite a while.

But he had to speak.

Roland knew he had made the decision when he had stopped Tilly.

He would rather put his faith in a faint ray of hope in the future than regret later.

“Brother?” Tilly reminded him, a little bewildered. She averted her eyes slightly to avoid Roland’s burning gaze.

Roland took a deep breath and said slowly, “What I’m going to say next may be incredible, but I still want to tell you that — ”

“Ashes may be still alive.”

Chapter 1232: Brother

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Tilly quavered. She slowly turned around, and there was a multitude of feelings in her eyes. As if confirming what she had just heard, Tilly asked, “What… did you say?”

“I said that Ashes might be still alive,” Roland repeated slowly. He knew he could not retract now.

“No… brother,” Tilly mumbled as she managed a smile. “I know you want to comfort me, but you can’t…”

“But it’s not what you think,” Roland cut across her. “To be honest, I was as incredulous as you when I heard the news, and I know it’s unfair to tell you before I confirm that it’s true. However, I don’t want to regret it later.”

Tilly fell silent.

She stared at Roland out of his countenance as if processing the information. She suddenly realized that what Roland had said was probably something unusual.

Tilly was one of the smartest and most open-minded witches among all.

After about seven minutes, she asked tentatively, “Who told you that?”

“Lan.”

“I’ve never heard of her…” Tilly muttered as she lapsed into thought. “Does it have something to do with the Dream World?”

Roland was not surprised that Tilly had quickly made the connection. He answered calmly, “Slow down. I’ll tell you everything.”

…

By the time Roland finished, the first hint of dawn was visible in the east. The first ray of sun broke over the horizon behind the mountains and gilded the roofs of the buildings in the distance.

Tilly was still lost in thought. She muttered to Roland as much as to herself, “That means… as long as you control the Realm of Mind, you’ll be able to bring Ashes back?”

“Technically, yes,” Roland replied while nodding. “According to Lan, after a witch becomes a Transcendent, she’ll leave a mark in the Realm of Mind. This is consistent with Kabradhabi’s statement.”

During the interrogation, Kabradhabi had told Zooey that their souls would return to the Origin of Magic. Once their kind dominated the world, he would come back. Although it was quite different from what Lan had told Roland, there was one thing in common.

That was, the Realm of Mind accepted souls.

“In addition, in the ancient book of the underground civilization, the author also wrote that the journey to the Divine Will is the process of a magic power upgrade. The winner will eventually rival God. If we view the Realm of Mind as the pinnacle of magic power, then Lan’s words, in a way, fits the description.” Roland paused for a second before he continued, “Nevertheless, considering that this information may be all from God, we can’t completely trust it. The best way is to verify its validity myself.”

“Brother…”

“Don’t worry. I’ll penetrate the Realm of Mind as soon as I can and try my best to retrieve Ashes, if she’s really there. Therefore, I want you to protect yourself before I find her, as I don’t want to infuriate a Transcendent who has exceeded her limit and is beyond the restriction of God’s Stones of Retaliation…” Roland said in a half-joking manner. Then he suddenly found that Tilly did not look right.

She was trembling, her head hanging, and she was mumbling under her breath as well. Roland held his breath and listened.

“That’s great… That’s great…”

Roland suddenly did not know what to say.

Tears started to trickle down Tilly’s cheeks and splattered against the back of her hand.

Looking at the quivering princess, Roland sighed internally as he slowly stretched out his hand and patted her head.

The next moment, Tilly threw herself onto him and held him tight. The trembling gradually perished into sobs, and Roland felt as though he had traveled back in time to that night again. However, Roland sensed that something had changed.

Unlike last time where Tilly had cried for hours, this time, she dried her eyes within 10 minutes. When she looked up, she forced Roland to turn away.

“Don’t… don’t look at me.”

Then he heard Tilly sniffle and clean up her face behind him.

It was a while before Roland was allowed to turn around.

“Sorry… I made you worried,” Tilly said in a low voice.

“I’m pleased that you’ve realized it,” Roland said while folding his arms. “You should also reconsider your request last time — ”

“Are you referring to the plane used to kill the demons?” Tilly said while blinking. “No, my request stands, brother.”

“Oi…”

“You need my help to reach the Fathomless Abyss. Now, it’s very likely that the demons have already erected a full-grown Obelisk. With that being the case, it’s going to be even harder for us to restrict the Devilbeasts. If we can’t dominate the sky, the First Army might not be able to crush the enemy so easily,” Tilly said as she stuck out one finger to stop Roland. “You’re right. I didn’t care about whether I’ll survive when I made that request. I just wanted to kill as many demons as possible. But now, I’ve changed my mind.”

“And you know what a difference it could make with someone assisting you. Not a single Aerial Knight knows how to fight demons. I’m the only person who can teach and train them,” Tilly went on while patting the chest. “I promise you that I’ll look after myself and wait for you to enter the Realm of Mind.”

Roland found it hard to decline her request. The sparkles in Tilly’s eyes came back, her demeaner as poised as ever, and she was radiant from within.

“Alright then… but you must keep your promise.”

“Of course.” Tilly resumed after a brief pause, “Also… thank you for telling me that.”

“I’m not sure whether this method would work —”

“I’m more than content. At least, we now have a mutual goal,” Tilly said as she again pressed herself to Roland’s chest. “I’m glad you’re my brother…”

…

After Tilly took her leave, Nightingale returned to the office and asked, “What did you say to Princess Tilly? I saw her just come out, and she looks like a different person…”

“The connection between the Dream World and the reality. If you want to know, I can tell you as well, but not now,” Roland said as he fumbled with the drawings. “I just received a message from Honey, saying that a fleet will be arriving at the port of the inner river in two days. They should bring the immigrants from the Kingdom of Wolfheart. Before that, I should finish the drawing for the new project.”

Nightingale shrugged and said, “Never mind me. Haven’t I told you? I won’t insist if you don’t want to say.” She walked to the desk and studied the drawing for quite a while before she said, “It looks like… the vehicle Anna drove the other day in the yard.”

“It’s the same thing, only a lot larger,” Roland said smilingly. “Didn’t Barov talk about the logistics in the meeting? This is the solution.”

Apart from expensive trains, there was also a cheap alternative, a wheeled truck. There were various types of wheeled trucks. Although they were not as efficient as trains, they were more flexible and also easier to operate than a tractor. They could run on a flat, hard-surfaced road easily.

There were many inner rivers in Graycastle and the Kingdom of Dawn, but none of these rivers were connected. Therefore, a fleet of wheeled trucks could facilitate the transportation between the two countries.

Chapter 1233: Being Trapped

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“I see,” Nightingale spoke after a moment of contemplation. “Compared to building a brand new railway, it’s much easier to build a road to connect the rivers. Railway construction needs Anna and skillful workers, but everybody can build a regular road. Even the refugees can do it. In this way, we can save a lot of time!”

“Exactly. This is another strength,” Roland said in approval. “As long as we plan it well, we’ll alleviate the stress of the logistics department in one or two months. This is very important for us considering we have such a tight timeline. It appears that you do, sometimes, grasp the nature of the problem.”

“Haha, of course… hang on,” Nightingale said and her smiles immediately faded out. “What do you mean by ‘sometimes’? I can think, and I can help you with your work and cope with my exam…”

Although she looked pretty frustrated, her voice trailed off.

Roland giggled involuntarily.

Nightingale had to first make sure that she did not fall asleep before she set to study.

Roland shoveled his eyes back to the map on the desk. If he wanted to connect the rivers in Graycastle and the Kingdom of Dawn, the fastest way was to build a road in the Eastern Region near the Redwater River that ran all the way to the City of Evernight. The road should then wind toward the north, reach the Windswept Ridge, and finally connect the Sparkling River in the neighboring country.

The Sparking River originated from the Hermes Plateau and diverged at the capital city into three branches. Two wider ones stretched away between the south and north of the Kingdom of Dawn and flew to the ocean. To further facilitate water transportation, the Moya Family had dug out a canal running from the east to the west over the past 100 years, which not only boomed the business activities along the river but also provided a shortcut for Roland’s road construction plan.

With that being the case, Roland only needed to build two roads, one from the Sparkling River to the Northside River and the other leading to the Cage Mountain. In this way, there would be a passage connecting the two countries. Compared to a costly railway, the two roads were no longer than 200 kilometers put together, and all he needed to do was to set up three ports for freights.

Since loaded trucks were heavy and could easily damage the road particularly on rainy days, Roland decided to use mortar and cement to harden the road surface instead of gravels to avoid subsequent maintenance. The road, therefore, would be of the same quality as those in Neverwinter.

Cement was now widely used in Neverwinter, but it was time-consuming to ship it to the Kingdom of Dawn, so Roland decided to produce cement locally.

After finishing the drawing, Roland wrote a letter to the king of the neighboring country, Andrea’s father, Horford Quinn.

He was going to dispatch some technitians to the City of Glow and taught the three families in the king’s city how to manufacture cement and assemble paddle steamers. Then they would be able to build a plant and mend the road for Neverwinter.

Roland believed that the nobles would see the potential value of cement.

With these two technologies, the Kingdom of Dawn could solve the transportation problem by themselves.

Nevertheless, Roland planned to provide completed steam engines because none of the cities except Neverwinter in this era were industrialized. It would thus be meaningless to send over raw materials.

Roland believed that the Kingdom of Dawn would take action immediately. If the Red Mist had already appeared at the crest of the Impassable Mountain Range, Horford would receive the news soon. By that time, he would know what he should do.

…

Two days later, Roland saw the first batch of immigrants from the roof of the Miracle Building.

Smoke coiled up into the air from the endless fleet and dropped a thick veil at the bank. People trodded on the trestle and off on the dock under the guidance of the police. A colorful sea of heads heaved up and down at the bank of the Redwater River.

“50,000 people… That’s the population of a whole city, Your Majesty,” Barov commented in excitement, although also a little worried. “I’ve never expected to see hundreds of thousands of immigrants from the Kingdom of Everwinter and Kingdom of Wolfheart coming to Graycastle. If things go well, we’ll soon reach our target of an increase of 200,000 people each year. Now, I should worry about your treasury.”

“As well as public safety and urban management,” the Chief Knight, Carter, rejoined a little apprehensively. “Those immigrants may not acknowledge your authority. Out of safety concern, I suggest settling them down in a certain area so it would be easier to manage them.”

“Then they’ll never become true Graycastle people,” Roland said while shaking his head. “If the police needs help, ask Barov. Punish the wrong-doers and reward those who make contributions. Send chronic offenders to the mine and subject them to heavy labor. I need workers not imprisoned slaves.”

Without a doubt, the king’s city would be more chaotic with such a huge influx of immigrants. This was an inevitable side effect of his immigration policy. Roland would not have carried out such a hasty plan had he had enough time. Now, the war was around the corner, so he had to implement the policy despite the potential problems it would bring.

The benefits of an population increase overpowered its downside.

For example, he could send 10,000 people out of the 50,000 new immigrants to the plants to increase the production of firearms. Then, the soldiers at the front would have more weapons and ammunition, as well as other new equipment.

Now he had both manpower and technologies and could officially start the project for the Cube-powered steam engines.

…

“Where am I?”

Valkries woke up again and found herself in a snow white room. The ceiling and the wall blinded her. There was a queer instrument ticking beside her. A transparent bag was hung above her, and the liquid in it dripped down the tube and slowly into her vein.

There was so much information unfamiliar to her swarming into her head that for a moment, she could not give a proper response. She had never seen anything like this before. Everything was so different from what she were used to.

For example, the white shirt she was currently wearing had pretty tight stitches, which was complete different from the clothes she usually wore.

Valkries closed her eyes and concentrated. No matter how strange the surrounding was, the only thing she could rely on was her power.

Valkries’ heart suddenly sank to the bottom.

She noticed that she was not in her own body.

Although this body looked exactly the same, the magic stone was gone. She would have died had the magic stone really disappeared.

However, surprisingly, she felt fine.

She could still sense the magic power slowly move within her body in an unfamiliar way.

The murmur of the Realm of Mind was also gone.

No matter how hard Valkries tried to concentrate, there was no response. She even condescended to call upon the Sky Lord, but she heard nothing back from the latter.

This meant that she was trapped.

Chapter 1234: A Strange World

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Yes, she was trapped.

Valkries now remembered that she had been delving into the depth of the Realm of Mind and tracking down a faint fluctuation. When she had crossed the borderline that separated the upper and lower level, her step had become heavier and heavier. The resistance from the Realm of Mind increased, and she felt something was dragging her down.

It was her first time to come thus far, so she must be careful. If she got lost, she might be trapped here forever. Valkries would have terminated this expedition and taken a break had she not sensed that the fluctuation she was looking for was getting closer.

The entrance should be just around here.

So she decided to dive deeper.

Hackzord seemed not to be very impressed with her bathing in the Red Mist Pond all day, especially when human beings had not realized that they had successfully transplanted the Birth Tower.

On the other hand, Valkries also wanted to know whether the human race had upgraded through the legacy shard.

She had never anticipated, however, that the Realm of Mind suddenly quaked while she was trying to find the source of the fluctuation.

She felt as if the muddy ground underneath suddenly cracked, sank, and formed a waterfall. She was immediately flushed down before she could realize it. When she woke up again, she found herself in this strange place.

Beyond a doubt, this place should be a part of the Realm of Mind, but Valkries was not sure whether it had anything to do with the male human she was searching for.

Through the window, Valkries could see a big city outside. Sierried highrises stretched away and disappeared at the end of the horizon, each as tall as the Birth Tower. Some were even taller than the king’s Presiding Holy See.

If this was that male human’s territory, Valkries did not understand why he had not noticed the presence of an intruder. The creator should have been omnipotent. Since Valkries was the mortal enemy of the human race, the creator should have taken action by now. If a witch, by accident, trespassed the Presiding Holy See, death would probably be the kindest punishment inflicted upon her.

The problem was that if this place had nothing to do with that male, then where was it?

When Valkries had sensed the quaver, she had felt the shockwave come from above. She was certain that she was on the right track, unless she had been searching in the wrong direction all along.

Valkries pondered for a while but could not find a satisfying explanation, so she put aside these questions. The most important task for her now was to adapt to this new body and find an opportunity to get out of this strange world.

Valkries was positive about one thing that this new body was much weaker than her own. The wound on her legs had still not healed up yet, which indicated that she currently had little self-repairing ability. Her Magic Barrier stopped working. Valkries had never been so weak for a long time. She felt as if she had traveled back to the time prior to her upgrade when everybody could cause substantial harm to her.

Fortunately, she could still summon magic power, which was an ability quite similar to Extraordinaries’.

While Valkries was checking her body, there was a pattering of footsteps outside.

The door was then pushed open, and two men entered smilingly.

Valkries almosted wanted to throw herself onto them and rip them apart, but she suppressed the urge.

This was not the real world!

She reminded herself. It appeared that these people had saved her when she had lost consciousness.

Perhaps, these people never knew such things as “demons”. If she acted recklessly, she would expose herself.

“You look pretty well, Miss Valkries,” the female said as she lifted one corner of the blanket and examined her plastored legs. “Amazing. No wonder the pillar didn’t wound your bones. You’re a martialist! If I were you, my legs would have been smashed to pieces.”

“Is this what a doctor should say to her patient?” the male said as he glared at the female and then looked toward Valkries. “I’m the doctor in charge here. You can call me Dr. Gao. According to the X-ray, you’ll soon recover. Take a good rest, and I’m sure the injury won’t affect your future contests. If you don’t feel well, please don’t hesitate to tell me.”

Valkries shook her head.

She hardly understood anything Dr. Gao had said, so she resolved to remain silent.

Valkries also noticed that these human beings appeared to be pretty friendly to her. She was puzzled as to why these people did not view her as a person of another race. Even if they did not harbor hostility against her, how could they speak to her in such an amicable manner when there was such a drastic difference between the two races?

Valkries even noticed that the female was particularly interested in her. Her eyes were glued on her.

“I’m glad you’re well,” the male named Dr. Gao said as he leafed through the brochure in his hand. “The Association will come to visit the hospital this afternoon, and they’ll also hold a meeting in the evening. I’ve already declined the request to attend the meeting for you. Those people are so insensible! They wanted you to sit the meeting through in your wheelchair! That’s ridiculous! But I can’t stop them from visiting you. This hospital is funded by the Martialist Association, so it’s impossible for me to stop them. You just need to lie in bed.”

“… Thank you,” Valkries said in a way an ordinary man would normally speak in this situation.

“You’re welcome,” the male said with a smile. “By the way, you must be bored. The Association didn’t send your cell phone here. Do you want to watch TV?”

Cell phone? TV? What were they?

Nonplussed, Valkries did not answer.

The doctor took her silence as a yes, so he picked up a square box on the nightstand, pointed it at a blackboard on the wall, and fiddled it.

Soon, light escaped from the blackboard!

“Now, you take a good rest,” Dr. Gao said as he waved his hand and withdrew from the room with the female.

Valkries goggled at the screen and almost lost herself.

How did they… do this?

The image on the blackboard changed. Everything was so lifelike. Valkries would not have been so surprised had the blackboard been a magic artifact, but this object was non-magical. She could not sense any fluctuation of magic power from the blackboard.

It took Valkries a while to get used to it.

She also discovered that the content of the television had something to do with the little square box. The image would change if she pressed the button on it.

If her assumption was correct, these contents might be closely related to this world.

This was an effective way to get to know about this world.

While Valkries was flipping through channels, she captured one strange word, “the Martialist Association.”

Based on what the male had told her, she was also a member of the Association, or more precisely, they assumed that she was a member of the Association.

She saw a crowded square on the television. The picture was shot from above. Perhaps, someone videotaped the scene with some magic artifact like a Stone of Flight.

“This is the third day since the attack at the Prism City. Firefighters are still rescuing members and cleaning up the debris.”

“The Association has confirmed the death toll. The victims’ identities still remain unknown at this point.”

“During the whole rescue process, many martialists displayed courage and sense of responsibilities. They went down to the evacuation exits to look for those being trapped.

“The Chief Disciple of the Defender Rock, Ms. Lan, was killed in action.”

“When she entered Exit 4, she was attacked by the Fallen Evils. To protect her peers…”

Valkries did not hear a single word said by the reporter.

Her attention was caught by the image on the “blackboard”.

Valkries was shocked. “Why, why do I see those strange and familiar faces in the Realm of Mind?”

Wasn’t the Cloud School… already disbanded?

Chapter 1235: The Cloud School

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Valkries shook her head and forced herself to calm down. She was certain that the Cloud School was gone. After their kind occupied the northwest of the Land of Dawn, Valkries visited the mountain where the school used to be situated every 100 years and would stay at the ruins of the school building for a couple of days every time she went there.

Because she used to be one of the students in the school.

She had learned how to connect to the Realm of Mind and also about human beings on that mountain. Her teacher was the “Transformer”, Heathtalese, who was also an Upgraded.

Heathtalese was not exceptionally powerful. In fact, she was even weaker than a relatively strong Inferior Demon. Because of this, the clansmen treated her with utter contempt. However, Valkries knew that the upgrade ceremony had nothing to do with fighting capacity. Heathtalese had successfully merged with magic stones three times, and she was a genius Upgraded in every aspect.

As her title suggested, the Transformer had obtained the ability to transform after merging with her second magic stone. Hence, she rarely revealed what she truly looked like. Most of time she disguised herself as a human. Since she could speak the human language fluently, many people would think that she was human at first.

Lan on the television was the identity she had used most often.

Valkries stared at that familiar face, and her thoughts strayed back to 1,000 years ago. Although the woman’s countenance and clothes were slightly different, Valkries was sure it was the same face.

If the founders of the Cloud School were aliens among humans, then the “Transformer” was an alien among her clan. Heathtalese did not really care about the fighting capacity that her magic stones would afford her, but she had a devouring curiosity about everything unknown. The “Transformer” was also the first person that made the initial contact with the Cloud School.

At that time, rumors about the Battle of Divine Will had been spread throughout the whole clan, and they had viewed the mankind on the Land of Dawn as their potential enemies.

Valkries was very grateful to her first teacher who had taught her so many things. She did not disdain Heathtalese because the latter was not good at fighting. Valkries knew very well that the “Transformer” had had a more profound understanding of the Realm of Mind as well as the Origin of Magic than anyone else in the clan. She had written dozens of books, half of which provided guidance to the later generations and helped them go through the upgrade ceremony. She was what human beings called a “mentor” for most of the clansmen.

In fact, the “Transformer” was probably the first person who had made an attempt to merge with four magic stones.

Had she succeeded, she would have become the first “Senior Lord” of the clan. At that time, there had been very few Inferior Demons, let alone a Senior Lord.

Unfortunately, the “Transformer” had failed. She had been devoured by her own magic power, without leaving the slightest trace behind her.

Valkries remembered that day because she had been right beside the Transformer at that time. She had witnessed how the “Transformer” gradually had fallen apart and collapsed. That was also why Valkires felt that the “Lan” on the television was a little unfamiliar. She had never seen two people that looked so alike over the past 1,000 years.

Valkries had asked the Transformer why she wanted to present herself in this way, for she believed that the face she had created did not belong to any prominent historical figures.

Heathtalese’ answer, however, was incomprehensible.

She said this was the face of an apostle.

As for who the apostle was, the Transformer did not know either. When she dived into the Realm of Mind, she sometimes could feel an entirely different strand of mind. It was whispering, but she had never officially met it. Nevertheless, the Transformer later remembered what it looked like.

The Transformer also said that if she could stablize herself in the chaotic Realm of Mind, she would be able to connect to that whispering sound. Unfortunately, she was not powerful enough to do so.

Valkries did not understand what that meant at that time, for she had just upgraded and known nothing about the Realm of Mind. In other words, the Transformer was a pioneer in the exploration of the Realm of Mind. The king, as a matter of fact, had not marked out its own territory in the Realm of Mind until the night before the second Battle of Divine Will.

Valkries had also asked the king whether he had seen that apostle, but the king denied.

Therefore, there could be two possibilities.

One was that this world belonged to the apostle “Lan”. However, according to the news on the television, Lan was dead. That did not make sense, for the creator of a territory would never die or leave the Realm of Mind.

The other was that the Transformer had returned to the Realm of Mind before being devoured by her own magic power and had thereby created her own territory. This theory might explain why the presence of Lan did not raise any suspicions, but it failed to explain the strange surroundings.

Valkries had wanted to leave this weird place as soon as possible in the beginning, but now she changed her mind.

She was concerned about what the Transformer had said when the latter had failed her fourth upgrade. The Transformer had said that even if they won the Battle of Divine Will, they would not gain the Divine Domain. Valkries wanted to know what had made her mentor say this.

Perhaps, this was an opportunity for her to find out the reason.

…

Roland yawned as he drove his mini van on the 2nd ring highway.

Although he pressed hard on the gas and the engine also roared, he still fell behind from other vehicles.

“What’s wrong? You didn’t sleep well?” Garcia, who was now sitting in the passenger seat, asked. For some reason, Roland felt that Garcia had become much more polite to him since she had stayed over at his place that night.

“It’s my day off. I planned to sleep in. Thanks to the Association, I have to get up early again,” Roland complained, unable to help himself. He was very tired after the meeting regarding the immigration policy. As time in the Dream World traveled three times faster than that in the real world, he had decided to take a good rest in his dream. It would not only save him a lot of time but would also give the Taquila witches an opportunity to enjoy themselves.

Now, the witches could have fun on their own.

Also, apart from entertainment, the ancient witches also shouldered the responsibility of searching for the magic creatures that had appeared during the Erosion. Roland remembered that Lan had told him that the God was watching this world. To eliminate the threat and reach God’s territory, the most effective way was to kill the Fallen Evils and use their power to expand the Dream World.

However, the reality was always cruel. Garicia had called him at noon and informed him that he had to visit the survived Association members in the hospital. All the celebrated martialists and the executives would be there.

Roland had intended to decline, as he had thought it was simply Garcia’s own idea. He had not anticipated, however, that it was a request from the Association and that the Association had appointed him, a licensed hunter, instead of Garcia.

“The Association wants to re-establish confidence in the Prism City after this massive attack,” Garcia commented while raising her brows. “I believe what they really plan to do is to hold a conference in the evening.”

Roland fell silent. It was not enough to calm down the public by just visiting patients. What they needed to do now was to display their power and fight back. In consideration of that, the meeting in the evening must have something do with the magic creatures.

This provided Roland with a perfect opportunity to conduct his own search.

Chapter 1236: Striking Similarities

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

About 20 minutes later, Roland reached his destination.

He looked around but did not find any building that resembled a hospital. Instead, what he saw were several splendid, magnificent modern edifices.

“Right here,” Garcia said with a nod.

“Are you sure?” Roland asked a little suspiciously as he drove toward the entrance, and then he noticed a name plate that read, “Green Meadow Sanatorium”.

“Of course. Everybody was as surprised as you when they first came here.”

A few burly guards wearing sunglasses and suits soon approached them and surrounded the car. One of them knocked on the window and said, “Sorry, this is a private premise. You can’t park here.”

Roland twiched his lips. Oi, oi, why was he always treated as crap? He was not here to park the vehicle but to visit patients. What was the problem with driving a mini van?

When Roland was about to display his hunting license, Garcia rolled the window down and handed them a card. “It’s a new vehicle, so we haven’t registered it yet. Please register it.”

The guards was stunned for a moment before they took the card and cast a few suspicious glances at the car. They then returned to the monitoring room. When they came out again, they spoke to them in a completely different manner. “My apology, Miss Garcia. You registered another car before, so we…”

“Isn’t it normal to switch a car?” Garcia interrupted him politely.

“Yes… of course,” the guard agreed immediately and then looked at Roland. “May I know who this gentleman…”

“My chauffeur.”

There was an awkward silence. It was a few minutes later that the chief finally realized his mistake and said, “I see. I’ll add the new license plate for you.”

A moment later, the gate was open, and Roland released the clutch and shuffled his vehicle into the sanatorium.

He could see the incredulous look on those guards’ faces.

A martialist who asked her chauffeur to drive a battered mini van… Garcia was probably the most shabby martialist they had ever known.

“I thought you never lied.”

“That’s because you don’t know me,” Garcia returned while shrugging. “I’m not that inflexible. It doesn’t hurt to lie a little bit here and there. Plus, you’re a member of the Association. You just haven’t got your identity card yet.”

“The hunting license doesn’t work?”

“Licensed hunters should keep their identity confidential, although there are a few exceptions. It’s the total opposite of celebrated martialists.” Garcia said solemnly, “The hunting license does show that the Association trusts you, but it also means a high risk. Many licensed martialists who exposed themselves have been besieged by Fallen Evils.”

This meant that if he revealed his identity as a licensed martialist, many Fallen Evils would come after him.

However, for the safety of Zero and other residents in the apartment building, Roland thought he’d be better not do so.

After his meeting with Lan, he could not view people in the Dream World as mere fictitious characters anymore.

Roland found the sanatorium was well facilitated. It was not very large, but it basically had everything, including a handsome garden, waterfalls and bridges. There were also signs that pointed out the direction to the hot spring, the swimming pool, and the golf court. It was more like a luxurious resort than a santorium.

Roland was deeply impressed.

Even though he was now the King of Graycastle, he had never thought of building a hospital like this.

The hospital building was at the center of the sanatorium. Its shiny, sparkly glass wall reminded Roland of a high-end hotel.

Roland and Garcia went into the hall, and soon a brawny man strode up to them. He was around 40, with dark skin, his martialist cloak whipping behind him. Roland immediately sensed his Force of Nature when the martialist was still around 10 meters from him.

“This is my master’s master,” Garcia said in a low voice and then bowed her head. “Mr. Defender…”

“I’m sorry about Lan,” Rock said heavily as he slightly crouched down and patted Garcia on the shoulder. “It was my fault.”

A little downhearted when hearing Lan’s name, Garcia shook her head and said, “This wasn’t your fault, sir. She always said to me that a martialist should devote himself to fighting the Erosion. If he’s scared, he doesn’t deserve to be an Association member.”

“You’re a good student,” Rock sighed. “Don’t worry. The invaders will pay for that.”

“I’m also willing to help fight the Erosion.”

Rock nodded in approval before he rose and looked toward Roland. “You should be that famous Fallen Evil hunter, Mr. Roland. Nice to meet you. I’m one of the four Defenders of the Prism City, Rock.”

“Nice to meet you,” Roland returned courteously and shook Rock’s hand.

“I have to thank you for easing the tention between the traditional and modern martialists,” Rock said frankly. “I hope you could still continue to protect this world.”

“The honor is mine,” Roland said resolutely.

He could not tolerate anybody that dared to destroy his Dream World.

Roland’s promise greatly cheered Garcia up. She was very proud that Roland had finally decided to take some social responsibilities.

The visit started at 3:00. There were around 20 people, all led by Rock. Apparently, not all the executives of the Prism City attended this event except a few representatives, including the celebrated martialist Fei Yuhan.

If truth be told, Roland was a little afraid of that genius girl. He remembered that during the joint mission last time, he had asked Ling to knock out all the survivors. However, Fei Yuhan overheard their conversation and started to suspect his true identity. Roland had resolved to deny the fact, but to his surprise, Fei Yuhan did not ask him about anything. Yet Roland was certain that she still remembered that incident.

Therefore, he managed to keep a distance from Fei Yuhan and remain silent. Fortunately, Fei Yuhan was very popular and was always surrounded by a lot of people, so she did not get a chance to speak to Roland.

They shook hands with patients and said a few encourging words. Since Garcia was not with Roland, and he was just a newbie in the Association, few executives knew him. As such, Roland simply followed the others and waited to be introduced. This was probably also the Association’s intention of bringing him here.

“The next patient is Valkries,” the doctor said as he peered down the list. “She was severely injured. We should have let her rest, but since you’re already here, let’s say hello to her. Please keep quiet after you get in.”

“We will. We believe that the health of the Association member is the most important,” Rock said as he gave a nod of approval and then pushed open the door.

There was only one patient in the room. The room was a lot larger than Roland’s apartment and could easily accommodate 20 people. Roland was the last to enter, and he waited to shake hands with her as usual.

However, Roland was shocked when he saw her.

It was a familiar face. The patient has thin, slender brows, a pair of cold eyes, a tall nose and beautiful lips. It was a beautiful and delicate face, even though her skin was blue. In fact, she looked even more attractive with pale blue skin.

For quite a while, Roland stood rooted the ground. Then, he started to search his memories.

He remembered the memory fragment in the apartment building.

It recorded an upgrade ceremony held in a demon’s city, and the host was exactly this Valkries!

Roland had almost thought that the Senior Demon had infiltrated the Dream World and invaded this world through the memory fragment!

Shocked and dismayed, Roland studied the patient attentively and then found that she was a little different from the person he remembered.

The biggest difference was that the patient in front of him did not have a third eye on her forehead.

Chapter 1237: Observation

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Roland was positive that the Senior Demon he remembered was, at that time, standing on a platform and teaching two upgraded demons fighting techniques. Her white muslin clothes swirling behind her formed a glaring contrast with the churning Red Mist pond down below, and her third eye on the forehead was glistening. He would never forget such an incredible scene.

Although the patient did not have that distinctive third eye, she, for some reason, resembled that Senior Demon. Roland was thus aroused by this demon martialist named “Valkries”.

When it was his turn to shake hands, Roland did not leave immediately but stopped at her bedside.

“Are you living the in the modular apartment?”

Everyone, who was about to withdraw from the room, was all taken back as Roland spoke.

Valkries remained expressionless. After a moment of reflection, she shook her head.

Roland remembered that the female demon was actually a lot older than Zero, so she should not be one of Zero’s captures.

“Do you have a twin sister by any chance, or someone who looks like you?” Roland pursued as he pointed at his own forehead. “For example, someone with an eye on her forehead?”

The crowd was stirred. The Defender coughed in embarrassment and reminded promptly, “Mr. Roland.”

“Just a minute,” Roland said as he waved his hand. “You just reminded me of someone I know.”

Valkries spoke in the same indifferent manner, “No.”

“How could that be possible? I’ve never seen anyone on the Cargarde Peninsula who has a third eye,” someone mumbled. “There are people who have three fingers though.”

“Alright…” Roland conceded but suddenly burst out boldly, “Charita!”

Valkries, however, did not respond at all as though still in a daze.

If Valkries was a demon from the other world, she should have understood the demon language and had some reaction.

It appeared that she really had nothing to do with that Senior Demon Roland knew.

Roland shrugged, extended out his right hand and said, “I hope you feel better soon, return to the Association, and fight the Erosion together.”

She hesitated for a second and slowly stretched out her hand.

The moment the two hands touched each other, Roland could not help uttering a surprised exclamation.

The Defender asked a little irritably, “What’s the matter?”

“Her hand is so cold… and a little wet as well.”

The onlookers gaffawed. Roland could hear them comment derisively under their breath.

“Frivolous.”

“Why did they pick such a brainless young man as the representative of the traditional martialists?”

“There, there. The patient needs some rest. Let’s visit the next one,” the doctor said while shaking his head. “What a mess…”

Roland shrugged. As the creator of the Dream World, he did not really care about what other people thought of him. Since he could not get anything out of Valkries, there was no point in continuing to stay here. He thus cast Valkries one last glance and left the room.

…

Valkries was still in a shock after everyone left.

She had just experienced the most difficult 15 minutes in her life. She had never thought that one day, she would exercise all her effort just to keep her face straight. It had almost cost all her energy.

When that man came up to her, Valkries felt all her blood within freeze. She would never forget that person. In the memory of the Silent Disaster, she had seen the exact same person stand on the other side of the legacy shard, watching the Silent Disaster being besieged by tentacles.

She had not only been watching but also experiencing it herself. Therefore, she had also been somewhat affected by the Silent Disaster’s emotions. As Valkries had also been quite shocked and flustered at that time, she immediately associated Roland with the man in the Silent Disaster’s memory when she saw him.

Her previous assumptions were all wrong, and she had to admit that there was a third possibility. The quaver of the Realm of Mind told her something. She had been on the right track, and this world was created by that man. In other words, Roland was the creator of this territory.

Had she met Roland in the real world, she would have immediately killed him. Like most of the upgraded demons, Valkries also possessed extraordinary fighting capacity. No matter how powerful Roland was, she would make every effort to finish him.

Nevertheless, things were a little different in the Realm of Mind. According to the king, nobody could kill him in his own territory. The king was an omnipotent and omnscient sort of existence that was almost like God to her. The king could be exaggerating, but Valkries did not dare take a chance.

She knew very well that she could encounter something worse than death. If Roland also had the ability to probe into her memories, the information she knew may jeopardize her entire clan.

Therefore, she must be extra cautious when dealing with such a tough enemy.

Fortunately, eveything was still uncertain. Valkries could tell that Roland was also in the process of figuring out her true identity. He did not have terrifying perspicacity like the king. Valkries was dimly aware that Roland had seen her somewhere. Although she did not know how, his act of demeanor told her that he remembered her.

Most likely he had met her in the other world.

Otherwise, he would not have asked her whether she had seen anybody with a third eye. The third eye on her forehead was actually the magic stone she had obtained during her third upgrade.

Also, the word “charita” meant “hero” in the ancient language.

Valkries stretched out her hand and studied it up and down. She thought of the moment Roland had touched her hand.

Her breath had almost stopped when Roland had uttered the exclamation. Luckily, she had successfully fooled him. Valkries still remembered the purpose of this trip. It was not only a challenge but also an opportunity. She had easily found the key person in the human race. As a male, he had inherited the legacy shard and also repelled the Silent Disaster with his mind. Beyond a doubt, this man possessed a lot of information that the clan did not know. She must get to the bare truth of it.

Valkries was sure that this man created this world to achieve something, just as the king created the Presiding Holy See to better manage his subordinates. She sniffed conspiracies here from the words “Fallen Evils”, “fight” and “Erosion”. Therefore, she must figure out what kind of schemes this man was planning in the Realm of Mind.

The conference that the doctor had mentioned might provide her a glimpse of what was going on.

Valkries clenched her fist at this thought.

Roland… right?

Now, I remember you!

Chapter 1238: An Army of One Person

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The conference was held in the hall of the sanatorium.

Almost all of the professional martial artists were invited.

However, Roland noticed that there were only about 300 people attending the meeting, which was significantly lower than the number registered in the Prism City. Apart from those who were injured or killed during the battle, some people had cold feet after the massive outbreak of the “Erosion”.

They were probably amateur martial artists who had recently joined the Association.

Garcia denounced such cowardice and believed that it was an insult to their awakened Forces of Nature. Those people would pay for their cravenness when the Fallen Evils completely overpowered human beings.

Roland consoled Garcia, but he knew the Martial Artist Association was a relatively loose organization. In a modern society like the Dream World, the Martial Artist Association had no authority to bind the martial artists and ask them to tag along.

Roland had anticipated what direction this meeting would go into.

The Defender, Rock, briefly explained the current dilemma the Association was facing. After the attack at the Prism City, more Fallen Evils attacked the Awakened. Although there was no solid evidence at this point, it appeared that the new enemy that appeared in the Erosion had the ability to control Fallen Evils. This meant that the war would enter a new stage. The Martial Artist Association would organize people and repel the Fallen Evils more systematically. In the meantime, the Fallen Evils had also come up with plans to kill martial artists. The situation for human beings was now very critical.

Rock thus suggested that all the martial artists, both official members and newbies, should stay here in this sanatorium until order was re-established in the Prism City, as the sanatorium would afford some protection from their enemies. He also expressed his wish that all the invited martial artists should realize the precarious condition they were currently in and united to fight this battle together.

This was a perfect way to raise the morale among the martial artists. Roland believed that once this information spread, some hesitant amateur martial artists would probably return to the Association.

Whether or not all the people came back depended on the outcome of the battle. If the Fallen Evils outstripped the Association, more people would probably choose to flee.

It was extremely difficult to re-establish confidence.

As Roland had expected, Rock started to discuss the countermeasure.

One strategy was to send for the martial artists from other cities to solve Prism City’s lack of manpower.

Secondly, the Martial Artist Contest should continue, in order to attract more Fallen Evils. The government and the executives of the Association had already approved this plan. Once the enemy appeared, they would face the wrath of the Defender and the martial artists.

Thirdly, the Association would set up a patrol team to prevent the Fallen Evils from attacking innocent citizens. Therefore, the martial artists would be divided into several groups, each of which being responsible for defending one area. In this way, they could immediately support each other in the event of an emergency and could also besiege the enemy once they received information from the intelligence agency.

The preliminary counterattack plan was quite conservative, considering that they lacked sufficient information.

The leader of each group could select their own team members, and a heated discussion immediately swept over the hall.

Roland did not want to be assigned to any team. In a sense, he himself was an army, and he did not want anyone to interfere with his magic core collection plan. Fortunately, few people in the Association knew him, so nobody asked him to join their team.

Until Fei Yuhan walked up to him and offered an invitation.

In fact, as the most popular martial artists, Fei Yuhan only invited two people.

But Roland turned her down without the slightest hesitation.

Everyone dropped their jaws, including Garcia. She asked Roland to think it over. It appeared that even self-disciplined Garcia spoke highly of this girl.

It took Roland a while to convince Garcia that he’d be better off fighting alone. The best proof was his previous feats and his hunting license.

The only thing that Roland was concerned about was that the other person Fei Yuhan invited was the demon martial artist, Valkries.

It was 10:00 PM when Roland returned to his apartment.

After Zero went to bed, Roland entered the second floor of the Rose Café through the side door of the warehouse.

More than 50 Taquila ancient witches bowed to him and paid him the highest respect. This was the first time that so many witches had come to the Dream World. The room was packed.

Back in the Union age, a team of 50 combat witches would have been sufficient to conduct a small battle.

“Any luck?”

Roland looked toward Faldi.

“Yes, the flies released by the Bug Nest sensed a few disappearing magic reactions,” Faldi replied as she scrolled down the cell phone screen and showed Roland the map. She was not used to using the digital map, but somehow she managed it. “Normally, this indicates that there are God’s Stones of Retaliation around there, or that our target can hide its magic power. If neither of the two applies, then it would mean that the target is dead.”

“But there’s no God’s Stone of Retaliation in the Dream World, and the Force of Nature isn’t as diverse as witches’ abilities,” Roland said.

“That’s right. So we assume that the Fallen Evils fought with the awakened martial artists. Somebody died and their cores were taken away,” Faldi replied while nodding. “Based on the direction of the magic reaction, they probably went here — ”

She pointed at a pier on the inner river.

It appeared that the river bank was always the first choice of locations to commit a crime.

“Since my flies can’t go that far, I contacted Ling for further investigation. She told me an hour ago that she found many Fallen Evils.”

“Well done,” Roland said with a faint smile. This was the reason he did not need the support of the Association. The Taquila witches could locate the enemies and kill them on their own. “I believe that you’re all ready.”

“Your Majesty, please issue your command,” the witches chorused.

Their morale was high after they had had a good time during the day.

For them, fighting was another way to savor their past.

In addition to enjoying food, using magic was extremely joyous for them.

“Everyone, ready, go!” Roland ordered briskly.

“Yes, Your Majesty!”

Chapter 1239: Two Options

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Updated by NovelFull.Com

The port was only around 15 kilometers from the apartment. To avoid unwelcome attention, all the witches dispersed and headed in different directions.

Roland was the last to set off. He drove his shabby mini van out of the residential area, with Phyllis and Faldi sitting at the rear.

He had upgraded their equipment after the joint mission organized by the Martial Artist Association. Although the equipment was not as advanced as that distributed by the Association, the appliances he had bought from the market were also quite a good alternative.

The walkie-talkies he had bought from the website were equipped with bluetooth microphones, which enabled the witches to communicate with each other within five kilometers. In reality, however, due to the interference of surrounding buildings and the complicated electromagnetic field, the communication was only effective when the witches were no more than two kilometers from each other. Since the speakers were less than 200 Yuan, and he could receive a discount if he placed a bulk order, Roland decided to equip each of the ancient witches with a walkie-talkie.

At least, the walkie-talkie was more convenient than a cell phone, and it attracted less attention of passers-by.

Roland often saw in a movie where an unexpected call jeopardized the whole mission. He felt it not only stupid but also unrealistic. He definitely did not want to make the same mistake.

Faldi, who had the ability to track people down, naturally became the key liaison person.

“Your Majesty, Betty’s team has reached the port and met up with Ling.”

“Ask them to hide themselves first until the rest of the team arrive,” Roland said without looking backward.

“OK. Dawnen’s team is still on the way and they’ll be there in five minutes, but she doesn’t have much money.”

“Um… ask them who has extra to give to Dawnen.”

“Hold on. Dawnen says that the driver has overheard their conversation and agreed to give them a ride for free.”

“Alright then…” Roland said as he rolled his eyes. Why did nobody give him a free ride?

Five seconds after Faldi hung up, Roland’s phone rang again. “Your Majesty, Twinkle says she has to take a detour. It looks like that she’s not going to the port.”

Roland frowned and asked, “Where is she?”

Before he finished, the phone was hung up abruptly, and Roland heard a loud bang on the other end of the line.

Then there was a series of noises.

Everything fell silent afterwards.

Roland massaged his temple and said, “Well… ask her to take another taxi. Remember to avoid the surveillance camera.”

“Got it, Your Majesty,” Faldi promised.

Around an hour later, all the witches reached the port.

The team that arrived first had already started to eat sunflower seeds.

Fortunately, the Fallen Evils had used the port as their temporary headquarters and did not notice the presence of the witches. They would have probably fled had this been a running fight. Roland suddenly had an urge to purchase more mini vans to avoid such embarrassment.

He cleared his throat and asked Ling, “What are the Fallen Evils doing?”

“Your Majesty, the Fallen Evils are all in the loading area. There are more than 30 of them. Some of their scouts are on the iron boxes outside. We could easily pass them unnoticed under Dawnen’s Veil of Invisibility. The lighting condition is pretty good in the area close to the inner river. I didn’t want to get too close to it, so I just took a look at the distance. Most of the Fallen Evils are there, but they could go anywhere. If we fight, I can’t guarantee that we could capture every one of them.”

Ling’s ability was to be fused with shadows, and she could hide herself perfectly at night just like Nightingale. In other words, she was the best scout.

Roland said thoughtfully, “Well, in that case, let’s lure them out and kill them. Entice them away from the river bank so that they can’t flee by water, and then we can surround them.”

“It seems feasible in theory, but how to lure them away?” Phyllis asked.

Roland smiled and pointed at himself. “I’ve heard that the Fallen Evils are attacking martial artists. They have no reason to let me go.”

After all the witches disappeared in the darkness, Roland revealed himself and strolled to the dump site, as though he was simply a resident who happened to be having a walk here.

The dump site was dead quiet. The pattering of his footsteps and the humming of insects with which the silence teemed, became extremely audible. Piles of boxes loomed against the soft glow of yellow lights. It appeared that nobody would come to this deep, desolate labyrinth of boxes at this hour.

Dawnen reminded the rest of the team over the cheap walk-talkie that there were a few Fallen Evils lurking at the port.

Apparently, the scouts of the Fallen Evils noticed Roland’s Force of Nature and notified their peers. To Roland’s surprise, the Fallen Evils did not attack him immediatley but watched him amble around the port for a few minutes.

Then, suddenly, the whole port area was as bright as day when the lights at the dump site were turned on!

In the blinding light, Roland saw a dozen people slowly reveal themselves from the shadow. After his eyes were adapted to the dazzling light, he found himself surrounded by the Fallen Evils.

The man, who appeared to be the leader, was wearing a mask with strange patterns on it. He stood out from all the other Fallen Evils. Roland noticed that his mask looked like a gate that was about to burst open.

There were also two men standing next to the leader, who did not look like ordinary Fallen Evils, for their eyes had yet slid out of focus, and they were wearing the clothes distributed by the Martial Artist Association.

“Good evening, poor man,” the leader said in a surprisingly polite tone. “I don’t know what brought you here, but you should know that you have no chance to escape. Rather than waste your time and energy, I would recommend you to first listen to me.”

Roland looked around and saw that there were Fallen Evils in all directions.

“Don’t be afraid. I don’t want to kill you. On the contrary, this may be a very rare opportunity. I just came to this world and I need your help,” the man said as he extended out his hands. “Don’t refuse it right away. Please let me introduce myself. I’m the ambassador of God, Alpha, from what you call the ‘Erosion’.”

Roland should have pretended to be frightened so that they would put their guard down. However, for some reason, Roland had an urge to punch the man in his face and shatter his triumphant, courteous smile.

“So, you’re the monster that invaded the Prism City?”

“Invasion isn’t the exact word, because this place belongs to God,” Alpha said placidly. “Now it’s time to return it. Look, lost man, the so-called martial artists will eventually be defeated and return to nothingness. It’s more advisable to pledge fealty to God.”

“I know it’s hard for you to understand now. We have plenty of time to discuss the true nature of this world. I can show you the benefit you could possibly gain from this deal, apart from those empty promises. I can show you power,” the man said while sticking out one finger. Soon, a flicker of red light ignited his fingertip, and Roland sensed a great fluctuation of magic power. “I can give this power to you, and you’ll become much more powerful.”

“Mr. Apostle isn’t lying,” two men beside the leader rejoined. “We were just awakened, and now we feel that we have tons of energy!”

“And you won’t lose your mind either like those Fallen Evils.”

“What if I decline?”

“Then I’ll have to turn you into one of those monsters. Although they’re relatively weak, they obey me,” Alpha threatened while shrugging. “You can choose between the truth and power and being reduced to an unconscious monster that has an insatiable desire for the Force of Nature. You know which one is a better choice.”

“Your Majesty, everyone is ready,” Faldi whispered over the walkie-talkie.

Roland twitched his lips and said, “Then let me tell you what the true nature of this world is. I create this world, and I won’t give it to anyone. So, you have two options. One is that you give me your cores and die here. The other is that I kill you, and it’ll take me some extra time to collect your cores. Which one do you choose?”

“Stupid man!” the martial artists who had betrayed the Association hollered. “You can kill us just by yourself?”

“No, haven’t you noticed that you’ve been surrounded?” Roland said and snapped his fingers. “Kill them.”

Chapter 1240: The Witches’ War

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Huh? Surrounded? Stop acting. Sir Alpha can sense every single fluctuation of the Force of Nature — ” Before the martial artists could finish, a flying box hit him right in the nose. He was thrown into the air and flew backwards, and he stopped dead.

Another traitor gaped at the witches who came out all of a sudden from all directions. Some came down from the sky and some from underneath, but most of them just came out of nowhere, as though they had been waiting for them for quite a long time.

This did not make any sense. Those women were no more than 10 meters from him. Even if they did not possess the Force of Nature, he should have heard their breath and footsteps!

Why did the scout not alarm him beforehand?

But he had no time to think it over.

Instantly, the two parties started to fight.

The quiet port was stirred.

Ling was hiding in the shadow. Light and shadow always came hand in hand. Although the dump site was lit by the street lights, the shadow cast by the boxes created a perfect hiding spot for her.

She had nailed her target already. Those Fallen Evils at the highpoint, which cast a long shadow on the ground and were fused with the darkness, gave her a perfect opportunity to launch an attack. If someone took a peek at Ling from behind, he would be totally shocked. Ling’s body had merged into the shadow in the entirety, with only half of her head poking out. Several bubbles escaped from her nostrils silently.

Ling liked submerging into shadows. It was a warmer and more comfortable sensation than bathing in a hot spring. She had thought that she would never be able to have this pleasure again after turning into a God’s Punishment Witch, until Phyllis had informed her of this incredible world a year ago.

It was a world of wonder that could bring her back to the past.

Ling had fallen in love with this world the first time she had visited it.

King Roland had transformed from a mortal with a strong personality into the Chosen One, whose authority could not be challenged, despite that he could not activate the instrument. Ling, Pasha and Celine always nagged Roland to take them to the Dream World. Ling had also persuaded Roland to pick her as the guardian of the three witches who were sent to school.

Ling knew that she had demons to kill, but it did not hurt to relax herself every now and then.

Anyone who attempted to cause His Majesty harm or destroy the Dream World was deemed as the mortal enemy of the Taquila witches.

As soon as the command was issued, Ling rose out of the shadow like a ghost and dived a dagger into one Fallen Evil’s chest.

Ordinary weapons could not fatally wound a Fallen Evil. Therefore, she had to also inject magic power into it. Ling could feel the Fallen Evil’s energy become unstable. It seemed that the two powers were interfering with each other. This proved His Majesty’s theory in a way: the Force of Nature and magic power were essentially the same thing. They were both from the “Erosion”.

Ling would only need to take out the corrupted core before the Fallen Evil collapsed into a pulp.

The moment that Fallen Evil fell, Ling flew several meters, passed a few boxes, and landed behind another Fallen Evil.

The fight was fierce below.

Soon, she eradicated all the scouts.

Ling stood on the highest point of the dump site and watched the battle from above. All the witches were as powerful as 400 years ago. In fact, they became even faster after receiving intense training after becoming God’s Punishment Warriors. Nevertheless, Ling was more pleased with the high morale than their progress in fighting skills.

Betty’s immense strength made her temporarily a Transcendent. She held an iron box single-handed and pushed her way through a group of Fallen Evils.

Twinkle and Phyllis were still the best partners. Every time Twinkle blinded their enemies with her ability, Phyllis’ Blade Claws would reach the vital parts of the enemy’s body.

Dawnen and Rother also did a wonderful job. Ling thought of the fierce battle back in Taquila age. She cast a glance at Roland. Perhaps, Roland did not even realize that the Dream World did not only provide the witches with mundane pleasures but also alleviated their stress.

They had gone through the darkest time of their life in the several hundred years after the fall of the three Holy Cities and the collapse of the Union. Everybody invested all their strength in adapting to their new bodies. The loss of sensations made them gradually forget about life enjoyment. Since they had no clues as to who the Chosen one was, everyone was stressed out. Even though they could switch bodies, their morale decreased every day. Ling had even doubted, at that time, that they would die of pressure rather than be killed by demons.

But the teeming Third Border City injected new hopes into them. They started to discuss which restaurant had the best take-out food, and the lost past gradually came back to them. Even if there were no Dream World, they would still be able to enjoy their life. This was so different from hundreds of years ago.

Ling knew all the other witches felt the same way, and that was why they had such a high morale.

They could not tolerate any Erosions in the Dream World.

She thus leaped into the air, jumped right onto one Fallen Evils, and joined the battle.

The moment Betty threw out the box, Roland dashed forward and struck the leader.

Based on his past experience, Roland knew that it was very difficult to deal with the red and black area and the black tentacles generated by the magic creature. Even witches would find a hard time getting rid of them.

However, the magic creature could not do any harm to Roland. As long as Roland held the leader back, the witches would finish the rest of the enemies off.

As Roland had expected, Alpha could not escape from his clutch, and his contemptuous tone changed.

“You—”

“I told you that I’m the creator,” Roland cut cross him, leaving him no chance to argue. He had already known what the leader was going to say. “I don’t care whether you’re an Apostle or not. I don’t give it a damn!” Roland pushed the man down to the ground and punched him in the face over and over again while mumbling furiously under his breath, until the man’s mask cracked and revealed the astrolabe underneath.

The man’s face was the core.

Roland pulled out the astrolabe immediately.

In a split second, the energy within him erupted from his palm and turned into a dazzling light beam that surrounded the astrolobe. As though attracted by the light beam, the cores of the Fallen Evils all fell off and splintered into thousands of glitters that gradually converged and lit the dark sky.

Roland, once again, felt that this world was changing.

However, this was not the end. The light beam became increasingly brighter and finally enveloped him! Roland felt that something was swarming into his head. An excruciating pain seared through him, and he almost lost his consciousness.

His vision blurred, and everything in front of him was reduced to a snow screen that he usually saw on the television in 70s.

He then heard hissing noises.

On the static noise screen, Roland saw a large pit.

Chapter 1241: God’s Eye

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“What’s going on?”

Roland tried to speak or move his body, but he was completely paralyzed. Several pictures fleeted in front of him.

Numerous black dots paced back and forth around the pit like ants on the move. Slowly, a platform rose. However, compared to the giant pit, the platform was incredibly small like a mound of earth.

To Roland’s surprise, he had seen buildings of the same material before.

He had seen them on the mural in the Temple of the Cursed.

Roland zoomed in “screen” with his mind, and the noises grew louder. The black dots turned into wriggly creatures, which were exactly the main character on the mural, the radiation clan.

He suddenly remembered that this was exactly what the mural depicted.

A dozen radiation clansmen ascended the platform while holding the God’s Relic. They encircled the platform, their bodies contracting and expanding alternatively, as if they were holding a kind of ceremony.

Below the platform were thousands of Match Men, who were pushed into the fathomless pit before the celebrating Radiation Clan.

The last piece of the Relic was inserted, and the transparent crystal became complete. It emanated a dazzling glow and drifted toward the pit. Then it plunged and disappeared from the sight.

Roland suddenly realized that this was probably what Lan called the “Bottomless Land”.

But this was just the beginning.

Roland’s eye widened as he beheld the following scene.

An orange light beam erupted from the pit and soared into the air. This was exactly what the ancient witches had described as the strange phenomenon upon entering the Dream World, but the light beam was much more intense. A “Bloody Moon” hung in the sky right across where the Erosion took place. For a split moment, the Heaven and Earth were connected, and Roland realized that the entrances to the so-called Bottomless Land and the Erosion were simply the two ends of the light beam.

The Radiation Clan swarmed toward the pit as flying moths darted into the fire.

But they did not plummet into the abyss. Instead, they drifted off as if supported by something and rose to the sky.

In an instant, there were innumerable black dots around the light beam.

Is this… the upgrade of a civilization?

Clouds scudded across the black dots and the light beam. Watching those black dots enter a new realm, Roland felt the whole upgrade process extraordinary.

Nevertheless, a deep sigh interrupted his train of thought. The voice reverberated across his head, so clear that Roland was positive that it was not an illusion.

Then time became seemingly faster, and the pixels on the “screen” became denser.

The image changed drastically.

Roland saw a few cities and towns dotted around the pit. Apparently, not all the members of the Radiation Clan were willing to enter the new world. Some preferred to stay. Probably, they feared the sky and the unknown adventure ahead of them. Roland did not know. He only saw several black dots disappear into the passage that connected the Heaven and Earth, like those legendary, audacious adventurers who set off for their journey. They looked, however, extremely lonely since most of their clansmen were already gone.

Now, the light beam dimmed.

In the end, it flickered and then vanished.

The noise screen again occupied Roland’s vision, which marked the end of the story. Roland speculated that peace would be restored eventually. The legend of the road to Heaven would become a part of the history of the Radiation Clan, a written record for future reference. Perhaps, someone else would come to seek the pit and look for the upgrade method to reach God, but this would be something many years later.

When Roland thought that this was the end, a “towering wall” suddenly appeared at the end of the horizon.

At first, he had thought it was an illusion, since the “noise screen” blocked his vision. However, when the “wall” approached the pit gradually, he finally saw what that was.

A huge wave taller than the Impassable Mountain Range pressed in and submerged the little towns below instantly. The wave was so high that the top of it almost reached the clouds in the sky. Sun rays glazed off the wave and formed a new horizon.

Roland could imagine how desperate the Radiation Clan were when they saw such a horrific scene.

But the disaster did not stop here.

After the tsunami, volcanos at the distance suddenly erupted. Ashes were sent flying in all directions and dimmed the sunlight. Thunderbolts cracked through the air. Then there came heavy rain and harsh winter. The geographical movement became, unprecedentedly, active. After several major disastrous transformations, the world had transformed into an entirely different look.

The screen started to hiss again.

The image distorted, and the pixels almost filled out the whole “screen”.

Before the scene vanished, Roland saw the glacier melt, and a green plant break through the soil and sprout.

“Your Majesty…”

“Your Majesty, are you alright?”

Someone shook Roland and looked at him apprehensively.

His eyes snapped open, and the pixels disappeared. He found himself again in the port area.

“All… done?” Roland mumbled as he studied his palm.

Phyllis thought Roland was asking her, so she said, “Yes, we killed all of them. Not a single one fled. Their magic cores also disappeared a few minutes later. You stood rooted here like you’ve fallen asleep. Your Majesty, are you really OK?”

Roland was not sure whether he was alright or not. All he had seen a moment ago did not seem like an illusion, for he could remembered all of them. They were more like some extra memories coming out from nowhere. In addition, he felt extremely exhausted, as though he had lived thousands of years in just a few minutes.

He somehow understood that sigh.

Roland thought of Lan’s words.

“The truth is always what you understand.”

Was this… the last of the Battle of Divine Will?

Roland took a deep breath and said, “I’m fine. I just saw some strange phenomena.”

“Strange phenomena?” Phyllis echoed while blinking. “This isn’t the time to say this, Your Majesty. The light beam just now almost lit half of the port and should have attracted a lot of attention. We must go. Otherwise, the Association will notice us.”

“Got it. Let’s head back the way we came,” Roland agreed with a nod.

Roland was not sure whether those were the Apostle’s memories or something else, but he believed that one day, he would find the answer to these questions.

And Roland believed that day would come soon.

Chapter 1242: Departure from the Northernmost Port

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

At the Northernmost Port in the Kingdom of Everwinter.

“Don’t push. Stand in line!”

“Abandon the luggage! The King of Graycastle will provide you with sufficient food and clothes. If you want to survive, throw your luggage into the water!”

“Hurry up! Ladies and children first!”

The port was filled with refugees who were swarming toward the ships. Had the First Army and the lord’s guards not maintained the order, those refugees would have probably trodded on each other to board the ships.

“Captain, we probably… can’t accommodate so many refugees,” the chief guard said apprehensively as he looked backwards at the ships packed with refugees that were now slowly departing from the port.

“It’s very brave of them to come to the Northernmost Port at this time of year,” Uncle Sang commented as he gazed at the front. Within three to four days, the Red Mist had spread out from the crest of the Impassable Mountain Range. The sky was awash with a crimson color, which cast a shadow over everybody’s heart.

“Captain… save a spot for me,” someone muttered.

Uncle Sang said with a smile, “If Nail asked me, I would definitely save a spot for him, even if that means I have to get off the ship.”

Over half a month ago, they had received instructions to leave the Hermes Plateau for the city at the far north of the Kingdom of Everwinter to carry out the immigration compaign. Compared to defend the Holy City, Nail preferred this task a lot better. He felt more relaxed after taking this mission and also became more communicative during the voyage. As soon as he reached the Northernmost Port, he started the campaign.

They were not the first Graycastle men that arrived at the Kingdom of Everwinter. Many of his colleagues had visited the kingdom and evacuated the cities ahead of time. The evacuation work did not go very well at first until the Bloody Moon emerged. Rumors were circulated among the community that the “Bloody Moon” represented the end of the world. Therefore, when local residents saw the crimson moon in the sky, they were terrified and immediatley asked the soldiers stationed there to get them out of the city.

Unfortunately, the situation turned for the worse.

Four or five days later, they were informed of the presence of the Red mist.

On the same day, the First Army encountered demons.

They did know the outcome of the battle, but the advance team started to retreat to the south, and Nail’s team also received instructions to retreat to the next port.

In the meantime, there was a huge increase in the number of refugees. Hundreds of thousands of people rushed to the Northernmost Port every day and asked the soldiers to take them away. Nail could not ignore their pleading, so he asked his men to build up a defensive line while at the same time asking the army at the rear to send him more ships via the carrier pigeon. Because of this, their retreat plan was delayed for several days.

Uncle Sang knew that once the news of the Red Mist was spread out, fewer ships would come to the north. Those Chambers of Commerce retained by His Majesty would not risk their own lives to carry out the mission. They would probably, very reluctantly, agree to sail out, but they would never reach here. These were probably the last ships that came to rescue.

Nail had foreseen that this would happen beforehand, so he had asked his team members to prepare some explosives in advance. They could not only ignite the explosives in the event of an attack from the demons but could also destroy the equipment on the ship that was not easy to take away to prevent the demons from obtaining these technologies.

“Captain, there’s smoke at the front!” someone shouted.

“Again?” Uncle Sang said. “Everybody, man your post!”

Shortstaffed, with no witch scouts to help them, they had to rely on the traditional means of communication to deliver messages.

This was not the first time that the demons had visited the Northernmost Port. There were actually a few demons’ bodies outside the town. According to the manual distributed by the management team, these demons were mostly Mad Demons. Although the enemies were scattered around and appeared not to be very powerful, it did indicate that the demons had set foot on the Kingdom of Everwinter and that they were slowly approaching as the Red Mist permeated.

As a troop that had been stationed at Hermes ever since the battle at the Coldwind Ridge, Nail’s unit did not participate in the Taquila battle. Although Uncle Sang had told him a lot about the war, this was, essentially, his first time to confront the demons. After several fights, Nail concluded that as long as the Mad Demons were more than 200 meters from the defensive line, they were easier to deal with than the church’s God’s Punishment Warriors.

Uncle Sang was not too worried about the beacon. Instead, he was more concerned about Nail’s decision. Without a doubt, it was impossible to take all the refugees away with only two ships. What would the captain do with the people left behind? Would he abandon them to their fate or take them to the south?

Just then, he saw a Mad Demon outside the barbed wire erected on the street.

Uncle Sang frowned.

Like most of the port cities, the Northernmost Port did not have a city wall. Therefore, they had built the defensive line at the dock. Apart from refugees, all the residents were gone. Naturally, the city attracted demons. However, to Uncle Sang’s dismay, the scouts were gone, too. Technically, they should have retreated after seeing the beacon and returned to the defensive line faster than the enemies.

Gradually, more Mad Demons appeared and swarmed toward the dock.

“Fire!”

The two machine gun squads opened fire together, and shells rained down at the demons. The demons were swift too. They immediately took refuge in the buildings nearby. After the dust and smoke dissipated, there were only two bodies left on the barbed wire.

Gun shots soon rented the air.

Apparently, the sniper team opened fire at the demons who lurked on the roof.

This was their military tactic. Considering that they did not have a broad view in the urban area, they had set up many obstacles over the past week. The soldiers had blocked most of the streets and alleys with garbage and property debris. These obstacles could not completely stop the demons but could hold them back. If the demons did not want to waste their time on removing obstacles and clearing the road, they would have to confront the machine gun squads directly.

Then, they would face a bitter and ferocious fight. Since there were not many demons, Uncle Sang did not think that the demons would dart to the front and spear. The demons should have retreated considering they were outnumbered. However, they were sticking to this hide-and-seek game, as if they intended to exhaust the First Army’s ammunition.

The demons today were apparently more persistent than those a few days ago. It seemed that they had a lot of war experience.

Uncle Sang sneered. Had the God’s Punishment Army been so persistent, they would have had a difficult time. Nevertheless, the First Army was now better equipped. They had 100 soldiers, four Mark I Machine Guns, and ammunition that could last at least one day. Uncle Sang was sure that the demons would end up dying here if things continued like that.

However, the situation suddenly changed.

With a loud bang, dust was stirred up in the residential area in the north of the dock. A huge armored monster broke through the stone walls and rose on its rear from the debris.

“Spider Demon?” a soldier asked in surprise.

“Load the anti-demon grenade!”

Uncle Sang’s heart sank. The manual did mention a type of demon that resembled a spider. However, this demon was a little different from the Spider Demon he knew.

Its limbs were covered with much thicker black stones that almost took up half of its body.

Chapter 1243: Rescue

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Two soldiers immediately approached the new enemy and fired the anti-demon grenade.

Two strands of smoke shot toward the gigantic Spider Demon from behind the bunk. They could not miss such a large target. Uncle Sang’s heart leaped to his throat as he watched the trajectories of the two shells. For some reason, he had an undefined feeling that the thick armor the demon was wearing was not that easy to deal with.

He was right.

One grenade hit the target and was bounced off into the ground.

The other one hit the demon’s front leg and exploded. Nevertheless, the demon was not stopped at all. On the contrary, it leaned a little forward and strode in their direction against the dust.

“Shot the body, you thickhead!” someone complained.

“Let me try!” Another soldier volunteered, who carried a box of shells and crept out of the trench.

Uncle Sang did not stop him, but he was not as optimistic as the others. Now he came to the realization why the new Spider Demon looked somewhat strange to him. Compared to the misshapen Spider Demon on the manual, this one looked more coordinated. The “armor” it was wearing was not made of random irregular-shaped stones but neat polygons. If those stones were connected, they could probably form a perfect trapezoid.

Also, its limbs swung on its side when it walked, which made it harder for the soldiers to shoot its torso or abdomen. No wonder the two previous shots had missed the target.

As Uncle Sang had expected, the next few shots did not stop the Spider Demon either. The demon almost automatically curled up the moment the soldiers fired.

In the meantime, Mad Demons appeared again in the rupture created by the Spider Demon.

“Damn it. Can’t those guys be more serious?” a machine gunner complained as he adjusted the muzzle.

“Enough!” Uncle Sang yelled briskly. “Retreat to the second defensive line and abandon this area. Prepare to ignite the explosives.”

“But…”

“Shut up,” Uncle Sang hollered. “If the demons besiege us from the side, we’ll be stuck here!”

Horns trumpeted across the battlement. Nail’s team retreated to the port according to the training procedure. The refugees panicked as the monster slowly approached them.

The soldier responsible for igniting the explosives connected the detonating cord to the motor and set the motor in motion. “Captain, we’re ready!”

“Very well. Let them have a taste of the explosives,” Uncle Sang said as he stared at the monster that clashed in every direction and motioned. “Just a moment… now!”

As the soldier pressed the lever, there was a huge roar. In an instant, the ground beneath started to quaver. The air was impregnated with smoke and dust.

Some explosives had been buried underneath the Spider Demon. The Spider Demon was thus sent flying into the air, and its stone armor became a huge burden. Its joints snapped under the impact. By the time it fell, it had been completely immobilized. Limped and seriously injured, it collapsed to the ground.

Someone in the battlement whistled.

Before they could take a break, another bang occurred in the east of the dock.

Another Spider Demon emerged on the battlefield.

Uncle Sang was glad that he had made the right decision.

He had a vague feeling that the attack of the demons this time might be very different from the previous attacks, Apparently, the demons intended to besiege and eliminate them. The fact that the scouts did not come back in time indicated that the demons had cut their retreat. Had he been hesitant a moment ago, the machine gun squads would have failed to retreat. Although the First Army had now abandoned their stronghold in the alley, they could still rely on four Mark I HMGs to repulse the Mad Demons.

However, this did not mean that the crisis had been resolved. They never knew how many Spider Demons there would be. If there were two more… no, one more Spider Demon, they could hardly hold onto the battlement. What was worse was that many refugees were waiting for the departure at the dock. If the battle sparked panic among them, the whole situation would get out of hand. They would not only be unable to save these people but would fail to board the ships as well.

After the smoke dissipated, the demons stepped forward onto the field where the explosion had just taken place.

Numerous gun shots rented the air.

“Boom!”

While Uncle Sang was worried about what step he should take next, he suddenly heard a familiar roar behind him. Immediately, he knew where that sound came from. This was the sound of the 152-caliber Longsong Cannon that the First Army was most familiar with!

There should not have been any artillery here.

Uncle Sang turned around in dismay and saw an iron ship slowly dock. The cannon parallel to the deck was directly aiming at the defensive line.

“That’s… the ‘Roland’!” a soldier, who recognized the iron ship at once, exclaimed.

“Didn’t they leave already?”

“Who cares? We have support!”

“Long live the king! Kill those filthy monsters!”

Shells brushed past the soldiers and landed on the battlefield in succession. Around 10 meters away from the trench, smoke and dust permeated the air. Some shells hit the sandbags before the trench and exhaled a rain of sand and earth that showered down at the soldiers. The soldiers would have loathed the Artillery Battalion with the most venomous words had it occurred in the past. However, now, everyone appreciated their help. The roar of the Longsong Cannon became the most beautiful music they had ever heard.

Had Nail not abandoned them but been awaiting this moment all along?

Uncle Sang noticed that some refugees, under the guidance of the soldiers, boarded the “Roland”. Most of the refugees got on the ship.

He did not know what Nail had said to the management team, but evidently, this was a good opportunity for them to withdraw.

“Everyone, listen. We have to go to the dock,” Uncle Sang yelled. “One by one. Don’t fall behind! Once everyone leaves, the explosion unit should ignite the rest of the explosives!”

Soon, the order was delivered and spread out throughout the whole trench.

They started their final retreat.

Although quite reluctant, they had to leave the Mark I type HMG and the rest of the ammunition behind. This was the king’s order. Personal safety took precedence over weapons, for soldiers could always create new weapons.

The troop thus entered the dock area, and the demons, in the meantime, also took the second defensive line against the gunfire.

But no sooner had the demons snatched their victory than an earsplitting roar shook them.

Thousands of kilograms of explosives sent the Mad Demons into the air.

In the aftermath of the magnificent explosion, the “Roland” whistled and departed from the ravaged Northernmost Port at a full speed.

Chapter 1244: Change Over Time

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Zooey stood at the bridge and peered down at the crowd on the deck. The “Roland” was not large enough to accommodate 1,000 people. After all the refugees boarded the ship, there was literally no room to sit.

For most of the refugees, it was their first time traveling by sea, and they soon felt nauseous and dizzy. The crowded environment further aggravated the situation. Even those who rarely got seasick felt their stomachs turn uncomfortably when surrounded by sick passengers.

Zooey appreciated the fact that she could not smell anything.

“Mortals are so weak…” Carol’s voice came from behind. “I can’t believe that we used to be like that too.”

“Yes, that’s incredible,” Zooey said with a nod of approval.

She knew what Carol was referring to.

After the captain had received the instructions to support the army, he had immediately sought the God’s Punishment Witches for help. Since the main task for the “Roland” was to locate the God’s Stone mine, Zooey was the decision maker. The magic core from the underground civilization was, at that time, on the ship, and its giant frame almost occupied the entire deck, so there was not much room for more passengers. Zooey should have declined the request to avoid creating potential safety hazards.

She would have refused to provide assistance had this occurred in the Union age, for back then, the rare magic core had been far more important than mortals. She would choose the magic core over a city without the slightest hesitation, let alone taking refugees. However, now, things were a little different.

After having a brief discussion with her peers, Zooey made a decision that even astonished herself.

She shipped the magic core to another port city and asked the First Army who garrisoned there to look after it. Then she steered the “Roland” back to the Northernmost Port. She had even told the garrison that if she did not return in a timely manner, they should take the responsibility of sending the core back to Neverwinter themselves.

“But it doesn’t feel bad,” Carol said smilingly while shrugging. “To be honest, I thought you would decline the request, and I was torn too.”

“I hope they won’t fail His Majesty,” Zooey said darkly.

What had changed their mind? Zooey searched her memories and remembered the First Army who had fought ferociously against the demons at the ruins of the Holy City, the nurses who had treated her in the hospital, the ordinary people in the Dream World who looked no different than the witches, as well as Roland Wimbledon…

“I hope so. We risked ourselves coming here to this area permeated with the Red Mist,” Carol said as she patted Zooey on the shoulder, and then headed to the bridge. “Anyway, we completed our mission. I want to go back to Neverwinter immediately and have spicy hotpot. Oh, my mouth waters…”

So did Zooey’s.

She heard her stomach protest. Fortunately, Carol shut the gate just at that time and therefore did not hear the noise.

Zooey cleared her mind and gazed upon the sinister Red Mist at the distance.

The Battle of Divine Will that had brought the Union numerous nightmares came once again, much earlier than they had anticipated. The demons had also achieved great progress, but somehow, Zooey felt peaceful.

This time, they were not fighting alone.

Hackzord was suspended above the city he had just occupied.

There was no smoke or ruins of properties. Most buildings remained intact as if the battle had not taken place.

Human beings hardly resisted. They were even weaker than 400 years ago. Had he not trusted Ursrook so much, he would have thought that this was the territory of the enemies in the Sky-sea Realm rather than human beings’.

Within one week, their army had advanced several hundred miles and also built their outpost in the cities not yet permeated with the Red Mist. Hackzord had to attribute the swift operation to the help of the mankind. According to his subordinates, they had only decapitated hundreds of people before the frightened lord and the nobles knuckled under and agreed to provide supplies to them.

It was just like the first Battle of Divine Will.

It appeared that the news that they had burned the Snow Reflection Castle had already been spread out and made a deep impression on other lords.

As more and more cities were conquered, Hackzord gradually received a lot of information from local people. He did not understand why the mankind, who had united together back in the Union age, was again scattered. He did not understand either that why humans’ territory, small as it was, was further divided into four kingdoms that never communicated with each other. The Union that had once dominated the continent was gone.

What had men achieved in the past 400 years?

The four kingdoms were not weak in his opinion, for his best commander had been killed by men.

Did they not know the importance of teamwork?

Yet anyhow, Hackzord was relieved.

He had successfully carried out the plan for the Western Front, although he had experienced some hiccups. He had successfully activated the Birth Tower as the king expected him to.

In a way, he was much more reliable than the boasting “Bloody Conqueror” and the irresponsible Mask. At least, he had fulfilled his promise.

Through a series of Distortion Doors, Hackzord returned to the rupture.

This was the last stronghold on the Land of Dawn, and Hackzord had decided to name this prospective city “Sky” after him. He was sure that this new city would be remembered by the whole clan.

Just at that moment, his guard sent in the update report.

Hackzord quickly skimmed the report through and noticed that a large number of refugees began to flee the Kingdom of Everwinter. He would not have paid it particular notice had those people been regular refugees, for most of them would die on their way.

However, to him, it seemed to be a well-organized, carefully-planned campaign. All the refugees were heading to the Kingdom of Wolfheart in the south by water or land. The troops who attempted to stop them had experienced fierce resistance, which was very similar to what Usrook had mentioned in his letter.

Although several units led by the Upgraded had gained the victory, they had not completely stop the refugees. More troops were needed to stop them. This was also one of the drawbacks to erect the Birth Tower in the mountainous area. Without the Distortion Doors, the Junior Demons and Inferior Demons could not travel to men’s territory by themselves.

Hackzord knitted his brows and asked, “Where’s Nightmare?”

“Her Excellency is still asleep in the Red Mist pond.”

“Damn it. She has been there for more than 10 days. I hope she’s not lost in the Realm of Mind,” thought Hackzord to himself.

Hackzord summoned the Distortion Door and went straight down to the bottom of the rupture.

Valkries still remained in her original position. She was sitting cross-legged in the pond, looking quite relaxed. There was not the faintest sign of her being devoured by the Realm of Mind, except that she had been there for an exceptionally long time.

This indicated that she was still roaming the Sea of Mind.

Had the person in front of him been the Bloody Conqueror, Hackzord would have given him a slap in the face to wake him up. He did not mind that this action would cause damage to the Bloody Conqueror’s memory, but he would not reckless do the same thing to the Nightmare.

Why did she have to pick this time to explore the Realm of Mind!

Hackzord felt a little agitated about those fleeing refugees. Dimly, he was aware that something fishy was going on, but it was hard to explain the situation to the king. The king had dispatched two Senior Lords to the Western Front already, so it was not likely that he would send another one simply to deal with these low lives. The other Senior Lords would definitely laugh at him if he requested for one more. However, the truth was that he had made every effort to conduct this operation, but the Senior Lords could not care less about this mission. The Senior Lords simply acted on their own and provided little help to the battle. Therefore, due to the lack of a reliable Senior Lord at the Western Front to properly command the troops, the army was unable to carry out an expedition.

Had Nightmare assisted him in pursuing those refugees, he would not have run into such an embarrassing and difficult situation.

Hackzord glared at the sleeping Nightmare and finally left the Red Mist Pond.

It seemed that he had to guard the Western Front himself.

Chapter 1245: The Great Immigration

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

At the Sedimentation Bay in the Kingdom of Wolfheart.

White drove his wagon into the busy dock area.

“Ladies and gentlemen, we’ve arrived at our destination. No matter what life you used to lead, you’ll have a brand new life from today onwards. I wish every one of you good luck. It has been a priviledge being of your service! Now, I can offer you one more additional service as a courtesy,” White said as he reined in his horse.

His business had been pretty good recently. After the arrival of the Graycastle ships, he had obtained more business opportunities, especially of short-distance transportation services. Every time he transported residents in the surrounding towns and cities to the port, he could earn around 10 silver royals, and normally, he could do that twice a day. He could have offered another ride at night had he not cared too much about the condition of his wagon. In that case, he would actually earn a little bit more than what he had got back in the church.

Further, the compensation was not paid by the passengers but by the Graycastle men. He only needed to stamp on the traveling document before he proceeded to the sentry post to request for his remuneration. The compensation was based on the number of the passengers he carried, and the Graycastle men had never delayed any payment.

Because of this, many people at the Sedimentation Bay started to provide similar transportation services, including sailors and handymen. Even though a lot of them did not know how to maneuver a carriage, they could ask someone who did to join them. The service was in such a high demand that they did not really need to worry about attracting customers. It was a job that allowed people to earn quick money. The only factor they needed to consider about was the traveling distance, as the farther the towns were, the higher expenses it would incur.

Graycastle men would like to offer help to anyone who was willing to leave the Kingdom of Wolfheart, both rich and poor. Apparently, the King of Graycastle did not really care about money. White thus did not want to lose such a lucrative business opportunity.

Everybody loved money.

White had also heard of the war in the north. There was suddenly a huge influx of refugees in the Kingdom of Wolfheart, so the rumor could possibly be true. Also, Smarty had told him that the lord of the Sedimentation Bay, Baron Jean Bate, transferred a large number of his personal properties to a ship, in an apparent attempt to leave this place. In consideration of these recent events, White also had to find a retreat for himself.

If he could earn a huge sum of money now, he would be able to live a better life in the future.

“What kind of service?” someone asked immediately.

“Some useful experience and kind advice,” White answered as he pointed at the port where a great number of large ships docked. “Look over there. Although everyone wants to leave for Graycastle, not everyone will have a pleasant journey. I had been at the Sedimentation Bay before they came here, so I know a lot. Perhaps, my advice could help you.”

“Then… please tell us…”

“Sure, but you have to pay me. Not much. One silver royal would do.”

White knew poor people did not really care about what kind of situation they were venturing into. They only needed to be fed and clothed. Therefore, he mainly targetted at refugees who had a little bit of savings. They loved to hear little tips and advice. Since White did not charge much, and they did not even pay for the ride, they did not mind buying the information.

Because White used to be that kind of person too.

“Haha, that’s a game that Rats normally play,” a well-dressed man with brown hair sneered. “But this man is obviously not as daring as Rats. One silver royal only. Here you go.”

Soon, the servant beside the man handed White the money.

White smiled stiffly. It appeared that the man was a noble, a diminished noble actually, for he had to now share a wagon with civilians.

“… Here’s my payment,” another young man said hesitantly and produced a silver royal from his pocket.

White waited for a while. It appeared that only two people were willing to pay, but it was better than nothing. He then decided to let the customers go.

Just at that moment, the young man said to the other passengers, “Don’t go just yet. I’ll share the information with you for free.”

“Hey, what did you say?” White stiffened.

“I paid,” the young man swelled up. “I paid for your information, but it doesn’t mean I can’t retell it to someone else. What? Anything wrong here?”

“You—”

“You probably want to bail out, but you won’t benefit anything from it. Even if I share the information to everyone at the port, it won’t affect your future business. However, you’ll lose one silver royal if you choose not to say.”

White’s lips parted. He suddenly did not know how to respond to such a sharp argument.

“You thickhead. You can do whatever you want. Why did you tell him?” the noble protested irritably. “You’re wasting our time.”

“I’m not doing anything wrong. I have nothing to hold back,” the young man said flatly. “I think it’s unfair not to let the coachman know.”

“Fair?” the noble echoed while casting a scornful glance at the young man as he looked at a fool, and then turned to White. “Oi, leave that man alone. I paid you. Are you telling me or not?”

White glared at the young man. He had to amit that the young man was right. “Alright, alright. I’ll say. What bad luck… you guys stay here. I’ll tell you all.”

Then White related the information he knew to his passengers. He told them what kind of people Graycastle men preferred, the departure time of the ships, some details they needed to pay attention to upon registration, as well as the second screening after their arrival. White particularly placed emphasis on the second screening process, for this was the information he had obtained from the soldiers and that the guide of the First Army would not reiterate. According to the Graycastle men, witches would partake in the second screening to detect lies. Once a person misrepresented in his application, he would be labeled as a “dishonest” man, and it would be a lot harder for him to find a decent job.

Apart from that, the noble status would not give them any privilege. On the contrary, people in Graycastle hated those who always boasted about their noble status, so it would be more advisable to keep a low profile. As long as one could read and write, or have a specific skill, he did not need to worry about his life there.

“Thank you for your kind reminders,” the young man said to White as he got off the coach at last. “This did save us a lot of trouble.”

“Bah, don’t mention it. You paid me,” White grumbled and smoked his pipe deeply. “Those people should thank you, but they’re all gone.” “Young man, don’t always try to be nice, especially nowadays… Otherwise, people will take advange of you someday.” ( Updated by NovelFull.Com)

He used to be like that too.

However, he had got nothing for being nice but only a fake leg.

“Perhaps, but this is my duty as a knight.”

“Haha, do you think I’ve never seen a knight? Or are you saying the knight on a book? Forget it. The last time I’ve heard of a knight was when I drank with a Rat in a tavern.”

“Everyone doing it doesn’t mean it’s right.”

“Yes?” White said as he raised his brows. The man looked serious. “Are you a knight?”

“Er… No, I’m not knighted, but my father was, but he…”

White gave the young man a look of comprehension. He now understood that this man had nothing but an ambitious dream. White waved his hand and said, “I’m not interested in your family. By the way… what’s your name?”

The young man immediately raised his head and replied, “Manfeld Castein.”

“OK, Mr. Castein,” White said as he exhaled a pipe of smoke and clambered onto the horseback. “An additional piece of information for you. There’s no knight in Graycastle anymore.”

Chapter 1246: The Ship to the South

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

As White had suggested, Manfeld found that nobody waited for him after the coach departed. He was surrounded by strangers.

However, he did not feel very frustrated about the lack of appreciation because he did that simply because that he thought this was the right thing to do.

Manfeld soon found the registration desk based on the information provided by the coachman. In fact, a banner was hung over that area, which attracted many passers-by.

Although there were lots of people, the registration proceeded in an orderly fashion. Iron bars segmented the crowd, and there formed a huge lineup between the entrance and the registration desk. Refugees were thus directed into a temporary “passage”, along which they shuffled forward slowly.

A Graycastle soldier received Manfeld. All the clerks were wearing the same uniform, so it was easy to distinguish them.

“Name?”

“Manfeld Castein.”

“Identity? Any criminal records? What’s your expertise?”

The inquiry was just as what the coachman had told him. Manfeld answered all the questions truthfully and did not dwell upon his family and background. He was about to talk more about his expertise when the soldier suddenly interrupted him after hearing him say he could read and write. “That’ll do. Trestle No. 6. This is your boarding pass. Don’t lose it. Next.”

Manfeld was immediately pushed out of the queue into the dock area before he realized that the registration was over.

“Well… that’s it?”

So the coachman was right then? One could live a very good life in Graycastle as long as he could read and write. But it appeared that everyone in Graycastle was literate. Manfeld had noticed that while he was waiting, the registration clerks were changing all the time. Sometimes, they would ask a soldier who maintained the order to take their shift temporarily, and nothing had gone wrong.

Manfeld felt very confused.

Also, the boarding pass was a little strange too. It was an iron plate, with a rope attached to one end so that he could actually wear it like a necklace. There was a series of engraved symbols and numbers on the plate. It would not cost much to make such a small plate, but it would be a different story if every refugee had such a plate.

Castein’s family used to own a blacksmith workshop, so he knew what that meant. A blacksmith could use leftover materials to make an iron plate, but he would need tons of materials to make 100 or 1,000 of them. It would only take a blacksmith half a day to engrave those symbols, but it would take a much longer time to repeat the same process over and over again.

However, there were more than 1,000 people at the port.

If this was what happened at the Sedimentation Bay every day, then they would need hundreds of thousands of iron plates! It was unimaginable how many resources and how much time they would need to distribute an iron plate like this to every single refugee. It would probably still not enough even if they summoned all the blacksmith in the Kingdom of Wolfheart.

Manfeld now had glimpse of Graycastle’s immense wealth.

Kingdom of Dawn used to be the wealthiest kingdom on this continent.

Amazed and surprised, Manfeld boarded a three-masted ship.

He was led into a cabin shared by 10 people, which was a lot better than what he had expected. He had thought that he might have to sleep in a warehouse. Manfeld was not sure if this was because he could read and write. Nevertheless, the stinky smell in the cabin was intolerable. Although his family had lost their past glory, he used to, at least, sleep in a comfortable bedroom.

Therefore, Manfeld immediately got out of the cabin and went to the deck to get some fresh air. Just at that moment, he heard someone calling for help.

The voice seemed to be coming from the end of the hallway.

Since not many people were on the ship and the sailors were busy working on the upper deck, the cabin was a little empty. Nobody except him had heard that voice.

Manfeld thus went in the direction that voice came from.

There was a storage room at the end of the hallway, and Manfeld gathered that few people except crew members would come here. He pressed his face onto the door and heard noises inside, as though someone was struggling.

Manfeld soon stepped back and threw himself against the door. The door was flung open.

Manfeld was taken aback by what he saw.

He did not expect to see a familiar face here. The middle-aged noble whom he had met in the coach was standing in the storage room while his two servants were trying to push two ladies down to the ground and tie them up. The ladies were gagged. Inarticulate groans escaped from their lips. Apparently, they were brought here by force.

“Hey, isn’t this the righteous fool on the coach?” the noble drawled. “If I remember correctly, you’re a noble as well, right? I’m Mick Kinley. What about you?”

“Manfeld Castein,” Manfeld pronounced his name for the third time. He noticed that as soon as he announced his name, the hope in the ladies’ eyes faded out, and they also stopped struggling.

“Castein? I’ve never heard of this name,” the middle-aged man said while shrugging. “But you’re lucky. Since you came here, I’ll kindly share the ladies with you, but you’ll have to wait.”

“Release them,” Manfeld said heavily.

“Huh?” Mick Kinley squinted and said, “Are you out of your freaking mind? Do you know who they are? They’re slaves! And God knows how many people have used them. I’m very surprised that I found these two little things on the ship. There’s no reason that their master would let them go. So, now, it’s very simple. They escaped from their master. You still want to save them?”

Escaped slaves were the most inferior slaves, who were not very different from animals. Therefore, nobles could literally do anything to them.

However, Manfeld had his own principles.

“Everyone doing it doesn’t mean it’s right.”

“This ship is heading to Graycastle, right?”

“… What’s your point?” Mick Kinley snarled.

“You should have heard what those Graycasle men said. The Wimbledons has abolished slavery. Therefore, the moment they boarded ship, they were no longer slaves,” Manfeld insisted defiantly. “And don’t you forget that there’s a second screening after we get off the ship. They’ll ask you whether you have criminal records. If I tell you what you did on the ship to these two ladies, do you think Graycastle men would let you go?”

“What are you going to do if I insist?” Mick Kinley said through his clenched teeth.

“You have to beat me first,” Manfeld said as he rolled up his sleeves. “I’m a knight — ”

No sooner had he finished than Mick Kinley threw himself toward him.

It was a quick battle.

Mick Kinley’s servants had apparently also received formal training. Manfeld was soon impaled in the small, narrow storage room. Mick Kinley kicked his bruised face.

“This is all you can do? I thought your swords are as sharp as your words,” Mick Kinley spatted. “Sh*t. Such bad luck! I’ll leave these two sluts to you, but don’t you forget that slaves will always be slaves, no matter where they go! What a fool! Let’s go!”

Mick Kinley slammed the door behind him, and the next moment, the three impaled were left alone in the stuffy storage room.

Chapter 1247: The Heart of A Knight

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

It took Manfeld a while to regain his consciousness.

His vision blurred, and he felt a searing pain through his cheeks. It was pretty hard for him to open his eyes.

Damn it. That brute had broken the unwritten rule that nobles should not hit each other in the face.

He struggled to sit up, slowly shuffled toward the two frightened ladies and ungagged them. “Don’t be afraid. I’ll release you just in a moment.”

The two ladies were too scared to speak, so they simply nodded.

Manfeld untied them after taking a long rest and said, “There you go. You’re free now. Don’t get caught by that person again…”

Manfeld believed that Mick Kinley would not have such a chance. Once everyone got on the ship, he would be under the watch of all the refugees. He did not think Mick would risk himself with so many people around him.

The women set free avoided him gingerly and immediately left the room at a trot. Their footsteps finally died away.

They did not say anything to Manfeld, not even a “thank you”.

Manfeld leaned against the wall and heaved a deep sigh. Somehow, he thought of what White had told him.

“Young man, don’t always try to be nice, especially nowadays… Otherwise, people will take advange of you.”

He shook his head and put these thoughts behind.

He was used to that.

He only hoped that he could return to his cabin before the ship set off so that at least, he could still have a bed.

Suddenly, Manfeld heard patterings of footsteps again, as the floor beneath him started to squeak.

What the hell? He wished it was not Mick Kinley coming back again.

The footsteps stopped abruptly at the door, and he saw a sliver of a woman looking out at him from behind the door.

Momentarily stunned, Manfeld recognized that the woman was one of the ladies he had helped set free.

After the door was pushed open, Manfeld found both two ladies were there. The one behind was carrying an extremely heavy wooden bucket that almost cost all her strength.

She placed the bucket in front of Manfeld. At that moment, Manfeld noticed that the bucket was full of water.

“You… ”

One of the ladies took out a handkerchief and dipped it into the water before she came up to wipe the blood off Manfeld’s face. The other kept apologizing, “S-sorry, it was all our fault. We were too scared to speak, because, because you said… you’re also a noble.”

Manfeld burst into a laugh.

Even though he was so sore, he could not help it.

“Er, what’s the matter?”

“Didn’t I tell you?” Manfeld interrupted the lady. “The moment you boarded this ship, nobles and slaves became equal, because the King of Graycastle not only abolished slavery but also took away nobles’ power. In other words, we’re the same.”

Manfeld actually knew that there was no knight in Graycastle, as merchants from all parts of the world had spread the news throughout the Kingdom of Wolfheart. Most nobles believed that King Roland’s behavior was outrageous, but he was very interested in Wimbledon.

After his family’s fortunes declined, Manfeld had been always thinking about one particular question, that was, what was a knight?

He had never thought about this question when his father had been still alive, as he had believed that he would eventually inherit his father’s title. However, when his family gradually lost their domains to other nobles, Manfeld found that things slowly get out of his control. The new lord did not acklowledge him, and those who were not qualified to manage the land became the ruler. He literally had nothing but a prominent surname.

According to the ancient books he had read, his ancestors who had established on this land had selected the most outstanding person as their king. The king then granted titles to those possessed of exceptional gallantry and valor and asked them to help him protect the land and his subjects. This was the origin of the nobility. A knight, as the noble of the lowest rank, should have compassion and sympathy for civilians. They should be men of honor and help their territories prosper.

Because knight possessed qualities that normal people did not, they were noble.

This was also what kind of person Manfeld wanted to be.

However, he did not see any difference between a knight and civilian after a knight lost his land. What was nobility then? A spirit or a deed?

Lords were replaced constantly as the fierce competition between nobles continued. A limp could be a knight, and a fool could be a knight as well, as long as they had land in their hands. This reality made Manfeld start to question the true nature of knightage.

Although misfortune had weighed upon him, Manfeld had never abandoned his dream.

He had been thinking about traveling to Graycastle for a long time, but he could not afford the trip. Nevertheless, the evacuation of local towns and cities in the Kingdom of Wolfheart provided him with a good opportunity to visit Graycastle.

Manfeld wanted to know whether he could still be a true knight in a country without a noble.

After hearing that “we’re the same”, the two women were profoundly relieved. “Really?”

“All the nobles have received the news. They view Wimbledon as the demon from hell,” Manfeld said as he summoned a bitter smile. “But now, we probably have to seek this horrible demon for help.”

The woman who was wiping Manfeld’s face asked after a moment of silence, “Why did you help us? Aren’t you worried that the noble…”

“He won’t kill me because I already reminded him, “Manfeld replied while shaking his head. “I don’t know what the second screening will look like, but I’ve heard that a witch will be there to detect lies. Even if he doesn’t think abusing you is a crime, he knows he can’t kill a noble.”

Manfeld took a breath and then went on, “By the way, I’m Manfeld Castein. What about you?”

This was the fourth time he had reported his name today.

“I’m Thylane,” one of the ladies said in a low voice. “She’s Momo.” Then she paused for a second and said resolutely, “That noble was right. We were sold to — ” U.p. dated by Novelfull.Com

“I told you that everything changed the moment you got on this ship. Please don’t say that again,” Manfeld said while waving his hand. “Like my coachman said, whatever life you used to live, the new life ahead of us will be completely different. I decided to leave the Kingdom of Wolfheart for a foreign country because of the potential change. Aren’t you the same?”

There was a long whistle.

It was deep and low.

The ship was about to set off.

“Let’s go back. I don’t want anyone to take my bed,” Manfeld said as he rose with some difficulties. He still felt sore, but he managed to walk. “I don’t want to sleep in this storage room all the way there.”

The two ladies exchanged looks. After a moment of hesitation, Thylane produced a white pill from her pocket and handed it to Manfeld.

“This is…”

“A painkiller,” Thylane said. “If you can’t bear the pain, lick it or take a small piece of it. But make sure that you don’t take too much, as it only delays the pain. It can’t stop it.”

Manfeld took the pill in confusion. What an amazing pill this was? It could only delay instead of stopping pain?

Thylane and Momo did not give further explanation. They carried the bucket and withdrew from the storage room

This time, the two ladies stopped at the doorstep and swept a low bow at Manfeld. “Thank you, Mr. Castein.”

Manfeld heaved a deep sigh.

It seemed that not everyone took advantage of others.

This was enough for him.

He studied the pill in his hand for quite a while before he licked it.

It was sweet.

Perhaps, the pill was made of flour, mixed with a little bit of honey.

Manfeld gathered that they had probably stolen the pill from the noble who had bought them.

Just at that moment, something incredible happened.

In an instant, his pain was gone as if he had never been beaten before.

Chapter 1248: The Use of the Core

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

In Neverwinter, Graycastle.

Within a week, the intelligence gathered by the First Army not only confirmed that the Red Mist had appeared to the north of the Kingdom of Everwinter but also provided Roland with a glimpse of the status of the evacuation campaign.

As Edith had predicted, the demons invaded the Kingdom of Everwinter before the Red Mist had completely spread out. They had largely shortened the process of growing a Birth Tower and had started attacking human beings from all directions. The immigration unit of the First Army had already fought the demons. Apparently, the demons had been waiting for this moment for a long time.

According to the report from Iron Axe, the result of the battle was not very optimistic. During the retreat, several units were raided, and the retreat thus turned into a flight. Soldiers were scattered by the frightened refugees. The casualties had mounted up to over 300, which was almost the same as the casualties during the night raid in Taquila. The refugees suffered a even greater loss.

The demons had apparently caught everyone offguard.

The dispersion of the advanced troops of the First Army did expediate the immigration campaign, but it also weakened their fighting capacity at the same time.

Fortunately, Roland had promised the army that no punishment would be inflicted on deserters if the desertion was for the purpose of survival. Therefore, no soldiers had turned into bandits. All of them gradually retreated to the Kingdom of Wolfheart and got in contact with the garrison there.

If those soldiers fled, the army in the north of the Kingdom of Everwinter might be flattened.

Those soldiers who had returned to the army would provide additional support to the local troops as well as important information to the commander.

For example, many units reported that they encountered a type of new Monstrous Beast not seen on the manual.

A unit that had successfully retreated to the Northernmost Port in the Kingdom of Everwinter mentioned that the demon put a new type of Spidery Monstrous Beast into use, which was even harder to deal with than the two well-known Spider demons. Neither mortars nor anti-demon grenades could effectively impale them. Only the 152-caliber Longsong Cannon could cause them damage.

As for the other Monstrous Beasts, Roland currently only obtained a description of their physical appearance. Their abilities remained unknown.

The Monstrous Beasts had apparently upgraded from the war.

The executives thus held several meetings after receiving the intelligence. The ministers had reached an agreement that they should stop the demons from advancing as soon as possible to earn more time for the immigration plan.

The officials had evidently benefited a lot from the rapid increase in the population of Neverwinter as more people joined in the production.

Roland thought so too. Yet unfortunately, this was the fastest he could do. He wanted to send thousands of people to the Kingdom of Wolfheart at once, but first of all, he needed to have enough ammunition.

Therefore, although Roland had already issued the command, it still took a long time for the army to assemble. This was different from the expedition to Taquila. During the expedition to Taquila, the army had advanced along the railway, where they had relied on the Blackriver and Leaf to sustain the logistics. Now, they lacked transportation facilities, so the General Staff had to find an alternative solution.

Roland also noticed another thing in the report.

He noticed that the successful escape of the unit should be attributed to the support of the shallow water gunboats. Meanwhile, the “Roland” arrived in a timely fashion because Zooey and Carol had abandoned the magic core that they treasured the most. This made Roland realize that the ancient witches could possibly use the relic of the underground civilization well in this war.

He thus contacted the three Senior Witches from Taquila directly.

Through the light screen, Pasha, Alethea and Celine’s giant bodies covered in tentacles appeared on the wall.

Roland quickly shared his idea.

“You mean… that we should use the Instrument of Divine Retribution as a power converter?” Celine asked.

“Not only the Instrument of Divine Retribution but also all the magic cores,” Roland said with a nod.

In theory, the magic cores could simulate all kinds of witch power, provided that the ancient witches adjusted the structure of their cyclones. There were four magic cores retrieved from the underground civilization in total, the largest of which was the most special one. Its cyclone was very complicated. According to the deciphered records, it was also the secret weapon that the underground civilization had put great hope in. Because of this, the ancient witches called it the Instrument of the Divine Retribution.

However, only the Chosen One could activate the the Instrument of Divine Retribution, but Roland did not possess magic power. So, for a very long time, this secret weapon had been sitting in the underground hall quietly.

If they could transform the cores into various magic power, it would be much more helpful than letting them just sit here.

The only problem was that the magic cores could not be replicated. Once they lost one, they lost it forever. That was the reason for the rift between the Taquila witches and the Starfall City. Many Union members had even lost their lives for it.

At the early stage of the coalition of the Taquila witches and the First Army, Roland had promised that he would not force the witches to hand over the magic cores. Even though the Taquila witches had now pledged alliance to him, Roland still wanted to first obtain their permission.

Alethea said hesitantly, “Your Majesty, you could do anything with it if you were in the Third Border City. However, I’m worried that you would damage it if you transfer it out of the cave.”

Roland felt very hopeful, as even Alethea, the most stubborn one, demonstrated a sign of approval. He said quickly, “I’ll certainly take caution and handle it with reasonable care. No intruders should be able to destroy it, but I’m afraid that wear and tear as a result of multiple uses will be inevitable. However, it’s better than storing it away.”

Alethea looked toward Celine and said, “How long will it take to transform the Instrument of Divine Retribution into a magic device and restore it?”

“I think… it’ll probably take 10 years,” Celine estimated. “The cyclone is too complicated. If there’s wear and tear, then we’ll probably never be able to restore it. However, I agree with His Majesty…”

“But…”

“Then the magic core can, at least, contribute to the war against the demons,” Pasha rejoined. “Now, we don’t need to look for the Chosen One anymore.”

Alethea lapsed into a long silence before she said, “Alright. Since you all agree, then I have no issues with that either.”

For a split second, Roland saw Celine tap her main tentacle. She said, “See? I persuaded them.”

Obviously, she was only talking to Roland.

Before Roland could respond, Pasha continued, “You should take the witches in the Quest Society more often to the Dream World, Your Majesty.”

Without a doubt, Pasha was bribing him.

Roland was amused.

“So,” Celine said as she put up a straight face, although the original carrier did not actually display emotions anyway. “What kind of power do you want the Instrument of Divine Retribution to transform into?”

Roland had known the answer a long time ago. He replied, “Mystery Moon’s magnetic force. I don’t think it’ll be too complicated, right?”

Celine said with a smile, “Leave it to me, Your Majesty.”

Chapter 1249: Civilization

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The reason was pretty simple. Compared to the summoning type of magic, the attaching magic type was more suitable for the magic core. Take Anna’s Blackfire as an instance. Even if the magic core had the exact same cyclone, it could not release or withdraw the power as freely as Anna. However, for the attaching magic type, they only needed to inject magic power into it to activate the instrument.

Mystery Moon had the ability to convert magnetic force into various types of energy, which would largely benefit Neverwinter.

Dawn I had always been a rare energy resource. Even with the help of Doris, it barely sufficed the need. With the expansion of the industry, they would soon run out of power.

Power generation and transmission was a very complicated science, and it was even more difficult than mechanics. Roland could produce electric motors and lightbulbs by applying what he had learned about electricity in the middle school, but it was impossible for him to build a reliable electrical grid.

He had also brought a lot of books regarding electricity from the Dream World but could hardly understood them. He recognized every single word in the book but did not understand what that meant. Therefore, he abandoned his ambition of learning on his own but put hope in the Taquila witches. Perhaps, in 10 or 20 years’ time, the Taquila witches would play an important role in the electricity industry, but they definitely could not help Neverwinter right now.

As such, his most important task at present became how to increase the production of Dawn I.

Workers in the plants could work at night, and residents could study if there was electricity. The power system, in a sense, could be also viewed as a time device.

Celine believed that there were no technical difficulties, as the original carrier had a far better understanding of magic power than human beings. Ordinary witches could only confirm the magic type and power level by using a Stone of Measuring. However, Celine could picture the cyclone once Mystery Moon demonstrated her ability.

When Roland brought Mystery Moon here, the little girl was, suprisingly, not very cooperative.

She mumbled, “If the magic core replaces me… will you still need me?”

It took Roland quite a long time to persuade her.

Mystery Moon’s condition was that the magic core that simulated her power should be named after her.

Mystery Moon protested, “In that way, you’ll still remember me even if you no longer need my help. Also, as a compensation, can I have two more bottles of Chaos Drinks?”

That was how she was brought here, accompanied by Lily.

It would take a few days to adjust the magic core and design an electrical grid that could transmit power throughout the whole city. Although Roland only used basic knowledge of electricity engineering such as series connections and parallel connection, and tried to simply the calculation as much as possible, the design was pretty much all he could do.

Meanwhile, Neverwinter greeted a group of unexpected visitors.

Rex came to the city with ten members of the Society of Wondrous Crafts and requested to see the King of Graycastle.

Roland soon met this unusual explorer from the Fjords in the parlor.

“I thought you wouldn’t come here anymore.”

Roland asked the servant to bring tea and desserts.

It had been three months since the departure of Rex and his party from Neverwinter. Had they not been continuously shipping the relics from the Southernmost Region, Roland would have probably forgot about them.

Roland studied this group of people attentatively.

All of them were windswept. It appeared that only those who were not used to travel by sea at the Fjords would tend to find another way to make a living.

“I’m sorry, Your Majesty,” Rex said, a little embarrassed. “It took me too long to assemble the members of Society of Wondrous Crafts. Although you’ve already given me the book, still many people question my authority and are not willing to share their research. They thought I’m as crazy as Fan when I told them that there was indeed an artifact that would enable men to fly in the sky.”

“Then what about these people here?”

“They believe you, Your Majesty,” Rex said as he swept a bow. “This time, everyone brought their families here and decided to settle down in Neverwinter. We’ll accept any conditions you offer.”

“Very well,” said Roland as he sipped his tea. “You’ll become residents of Graycastle after the Administrative Office complete the evaluation.” In fact, giving him the book was also another form of screening. People joined the Society of Wondrous Crafts only because they had no alternative way to make a living, so there must be both good and bad members. If they did not have the capability to understand the book, there would be no point in recruiting them.

“What do you mean by evaluation?”

“A standard procedure that you must go through before officially becoming a Graycastle resident. They’ll take down your information. Don’t worry, it’s not a contract or anything.”

Everyone was profoundly relieved. It was obvious that although they had brought their families here, they were still quite uncertain about their future.

Perhaps, he should say something to make them feel more at home.

Roland thus summoned his guard, Sean.

“Your Majesty, what can I do for you?”

“These people are my guests. Show them around and let them get familiar with the new king’s city of Graycastle,” Roland said as he extended out his hands. “Especially the Miracle Building. If they found their new society there, they’ll also need an office on the top floor. So you’d better first let them get an idea what that place looks like.”

“Yes, Your Majesty.”

After the group of confused people left with Sean, Roland said in a low voice in amusement to Nightingale, “You go follow them.”

Two hours later, Nightingale came back to the office.

“How about it? Roland asked and poured her a glass of Chaos Drink.

“I knew it was going to be like that,” Nightingale said as she twitched her lips and drained the glass. “You’re just like a kid showing off your toys. Rest assured. Now, I’m sure they won’t leave even if you ask them to.” U.p.dated by Box n o v e l. com

“You’re wrong. I just want to give them more confidence.”

Nightingale rolled her eyes.

“Ahem, alright. Maybe you’re right.”

“Glad to hear,” Nightingale snapped and shoveled the empty glass under Roland’s nose. “Do you want to hear more about it?”

“Yes,” Roland admitted quickly.

“Then two more bottles of drink.”

As the Miracle Building was the landmark of Neverwinter, one could view half of the city from the roof of the building, including the mining area at the North Slope Mountain enveloped by thick smoke, as well as the Redwater River filled with various different concrete boats. Trains carrying raw materials ran in between, and a little farther on in the south, one could see biplanes flit across the sky. At night, the plants were alive with lights, and the glitters reflected off the surface of the water like shiny stars.

This was exactly what Roland had expected.

For those who had never seen such a scene, the moment they ascended the roof, they met a whole new world.

The spectators would be able to witness the splendid human civilization from there.

Chapter 1250: Anna’s Plan

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Anna was quite amused after hearing Roland’s account of the Society of Wonderous Crafts.

“If those people knew that you created most of the artifacts in the book, they would be astonished,” Roland said casually as he played with Anna’s hair. “They’ll definitely listen to everything you say.”

“We do need some new blood in the Ministry of Industry,” Anna replied with a smile. “But I don’t know how much they can help.”

“They won’t be too bad, as they saw the value of that book,” Roland said while shrugging. He remembered that he had lured the Chief Alchemist to Neverwinter with only a few redox equations back then. “They even brought their families here, which indicates that they’re indeed very curious about those innovations. Given that, I believe they’ll rise to fame once they have that opportunity.”

Roland paused for a second and then went on, “Of course, before they officially join you, they have to learn from the beginning first. I’ll leave it to you. This is also the first step to build up a healthy relationship with your subordinates.”

Anna leaned toward Roland and placed her beautiful head on his chest before she said, “To be honest, I don’t know if I can do this job well…”

“You asked me to appoint you as the Minister of Industy in the first place,” Roland joked. “So, you’re scared and want to bail out now?”

Anna stretched her hand, and a sliver of Blackfire ignited her fingertip. She drew a circle in the midair and said, “Do you want me to tie you up and tickle you with the Blackfire again?”

“Er… I mean, if you don’t know how to do it, just ask Tilly,” Roland said as he averted his eyes. “I’ve heard all the Aerial Knight trainees in the pilot school fear the princess.”

Anna’s face lighted up. She exclaimed in excitement, “Right! I can ask her, but…” she hesitated for a moment and said, “I haven’t talked to her for a while, and I’ve heard since the expedition, she’s been…”

“Don’t worry. She’s fine now. I believe she’s back to normal again,” Roland comforted Anna. “Perhaps, she’ll be extremely happy to see you. You used to give exams together.”

Roland had not told anyone else about the possible resurrection of Ashes because he was afraid that everyone would bet their lives on this battle if they heard Ashes could probably come back to life.

“OK,” Anna said as she nodded resolutely. “I’ll do it!”

Seeing that Anna was no longer annoyed, Roland quickly changed the subject. “By the way, how’s the project of the Cube-powered wheel truck going?”

“I’ll still need a few more days to complete the first sample truck. It’s pretty similar to the Cube-powered car in terms of structure, but it’s easier to operate and also more stable, although it isn’t that flexible.” Anna’s manner immediately tightened into formality once she started talking about work. “Also, I don’t see any problems using it to load and unload cargo, as long as there’s no issue with the road construction.”

“What about the tractor?”

“That I’ll need more time,” Anna said while shaking her head. “The drawing you gave me doesn’t provide many details. I’ll have to figure them out on the go. Its frame and operation systems are also quite different than the wheel truck’s, so it’ll still take me a considerable amount of time to create a usable sample tractor.”

However, they did not have much time left.

The demons would only become even harder to deal with in the future. The army thus urgently needed an armored troop to change the situation. The problem was that there were not many drawings of completed models of this kind of large, ancient automobiles in the textbook for reference. Roland could only find a few drawings of spare parts in the Dream World, and he was not sure whether these parts would fit the model Anna was trying to create.

The industrial technologies in Neverwinter were not yet so advanced as to allow them to directly use modern parts. Both the caterpillar tractor and the armored trucks were consumables. Anna could not make them all by herself.

She had practically nobody to help her.

When the industrialization reached a certain level, each major project would involve hundreds of derivative subprojects. Therefore, it was impossible to sustain the whole industry with only a few learned professionals. This problem would become even more critical as time progressed. For example, Tilly had pointed out the drawbacks of the biplane and also made suggestions to improve it. However, Roland did not have anyone at the moment to work on these issues.

Roland would need an extra 50 years to solve all these problems.

However, the demons would not allow this to happen.

“Let me think it over,” Roland said slowly.

“Roland, I remember you told me that the Dream World has become more and more diverse, right?” Anna said while blinking her lake-blue eyes. It seemed that she had an idea.

“Yes, like it’s now self improving. Thanks to that, I was able to bring new materials here.” According to Lan, this was a sign that the Dream World was expanding. It was now challenging God’s power.

“If that’s the case, why not seek help from the Dream World directly?”

“Are you saying… that we ask more people to look for help?”

“No,” Anna said as she smiled slyly. “I thought of a better way.” She then whispered to Roland and disclosed her plan. “I’m not sure if it’ll work.”

Roland was momentarily stunned. He lapsed into thought, feeling increasingly excited. “This… might work!” he exclaimed.

“You can try it later,” Anna said as she stretched her legs. “If my method works, it’ll make our life a lot easier. But now, stay with me…”

…

When Roland woke up in the Dream World, he already had a wonderful plan.

Anna’s idea was very simple. Since there were no learned professionals in Neverwinter, he could, alternatively, recruit talents in the Dream World. After a long contemplation, Roland decided to found an organization under the pretext of entertainment to recuit antique machinery collectors. He did not think the organization would raise suspicions. In this way, he could provide research and technical support to the real world.

He could even test and improve the completed product in the Dream World.

It would definitely be more effective to found such an organization than conducting research online.

Nevertheless, he would need raise enough capital to start this project.

The income from fighting Fallen Evils was definitely not going to be enough.

Unless someone provided him with great financial assistance.

Roland could only think of one person in this world.

That was Garcia’s father, Garde, a member of the board of director of the Clover Group.

Roland knew that Garde, shrewd as he was, would not easily agree to support him if he directly went to negotiate with him without any preparation. Even though it was just a small amount of money for Garde, he would not invest it for no reason.

Garcia could not help him much with this matter, so he had to think of another plan.

Roland thus picked up the telephone and called the Defender of the Prism City.

Chapter 1251: Partner

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Hello, Mr. Roland,” Rock’s calming voice immediately came from the other end of the line. “I didn’t expect you to call me so early in the morning. Is there an emergency?”

Roland then suddenly realized that it was only 7:00. Feeling a little embarrassed, he faltered, “Er… sorry, did I wake you up? I do have something that needs the Association’s help. It has nothing to do with the Fallen Evils, but it’s important to me.”

“No worries,” Rock said. “Normal people tend to sleep more. However, for me, as an aged Awakened, I’m awake most of the time. What can I do for you?”

Roland had been pretty active recently in the Martialist Association. He had not only managed to kill a great number of Fallen Evils, but more importantly, he usually acted alone. Nevertheless, he killed more Fallen Evils than anyone else except the two teams led by the two Defenders and the team comprised of celebrated martialists led by Fei Yuhan. His outstanding performance encouraged all traditional martialists, which made Roland quite influential among the Association executives.

Of course, Roland did not report all the Fallen Evils he had exterminated. Most of the fallen cores had dissipated and returned to the Dream World. He always took a group of Taquila witches with him when conducting an operation. Therefore, the Fallen Evils were literally defenseless when confronting a group of combat witches with various strange abilities.

Anyhow, Roland soon made his name among the Association members. He could access any facilities in the Martialist Association and was also entitled a telephone that allowed him to directly communicate with the Defenders.

“Before that, I would like to ask you one question first. What’s the relationship between the Prism City and the Clover Group?” Roland remembered that Garcia had once told him that her father had participated in the construction of the Prism City.

“In short, we’re long-term partners,” Rock answered. “Of course, we’ve developed partnership with many corporations, as the operation of the Association requires a large amount of money and resources.”

“In other words, we’re also their big clients?”

“You can put it that way.”

“Very well,” Roland said, and he quickly told Rock what he needed.

Surprisingly, Rock lapsed into a long silence. After quite a while, he said hesitantly, “I have no issue with that, but… why is it important to you?”

“It’s also important to this world,” Roland replied truthfully. Even if Nightingale came to the Dream World, she would not be able to tell whether Roland was lying or not, for the Battle of Divine Will indeed concerned every single person in this world. If the human race was defeated, Roland would die too. By then, the Dream World would also stop working and freeze in an eternity in the Realm of Mind.

“Alright, I see,” Rock conceded. “But anyway, I have to thank you on behalf of the Association. Without you, there would not have been so many young martialists choosing to stay, and our situation would have been even more precarious.”

Roland was somehow a little moved by the Defender’s sincerity when he heard the reply. Although the reason for him to hunt down Fallen Evils was quite different from the Association’s, he did feel that Rock truly appreciated his help. Perhaps, just like Lan had said, for them, this world was real.

Roland had wanted to say, “That’s nothing. It’s my duty”, but for some reason, he changed his mind in the last minute.

“… I’ll protect this world,” he said.

Roland then hung up the telephone and sent Zero off. Although Zero was now awakened, she still needed to go to school. Since Saint Miran, Dido and Ling were all in the same school as Zero, Roland did not worry about Fallen Evils.

After that, he went to the Rose Café.

Since his last meeting with Lan, the coffeeshop had been closed, and the roll-up door had been clamp shut. The only way to access the coffeeshop was through the side door from the warehouse.

It was always busy here.

The witches were currently preparing their breakfast. Roland instantly smelled delicious barbecue as he pushed open the door.

After he had a big breakfast and the witches were all gone, Roland drove out of the apartment building.

The headquarters of the Clover Group was in downtown, so Roland soon arrived there.

Since Roland had told the Association that he would visit here in advance, he was immediately led upstairs before he could reveal his martialist identity. The elevator stopped at the 100th floor, and Roland greeted a bright, spacious office surrounded by large French windows. Now, he had a new understanding of the financial capacity of the Clover Group.

“We met again, Mr. Roland,” Garde said as he came up to Roland and shook his hand. “I didn’t expect that you would elevate yourself from a newbie to such an important figure in the Association so quickly. Young men indeed have great potential!”

Roland was a little surprised at this warm reception. He remembered that last time, Garde had been pretty cold to him even though he had showed him his hunting license.

So it was true that businessmen cared more about a person’s background than his professional competence.

After a little small talk, Roland jumped into the business and asked, “Did the Defender, Rock, tell you the purpose of my trip?”

Garde shook his head and answered, “Mr. Rock only told me that you need some help from the corporation and asked us to assist you as much as we can. But you know that I don’t make the final call in the Clover Group.”

This meant that the Clover Group would proceed with the purchase of the apartment building. Even if Garde agreed to terminate the plan, the Board of Director would not easily approve this motion. Roland smiled. He knew that Garde thought that he had come here for Garcia. In fact, nobody could demolish a building guarded by the witches unless he let them do so.

Roland was also very pleased that the Defender did not tell Garde about his actual plan but leave Roland some room for negotiation. It seemed that the Defender completely trusted Roland, which made Roland like the Association even better.

“It isn’t something too complicated,” Roland said as he spread out his hands. “I want to found a small manufacture plant, or a machinery model factory that aims to design and manufacture some old machineries such as steam engines, old-school tractors, etc… Something nostalgic, like armored trucks and artilleries. Do you understand?”

Garde twitched his lips and asked, “Are you planning to make a movie?”

“You can put it that way, but unlike those fake props, I need real ones, and I also have specific requirements.”

“As far as I know, few people need them nowadays…”

“I’m not going to sell them. I make them just for fun. I don’t need an assembly line or anything, so it saves you money.”

Garde was silent for quite a while. He viewed this business as a complete failure.

“I didn’t know that Mr. Roland had such a peculiar hobby,” Garde said finally. “In other words, you want the Clover Group to help you found a small factory and hire designers and workers?”

Roland suddenly realized that it was not going to be an easy project. Apart from the factory, the designers should have an engineering background, and it would not be that fast to recruit so many professionals even for the Clover Group. Roland thus replied, “Yeah, that’s pretty much about it. Take your time. I’m not in a rush.”

“I need to ask my secretary first,” Garde said as he returned to his desk and picked up the telephone.

15 minutes later, the secretary called back.

Garde turned around and looked at Roland. “Perhaps, there’s a factory that meets your requirement.”

“Well, that was fast!” Roland said in surprise.

“It’s pure luck,” Garde returned modestly, although he looked pretty proud of his corporation. “I can take you there if you don’t have any other plan.”

Chapter 1252: The Design Bureau of Graycastle

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The factory Garde referred to was situated at a construction site in the southern suburb.

Garde offered a ride to Roland, so Roland did not have to drive his battered mini van. In fact, he had a luxurious travel experience.

Roland had to admit that the car seat of Garde’s vehicle was even more comfortable than his couch at home. He also loved the iced champagne in the freezer at the rear. It was such an addictive trip.

Nevertheless, Roland preferred coke to champagne.

Garde drove off the highway and onto a rutted road. At this point, Roland could hear the roars of machineries and see trucks and excavators everywhere.

Above the construction site hung a large banner which read, “Clover Construction Corporation Ltd.”. A little farther on lay serried towering pile foundation.

In response to Roland’s curious look, Garde explained, “The corporation plans to build a modern car dealership for alternative fuel vehicles. Currently, the construction department is responsible for this project. It’ll be later transferred to the manufacture department. It took us a while to get this project approved. We just got the approval a few months ago.”

No wonder Garcia did not really talk about the demolition of the apartment building anymore recently. The Clover Group had temporarily shifted their focus on something else.

“What about the factory?”

“It’ll be demolished,” Garde returned. “It used to be an agricultural machinery plant. Although having gone through several reforms, it eventually failed to keep up with the times. Considering your special request, I’ll save it for you. Although I’m not the superintendent of this project, I’ve already talked to the person responsible for the demolition. He says it’s OK to leave it as it is for now.”

“What about the staff?” Roland asked. He cared more about the recruitment than the venue itself.

“Most of them are gone,” Garde said while shrugging. “Only an old technician who is about to retire and a dozen workers are still working. They belong to my family. Once the car dealership is officially open, they’ll probably switch to their new roles.”

Roland could not help thinking that this plan sounded pretty unreliable, but it was better than nothing. He certainly could not open a design bureau full of top designers and experts at once. This was a good start after all.

When they finally reached the destination, however, Roland’s heart sank further. What came into his view was a dilapidated plant no larger than 500 square meters. The steel plates on the wall were all rusty. The floor was incubated in thick dust. Roland’s spirit was further oppressed by the dust and grit that lay thick on the machine tools. Apparently, the plant had been deserted for a long time.

He followed Garde upstairs and to the manager’s office, from which came the voices of two people.

“Sigh, I don’t know when the corporation will demolish this building. I feel like my butt is covered with mold as I sit here days after days.”

“It isn’t that bad to sit here doing nothing. You won’t get a raise in the new company anyway. Perhaps, you’ll have to work overtime every day. I would rather stay here.”

“What nonsense you’re talking about,” an elderly voice cut across them. “Young men like you should be proactive.”

“Proactivity means nothing… If I could retire now, I would do it immediately.”

“By the way, Master Xie, you’ll be retiring soon, right? I’ve heard that the boss has asked you several times. I believe he wouldn’t say anything even if you stopped coming here now.”

“I like it here… I’ve been working here for nearly 30 years. I would like to stay here as long as I can before it’s torn down.”

“Do you mind me taking some pictures for you?”

“You brat! Photos can’t be the same!”

“Hang on, I just heard someone coming — ”

Then there was a rustling sound coming from behind the door.

By the time Garde’s secretary opened the door, everyone in the room was back to work. Some of them were organizing documents on the desk while others were typing in front of their computers as if they had been busy from the beginning.

“M, Mr. Garde, what wind blew you here?” Everyone was stunned as they saw Garde. Apparently, the boss they had been talking about was not Garde. It somehow reminded Roland of a governmental official who suddenly showed up at a small village unexpected.

“I came to show my friend around,” Garde replied and then cast a look at the eldest worker among all. “You’re Master Xie, right? I’ve heard you’ve been working here for several decades?”

Roland rested his eyes upon this elderly mechanist. He was around 60 years old by his appearance, his hair almost gone, with only a few thin strands of hair clinging to his scalp. A large pair of reading glasses slid off his nose bridge. He looked tiny and withered, with a discolored thermal in his hand. Except for his beedy, glistening eyes, he looked no different than those retired elders in the apartment building.

Perhaps, the only thing that this Master Xie took pride in was his length of service.

“Yes, you’re right, sir,” Master Xie said in a sort of unctuous tone as he massaged his thermal a little restlessly. “I’ve been working in the plant for 29 years, 29 years precisely.”

Roland’s heart sank to the bottom. Master Xie did not seem very reliable or professional to him. A real master, in his opinion, should be conceited and proud. He was now thinking about recruiting people online.

“You did a great job,” Garde said smilingly. “My young friend is actually interested in taking over this plant. Show him around and give him a basic idea of this factory.”

“Al-alright,” Master Xie stammered as he gave Roland a surprised look. “But isn’t the plant going to be…”

“If he likes it here, we can leave the plant open.”

Roland immediately sensed Master Xie’s burning gaze.

“How can I address you, sir?”

“Just Roland.”

“OK, Mr. Roland, please follow me!”

Master Xie took Roland down to the plant in great excitement. He was about to introduce the long history of the plant when Roland suddenly interrupted him, “Compared to that, I’m more interested in what you did in the past?”

“I did pretty much everything…” Master Xie said with a smile. “I was a fitter at first, and then I was promoted to workshop supervisor. Later, I became the assistant director of the plant. I had to take three or four people’s shifts when it was busy. During the day, I supervised the assembly line, and at night, I taught young workers how to repair machineries. Gradually, my eyesight got worse, so I stopped working at the front.”

Roland stopped and asked, “Do you have designing experience?”

Yes, naturally. Although I didn’t go to college, I learned a lot by myself. The plant used to have night school. But pencils and rulers are, after all, incomparable to computers. After the corporation founded a design department, nobody these days look at those drawings anymore.”

“If I want a caterpillar tractor that is very different from what’s available on the market, are you able to create one?”

“A tractor? Haha, I’m too familiar with it. I’m not boasting, Mr. Roland. I can make one with my eyes shut as long as you provide me with a few apprentices to assist me.”

Roland asked in surprise, “Why didn’t the Clover Group assign you to the design department then?”

“They design on computers now. I’ve heard that everything in the new plant is automatic. Robotic arms and robots do the majority of the work. The staff members in the old plant all went to sales and administration. I can’t do anything there even if they recruited me.”

There was a hint of melancholy in Master Xie’s voice.

However, Roland had now completely changed his previous opinion on this old worker.

Who cared that he looked ordinary? An ordinary worker like Master Xie knew exactly how to keep a low profile.

What did it matter that he looked a little too homely? A modest team leader was easier to manage.

It was totally fine that he did not know about computers. In this way, Roland could hire a bunch of cheap designers.

“Very well, very well,” Roland said while nodding vigorously. His lips curled up into a satisfied smile.

“Huh?” Master Xie was utterly bewildered and did not understand why Roland said that.

“The plant will remain open,” Roland said flatly. “I’ll transform it into a new design bureau, and you’ll be my chief designer.”

“A design… bureau?”

“That’s right,” Roland said as he extended out his hand. “Welcome to the Design Bureau of Graycastle.”

Chapter 1253: Things of A Wrong Age

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Um… Mr. Roland,” Master said after a firm handshake. “What’s that Design Bureau for?”

“To make everything I want you to make,” Roland answered smilingly. “For example, right now, I want you to make a brand new tractor. It must be easy to operate and manufacture, also with a great potential for future modification.”

“There should have been a lot of tractors like that on the market…”

“I certainly expect more than that. What I just mentioned is just a basic idea,” Roland said while shaking his head. “First of all, except for the engine, you must make everything else by yourselves.”

“Then it’ll cost a lot,” Master said while clicking his tongue.

“I don’t need a lot of them. It should be around the same price as those handicrafts. I have a few collector friends who’re willing to spend money on them.”

“I see…”

“Also, no automatic machine tools should be used during the manufacture process. Well…” Roland paused at these words and surveyed the surroundings. “The tools currently used in the plant look fine to me. I need the size and the manufacture method of each spare part. In other words, the Design Bureau should not only make them but also draw the floor plan for the assembly line.”

Seeing Master Xie look a little worried, Roland added, “Of course, I’ll recruit some students to assist you. You only need to give them work to do.”

“OK then… It’ll probably take more than half a year to complete the project with just pencils and paper.”

“The last thing that I’m going to tell you now is the most important one,” Roland went on. “You must have creativity.”

Momentarily stunned, Master Xie asked, “I’m sorry?”

“For example, the tractor that I want you to make is powered by steam. Therefore, technically, we need a large boiler to store fuels and water. However, in reality, there are no such parts, so you should imagine that it’s powered by nuclear energies, like those in movies.”

“…” Master Xie was now totally speechless and astounded.

“Given that, you must minimize the impact of those ‘non-existent parts’ when you make the model. Only in that way can we collect reliable data during the test. Do you understand what I’m saying?”

“Er…” Master Xie thought for a while before he asked gingerly. “You mean that we should imagine it as something that doesn’t belong to this era?”

“Exactly,” Roland said, grinning. “Do you have any technical difficulties?”

“In theory, no, but…” he said hesitantly. “But to tell you the truth, you probably can’t really use it even if we successfully produce such a machine.”

“That’s exactly what I need. My collector friends don’t really want them to have practical values.”

Profoundly relieved, Master Xie then asked, “Well… Mr. Roland, what about the salary of the chief designer?”

“Twice your pension,” Roland replied with a smile.

After Roland returned to the Garde’s car, Garde put down his wine glass and shrugged. “So, what do you think?”

“Pretty good. I just don’t know how to calculate the expenses of a factory…” Roland said courteously.

“Forget about those trivial matters. It’s an honor that we Clover Group could help the Martialist Association,” Garde said while waving his hand. “I’ll talk to the other executives regarding this project later. From now on, you’re their new boss.”

It was not hard to leave a factory that was going to be demolished open, as the land and the property still belonged to the Clover Group. All the corporation needed to provide was the salaries of the workers and the expenses for the maintenance of the old machineries. It was obviously a very good deal for the Clover Group, for they earned the trust of the Defender of the Prism City at a minimal cost.

Had Roland conducted the project all by himself, he would have needed to spend hundreds of thousands of dollars, and there was no guarantee that he would succeed.

Having said that, Roland did not want to miss a single opportunity of using the Clover Group.

“Is it really OK? I think we need to at least recruit more people to ensure the smooth operation of the plant. To increase productivity, we also need to work out a reward system, and that’ll cost a lot of money.”

“Hmm…” Garde pondered for a while and said, “I’ll send a person to help you with the finance. If there’s any extra expense, just let her know. But Mr. Roland, you know the Clover Group won’t approve if you request too much…”

“I understand that you’re not the only person who makes the decision. Don’t worry, I know what I’m doing. Thank you for your help.” Sending a finance personnel was also an effective way to minimize risks while also keeping an eye on his spending.

“That’s nothing.”

They clanked the wine glasses.

Three days later, the agricultural machinery plant became the Design Bureau of Graycastle. Although it looked as desolate as ever, the workers in there were quite enthusiastic about their new job after being promised they they would get promoted and have a raise.

Roland instantly felt a lot relieved after this matter had been settled. He could not help smiling when he thought of the prospective expansion and the grand future of the Design Bureau of Graycastle. Even his work had become more enjoyable.

With the help of the Design Bureau, Anna did not neccessarily have to work day and night. She could, instead, put more of her efforts into inventions that she enjoyed much better. Overall, the project brought a lot of benefits.

The workers in the Bureau would probably never know that their drawings would one day turn into reality in the other world and become weapons used to perpetuate the glory of the mankind in the bitter war against a foreign race.

“What are you laughing at, Your Majesty?” Nightingale asked as she revealed herself and cast him a despicable look. “Having fun last night? I hope you didn’t do anything improper in the dream.”

“How come? Do I look like that kind of person?”

Nightingale twitched her lips and said, “It’s very understandable. Phyllis told me that the ancient witches don’t really care about it. They view it as something just as normal as sleeping and eating.”

“… Did she?”

“No, I’m teasing,” Nightingale said while squinting at Roland. “So, you were thinking about that, were you?”

Apparently, this was one of Nightingale’s trap.

“I’m impressed with your imagination,” Roland said sarcastically as he stared at her. “I’m happy because I solved a big problem. It’s not what you’re thinking.”

“Hmm, I detect that it’s 95% true. I take it as you’re telling the truth,” Nightingale said while spreading out her hands.

“Wow, you can round it up to a specific percentage now?”

“Yes, probably because I use my ability more often, I feel my sense become sharper.”

“Then what about the left 5%? Just a disclaimer, I didn’t lie.”

“Perhaps, you aren’t that certain subconsciously,” Nightingale sneered.

Roland was speechless. He had a feeling that he would eventually fall into Nightingale’s trap if he continued with this conversation.

“By the way,” Nightingale went on after she ate a piece of dried fish. “You haven’t been staring at the Bloody Moon recently.”

“That’s right…” Roland said and suddenly realized that he had not looked up at the sky for a long time. The crimson sphere was still suspended in midair, completely stationary however he looked at it. “Probably because I know that it’s just a hollow of nothingness.”

Just then, the telephone on his desk rang.

It was from the Administrative Office.

“Barov? What’s the matter?” Roland said after he picked up the receiver.

“Your Majesty, the increase in the immigrants exceeds our expection,” Barov complained over the telephone. “If things go on like that, we won’t have much money left in the treasury!”

Chapter 1254: A Currency Reform

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Roland passed through a few heavily guarded gates and entered the treasury in the castle district.

Back when he had still been in the Border Town, he had only had a few cases of gold royals that were sufficient to maintain the operation of the small town. Since the sale of the steam engines and other magical artifacts, his revenues had increased rapidly and soon reached a peak.

With the expansion of his territory, the expenses incurred also increased correspondingly. For the convenience of the Administrative Office, a treasury was built between the castle and the Administrative Office. Although it has heavily guarded, all the directors had access to it as long as they followed an appropriate procedure. This decision had indeed sparked a heated discussion in the beginning. It was unprecedented that a noble spent all his money on the expansion of his territory, let alone allowing other people to access it.

At that time, nobody except Barov had known that Roland did not give a damn about his treasures. All he had cared about was the urbanization of the city. For a very long time, the revenues in Neverwinter had been greater than the expenses. Barov had not had a financial issue for quite a while.

“Your Majesty,” Barov, who had been waiting in the treasury, said respectfully. “You see, we only have 12 cases of gold royals left.”

Normally, there were around 2,000 gold royals in a case, which meant that they currently only had 20,000 gold royals in total. The treasury now looked pretty empty compared to the past.

Although there were mounds of silver royals and bronze royals, they were not worth much.

“How long will they last?” Roland asked.

“Based on the current situation, two months at most.”

“It’s faster than I thought,” Roland commented as he raised his brows. “Are most of the spendings on the payrolls?”

“Yes. The payroll expenses take up more than half of the total expenses. As the population grows too fast, there’s a big increase in the payroll of the construction team and the welding unit. Plus, we have to pay the Chambers of Commerce from the Fjords 4,000 to 5,000 gold royals every month. If we stop this payment, the Administrative Office will be able to manage until we receive the profit of the sale from the Joint Chamber of Commerce — ”

“We need people,” Roland cut across Barov.

“Then…” Barov said as he massaged his hands nervously. “I remember you said in the last meeting that there was a permanent solution. Is it true?”

“You still remember,” Roland said smilingly as he surveyed the treasury. He had anticipated that this day would come. The treasury was quite spacious and bright. It would be almost the same as an ordinary residence if without the iron bars and the shelves. Therefore, it would be a perfect place to produce notes. “When’s the next payroll due?”

“In a week.”

“Store away these gold royals. We don’t need them for the time being,” Roland said while nodding. “Come with me to my office. I need to found a new department, and I’ll discuss the details with you when we get there.”

Although it was a little earlier than Roland had expected, Roland had started preparing for this day half a year ago. He had actually conducted a pilot project by distributing notes to the Witch Union and the Sleeping Spell. The result showed that the witches had no way to forge those testing notes, which indicated that it was now time to replace metal currencies with paper currencies. He could put them into use anytime.

“Yes, Your Majesty,” Barov responded. It was obvious that this old governor feared that he would sink into poverty again. After receiving the confirmation, his face lighted up, all the wrinkles around the corner of his eyes smoothened. “By the way, Your Majesty, what’s the name of this new department?”

“Bank,” Roland replied.

Five days later, a new notice posted on the bulletin at the central square in Neverwinter created an uproar among the public. The Administrative Office, very surprisingly, sent a person to further explain the notice, which was very rare after the implementation of universal education.

The notice also made the headline on the Graycastle Weekly. According to the notice, the king was going to distribute a new type of currency to replace gold royals, silver royals and bronze royals.

For the next couple of days, everyone in the kingdom was discussing this currency reform.

So were the customers in the hotel where Victor stayed.

Victor had planned to return to the Port of Clearwater after the magic movie. However, the appearance of the Bloody Moon disrupted his original plan. Due to disorder and the unstable situation, he immediately changed his plan and decided to stay in Neverwinter for a while. He made this decision not out of his loyalty to the king but because he believed that it would be only worse in other cities. Since the Bloody Moon represented the end of the world, the safest place on this continent would be Neverwinter.

Peace was soon restored after the king and the queen came to sooth the masses. With the the police and the garrison cracking down criminals, order was quickly re-established. Victor, as the witness to the incident at the movie theater, was summoned by the police several times for investigation purposes. When he was about to leave the soft arms of his maid and head back to the south, he heard the news of the currency reform.

The shock brought about by this new policy was far greater than that by the Bloody Moon.

The king was going to abolish the currency system that had been in use since the foundation of the four kingdoms!

As a businessman, Victor had not believed it when he had first heard the news. He had thought that they were delirious ramblings of some drunkards. Gold was the most precious metal throughout the four kingdoms as well as foreign countries. How could the king abolish the currency system all of a sudden?

Nevertheless, he later confirmed the validity of the information after reading the newspaper brought in by the maid. The rumors circulated among various taverns and pubs also further confirmed the news.

The first reform policy was that “All the old currencies shall be replaced by the new currencies. It is mandatory to use the new currencies to conduct transactions in accordance with their face values”.

This meant that the king could use a piece of paper to purchase all the goods brought into Neverwinter, which was pretty much like robbery.

“I saw many people flee the city with their cargo when I came back,” Twinkle, who was lying on her stomach on the bed, said apprehensively. Victor was not sure if she was worried that he would leave the city like everyone else or about the Rainbow Stone clothes.

Victor managed a bitter smile. Twinkle did not know that his fortunes had been closely tied to the King of Graycastle. Without Miss Leaf providing him with the seeds, he would not be able to expand his brand.

Whatever happened next, Victor would not abandon the business in Neverwinter easily.

He knew Roland Wimbledon would soon implement this policy throughout the whole nation.

The king himself was an excellent businessman with an acute business sense. He had no reason to rob people at the moment to maintain the status quo. At this thought, Victor calmed himself down and read on.

The second and third policies concerned the livelihood of the community.

“All the salaries in Neverwinter will be paid in the new currencies.”

“All the transactions in the Administrative Office and the Convenience Market, including but not limited to food and real estates, shall be carried out through the new currencies.”

The fourth policy was regarding the number of paper notes distributed to the public.

“The Administrative Office will offer a long-term currency exchange service that enables residents to exchange their old currencies, namely, gold royals, silver royals and bronze royals, for the new currencies, and vice versa. The Administrative Office will charge a 5% transaction fee for each transaction when residents exchange the new currencies for the old ones.”

Victor saw the underlying implication behind this policy.

It seemed that this policy was made to force foreign merchants to use the new currencies.

“Also, the transaction fee could be waived for merchants who have permission from the Administrative Office to run business and who have submitted the application for same.”

Chapter 1255: Graycastle “Yuan”

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Below the policy was a sample application form.

Applicants not only had to provide their personal information but also their transaction records. Victor skimmed the application form through for several times, and suddenly, the truth flashed across his mind.

He finally understood the purpose of the new policies as his eyes shoveled between the fourth and fifth articles. It gradually dawned on him that the king’s true intention of making these two rules was to increase tax revenues!

Like most major cities, merchants in Neverwinter had the obligation to pay commercial taxes. However, the problem was that not every merchant abode the rule. Victor never missed a single payment, but tax evasion was actually very common among merchants. He was indeed one of the fews who paid the taxes every time.

Merchants who had real estate properties would, more or less, pay taxes partially, but those who leased the premises and traveling merchants almost never paid. Without the previous patrol team who had constantly blackmailed merchants, Neverwinter provided small business owners with a perfect, and even better tax-free zone than Valencia and Eagle City. Because of the great business environment, businesses had soon flourished in the new king’s city within a very short period of time.

But now, everything was about to change.

The application could waive the currency exchange transaction fee, but applicants would also need to provide their sources of revenues. Then the Administrative Office would deduct taxes from their earnings based on the information on the application form.

Was there no other way to evade taxes?

There certainly was. Merchants could exchange the new currencies for gold royals and sell their items bought from Neverwinter somewhere else to make up the loss.

But this was not a guaranteed solution.

Nobody could assure that the revenues would be exactly the same as the expenses. To maintain the business, one should possess more new currencies than the old ones. The only way to achieve this goal was to either exchange new currencies for gold royals or reserve the gold royals for the future.

As time progressed, merchants would, inevitably, have a certain amount of new currencies and realize that they were easier to use and carry. Gradually, merchants would exchange new currencies among themselves. They would probably exchange gold royals at first and then slowly, directly use them to purchase goods.

This meant that no matter which way merchants chose to go, Neverwinter would always benefit from them!

What was clever about this policy was that it did not really prejudice the interests of merchants. In fact, it was quite considerate of merchants’ feelings.

The declaration could increase the municipal tax revenues and thereby create a better business environment. On the other hand, legal business owners actually benefited from this policy as well.

For merchants who chose to use the new currencies, there would not be much difference. They could still evade taxes and press others to also use the new currencies. Since all transactions in Neverwinter should be conducted via the new currencies, the new currencies would gradually replace gold royals and spread out to the territories beyond the jurisdiction of the King of Graycastle!

Victor also noticed that the whole currency reform, as a matter of fact, aimed to take things slow and give people time to get used to the change.

Without a doubt, the new currencies would be legally effective as long as the King of Graycastle took control of food in his domain, not only because of the implementation of the currency policies but also because Neverwinter itself was a large market.

Merchants who fled the city might not even have truly thought about the policy. It was pretty shortsighted of them to abandon such a lucrative market simply because of the currency reform.

Victor used to think that the reform was ludicrous, but now it appeared that it was not as bad as he had thought. As long as King Roland Wimbledon guided the country properly and take appropriate steps, this reform might be a great success.

Victor shuddered involuntarily.

The currency reform was just the beginning.

Once everyone gladly accepted the new currencies, the king would immediately gain immense wealth that no business could ever bring.

The nobles who were so good at business in Kingdom of Dawn would probably drop their jaws.

The only problem right now was whether someone would forge the new currencies created by His Majesty.

Victor thus asked Twinkle to purchase some paper notes from local residents at a price five times the normal price on the payday two days later.

He soon found that his fear was unnecessary after he saw the actual notes.

“These notes are… so beautiful,” Twinkle exclaimed as she toyed with a brand new note.

“True,” Victor agreed. The new currency looked quite expensive, which was very different from what he had thought. It was soft and durable. Obviously, it was not made of ordinary paper.

The most peculiar part was its pattern on the face.

There were six kinds of paper notes in total, their face values ranging from 10 to 1,000. The largest value was equal to a gold royal, and one could easily tell from the golden pattern on it. The face values of the rest of the paper notes were 10, 20, 50, 100 and 500 each. A new currency unit “Yuan” was used. The colors and patterns of the paper notes varied according to their respective face values. For example, the 1,000 note was printed with the image of the king and the queen. Below printed a line that read “Royal Bank of Graycastle”. Although the font was tiny, it was pretty visible to read.

Victor drew the notes closer and discovered that the texts and the images on the notes were all comprised of tiny stripes even thinner than hairs. Each stripe was clear and separate from each other, so it was impossible to forge the notes.

Victor studied the other notes. The ￥500 note was printed with the image of the Witch Union and the ￥100 plants and workers. The other notes were printed with the Miracle Building, trains, etc. All the notes were printed with the coat of arms of the Graycastle royal family that featured a high tower and two spears on the back. Victor curled up his lips. It was evident that the notes were carefully designed and well made like artwork. Even if they did not have any practical values, Victor was sure that many collectors at the Fjords would be willing to collect them purely for their aesthetic values.

This was indeed a very clever strategy. The colorful notes definitely cost a lot, but in a way, they built confidence among the public. Nobody would have believed a piece of paper could replace gold royals. However, if this paper resembled a piece of art, then people would have more confidence in them, although essentially, they were the same thing.

Victor put down the notes and heaved a deep sigh.

“What’s the matter?” Twinkle asked curiously.

“There will be a drastic change in the business world soon,” Victor replied in a low voice.

Chapter 1256: Reception and the New Plan

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“How’s the currency exchange going?”

Three days after the release of the new currencies, Roland held a director meeting in the castle boardroom to discuss the response of the public to the currency reform.

Roland had learned from the history that it was extremely hard to foundamentally change the conception of money and break the tradition that had been observed over the past thousand years. A tiny error might result in an avalanche of disasters. The failure of the currency reform would possibly jeopardize the public’s confidence in the Administrative Office and even the king himself, which had taken Roland so long to build.

“Fewer people exchange the currencies then we expected, Your Majesty,” Barov said, looking pretty relaxed. “The transaction amount over the past three days is 1,000 gold royals. Considering there will be a lot of changes at the beginning of the reform, we could use the gold royals in the treasury for the time being before everything is stablized.”

To avoid a bank run, the amount of bank notes printed this time would be equal to the payroll expenses this month. Therefore, even if they were all replaced by gold royals, they would still have two months to print new notes. However, if that happened, it would mean that the reform had failed.

“I think your worry is unnecessary, Your Majesty,” Barov said smilngly as he stroke his beard. “Most of the subjects would not choose to use new currencies in exchange for old ones, unless it’s absolutely necessary. They don’t want to pay the transaction fee.”

“But it doesn’t mean that people accept the new currencies,” the Minister of Agriculture, Sirius Daly, replied cautiously. “I notice that the sale of food has increased a lot recently in the Convenience Market, including the sale of spice and dried food.”

Roland was a little taken aback by the unexpected increase.

He then smiled and came to the realization that the subjects did not want to pay the transaction fee, so they purchased a great number of life necessities as a backup. In fact, food had once been used as a universal equivalent in the history. Dried food and spices had a long shelf life, so naturally people would buy them in bulk to prepare for any future emergencies.

Roland somehow thought of an advertisement which said, “Paper for food. Nothing to lose. What are you waiting for?”

But Roland was relieved.

People were not likely accept the change within a few days. The increase in the sale of goods did not really affect the Administrative Office. There were sufficient wheat, eggs and cheese for the entire Western Region. By the time the Administrative Office received the part of sales profit they were entitled to from the Joint Chamber of Commerce, he would be able to know the result of the currency reform.

Roland thus said to Sirius, “That’s fine. Let them buy as much as they like, but you have to keep an eye on them and make sure there’s no shortage of food. As long as residents don’t exceed their personal limit, they can buy whatever they want.”

The Convenience Market mainly supplied life necessities. It was a store directly controlled and supervised by the government. Residents had to show their identity cards to make the purchase. It was highly unlikely that the city would run out of food, provided that no merchants interfered with the market.

“Yes, Your Majesty!”

“By the way, what’s merchants’ reaction?”

Barov replied quickly, “Your Majesty, the merchants in Neverwinter are roughly divided into two groups. Traveling merchants are on the fence about it. Many stores are shut down. Do you think we should…” he broke off and made a gesture that suggested driving those merchants out of the country.

Roland shook his head. It appeared that many business owners resisted the new currencies by closing their shops. He said, “Let them be as long as they don’t break the law. Their lease has not expired yet anyway. It’s up to them to decide whether they should continue with the business. What about the other group?”

“There was not much feedback from the big Chambers of Commerce at the Fjords. Many are still running their businesses. They asked whether they could use the new currencies to purchase steam engines and paddle steamers. I gave them an affirmative answer as you instructed.”

A flurry of whispers swept over the boardroom.

Apparently, everyone was surprised at this reaction. They were mortified to see that foreign merchants gave more support to the king’s policy than domestic tradesmen.

Roland did not really mind that, however.

It seemed the Fjords people were more willing to accept new things. For example, Margaret was the first person who had shown an interest in the steam engines and provided financial assistance for the industrialization of the Border Town.

“There’s an exception though,” Barov said on a cough. “A clothing store named Rainbow Stone remains open. The owner even put up a banner celebrating the currency reform and offers discounts. I’ve heard that residents lined up to buy their clothes.”

Roland blinked and chuckled. He knew that was Victor Lothar who had requested to collaborate with Leaf.

Was it just a bold action or he actually understood the importance of the currency reform?

“Very well,” Roland said as he looked toward the Minister of Publicity, Honey. “Make a report of that. Trust is now more important than gold.”

“Got it,” Honey said with a nod.

“That’s right, trust is more important than gold, Your Majesty,” Edith, who had been silent, suddenly spoke. “Please beware of upcoming rumors. I believe it’ll be not long before we hear them.”

“What do you mean?” Barov asked, frowning. “Is there going to be someone attempting to subotage the currency reform?”

“That’s very normal. Everything has two sides. Merchants who don’t like the paper notes or who simply want to destabilize the government would spread rumors. Do you really think the nobles would submit to His Majesty’s ruling in just two years?”

“Er…” Barov was at a loss for words.

They certainly would not. In fact, they were just bidding their time to overturn his sovereign.

They did not care whether the demons had invaded the city or not.

“Don’t worry. Honey and Summer will look after it.”

“Also, the mining area in the Western Region always needs people,” a cold voice said in the boardroom. Although nobody new who said it, everyone could tell the person was serious.

Roland surveyed the room and said, “Alright, this is just the beginning. I believe the new currencies will be spread out throughout the whole nation in a few months and replace gold royals. It’s very important to the Battle of Divine Will. Everyone must keep working on it!”

“As you command!” everyone chorused.

“Your Majesty,” Barov said hesitantly, “Can we print so many notes within a few months?”

“The amount currently available is just enough to pay out salaries, but we can definitely print more. You don’t have to worry about it,” Roland returned.

Although a note was just a piece of paper, it contained the most advanced technologies in Neverwinter. Considering there was a huge number of gold royals and silver royals that had been accumulated over the past thousands of years, Roland was not going to ask Soraya to take the workload all alone. The pulp used to make bills was mixed with a certain amount of rubber worms’ slimes to enhance the durability of the finished products.

The number on the face of the note was actually pre-printed on foils and served as an anti-counterfeiting mark. Only Neverwinter could produce extremely thin foil paper.

A new rolling press machine was used to print notes, and the ink used for printing was jointly produced by Darkcloud and Broken Sword. The color was very pigmented and long-lasting, much better than the pigments extracted from plants and minerals. Roland believed that they could last for a very long time before the next printing.

Overall, a large part of the manufacture process was completed by ordinary people, whereby the witches only provided raw materials. The production was highly efficient, which made mass production possible.

Roland was relieved that he finally carried out this currency reform. Now, he had both men and money, so the problem next was how to utilize these resources and increase productivity.

“I have a new project that requires approximately 20,000 to 30,000 people, which is about the population of a major city,” Roland said to Barov. “You and the other directors shall work together and draft a plan.”

“Yes, Your Majesty.”

“First of all, the Ministry of Chemical Industry — ” Roland broke off and looked at Kyle Sichi.

Apparently, it was time to produce more ammunition.

Chapter 1257: A National Machine

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“I need an additional ammonia plant and a saltpeter plant. You knew that, didn’t you?” Roland asked.

Agatha and Paper had been working on these two materials, but the production rate was not satisfactory due to the lack of catalysts. Although their method was much better than the original acid-making method that involved saltpeter, they could not further increase the production as a result of limited manpower and magic.

After Roland obtained a copy of the complete periodic table of elements, the chemistry laboratory immediately started to make sample elements. With Lucia’s help, the Ministry of Chemical Industry was now able to create a sample for every element on the table, including many rare elements such as platinum and rhodium that were normally used as catalysts in chemical reactions.

As long as there were enough people, they could build as many plants as they wanted. Mass production might not be the most efficient way to produce war materials, but the original acid-making method was solely reliant on Agatha’s and Paper’s abilities.

Kyle said slowly, “Your Majesty, we’ve already verified the theories through experiments and simulated the acid-making process in a small reaction vessel. As long as we have sufficient manpower, we can start working anytime.”

“I can offer you all the literate immigrants. You can start after this meeting,” Roland said. “Also, I plan to create a new production line for lead-acid batteries.”

Kyle nodded in comprehension. Perhaps, not many people knew what those things were, but he had learned elementary and intermediate chemistry by heart and certainly understood what Roland was talking about.

Lead-acid batteries were also known as storage batteries. It was not even that hard for the Alchemist Workshop to make them, since the only materials required were lead, lead dioxide, and dilute sulfuric acidm, let alone the current Ministry of Chemical Industry. Plus, the experiment on electrolytes with a light bulb was a classic experiment in high school chemistry.

The strength of storage batteries was that they could be recharged by supplying water regularly. There was no technical difficulty whatsoever in producing lead and lead dioxide. The reasons that he had not produced them earlier were that they rarely needed storage batteries and had insufficient manpower.

“How many do you need approximately…” Kyle asked as he produced a notebook.

“Around 100 per month,” Roland replied.

Storage batteries would be mainly used to start off piston engines for the biplanes. As the biplane was the most advanced industrial product in Neverwinter, it was unacceptable that it took so long for the plane to take off. Roland attributed this drawback to the lack of manpower. However, with the influx of a great number of immigrants, they could now eliminate this defect.

With so many additional people, they could literally do whatever they wanted.

“We would only need around 10 people to finish this small project,” Kyle commented sagely as he stroked his beard. “Of course, we still need Queen Anna’s help to manufacture other parts like lead plates and shells.”

“If you could provide me with detailed drawings, the Ministry of Industry has no issue with that,” Anna said while nodding.

“Then please give me a few days to think it over, and I’ll send you the drawings shortly.”

Roland sipped his tea in satisfaction. After years of education and training, there were now many talented people in the Administrative Office. It was very common that a project involved various departments. For many projects, Roland only had to provide his advice here and there in the very beginning, and his ministers would finish the rest.

“Now, the Ministry of Industry shall — ”

After the war of Taquila, Roland realized that there were a lot of things that needed to be improved. Now, he finally got an opportunity to do so.

First was the fighting capacity of the infantries.

Roland called it the “General Purpose Machine Gun Plan”.

The basic idea was to produce a lighter version of Mark I type HMG with a simpler structure. The barrel and rack should be separate so that the weapon could be more portable. A cartridge should be used to enable soldiers to open fire immediately in the event of an attack. In that case, soldiers would be able to suppress the Senior Demons and earn time for the anti-demon grenade unit.

Since there would not be much change in the gun structure, the only way to reduce the weight would be switching over to a lighter material, aluminium alloy and plastic made from the slimes of rubber worms, for instance. Both of the two materials were not manufactured on a large scale, but the production of the biplanes required a lot of them. Therefore, they would not produce many new machine guns.

But it was better than nothing. Plus, the Aerial Knight also needed machine guns, so this project was very necessary.

As far as Roland saw, the First Army could still remain in a superior postion in the Kingdom of Everwinter and the Kingdom of Wolfheart without upgrading their guns. Only the elite unit, who usually took on special missions such as scouting, covering and rescue, would need such an advanced weapon.

Also, the semi-automatic rifle invented by Van’er was in the process of mass production. Every five soldiers would have a “Van’er Rifle”. The reason that Roland did not change all the bolt rifles was logistics. Since the linkage was left in the air, the rifle was not actually very durable. It could easily get jammed after multiple shots.

However, the “Van’er Rifle” could effectively increase the firepower.

The next project that Roland had in comtemplation was the biplane. After four months of intense tests, the first generation of biplanes was finally put into use and was named the “Fire of Heaven”. Although this new model was very similar to the “Unicorn”, and its structure was not extremely complicated, it was still unrealistic to ask ordinary workers to manufacture and assemble it. As for the production of the engine, it was still reliant on Anna’s ability.

Having said that, Roland still planned to gather the top workers in the industrial zones to tackle these potential problems. These people had elevated themselves from apprentices who used to flail hammers to excellent machine tool operators. It was also a good time to test how far the industrialization of Neverwinter had gone in the three years after the establishment of the first steam engine plant.

The only way to suppress the Devilbeasts was to dominate the sky.

The “Fire of Heaven” was obviously just the beginning of this magnificent endeavor.

The last project Roland had in mind was regarding the new Spidery Monstrous Beast. Roland planned to create a small-caliber cannon larger than the mortars but smaller than the Longsong Cannons to repel the Monstrous Beasts. The caliber should be around 75 milimeters. It could be easily carried on horses and by soldiers, and Hummingbird did not necessarily have to reduce its weight.

It was not difficult to make such a cannon. Roland only needed a few workers from the cannon plant. However, before that, he had to first create a sample cannon and test it out.

He had discussed these prospective projects with Anna numerous times in private. They soon reached a mutual understanding without any unncessary explanation.

This would be the grandest manufacturing project in Neverwinter in the history of time, for the project involved nearly 10 plants and a workforce of 20,000 and 30,000 people.

With the implementation of the immigration campaign, the industrialization in Neverwinter would become even more intense and rapid.

A machine titled “nation” was set in motion.

Chapter 1258: Air Combat Maneuver

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The students in the Aerial Knight Academy were busy training.

All the trainer aircrafts were spreading out in a line at the end of the runway, and the 30 official trainees were listening to Princess Tilly’s instructions. A little farther on, students who had not passed the exam or those who had recently joined the team were sitting near the runway, waiting to watch the next round of trial flights.

“From today onwards, your training will enter a new phase!” Tilly proclaimed as she paced back and forth in front of the students who were a lot taller than her. “Now, tell me what you’ve learned over the past one month! Start from Patter!”

“Lifting, Your Highness!” the students named Patter replied in excitement.

“Next.”

“Hovering!”

“Magic Movie!”

“What?”

“No…” the student faltered. “I mean balance training, Your Highness!”

“Strange…” Finkin muttered. “Princess Tilly seems to be nicer these days.”

“Really?” Hinds said under his breath. “She won’t exempt you from punishment if you make a mistake. Don’t you remember? We just cleaned the bathroom for a month.”

“I’m not sayiing that,” Finkin mumbled as he looked toward Good. “What do you think?”

Good nodded and said, “I have the same feeling.” He could sense that Princess Tilly had been somehow very anxious for a long time, possibly because of the poor performance of the aerial knight trainees. There were only 30 people out of 200 students who had passed the exam.

Another reason was that there were only six usable planes in the hanger. The rest of them were all crashed during the training. Like the instructor Eagle Face had said, one plane was even more expensive than a ship, which normally cost thousands of gold royals. No wonder Princess Tilly were so sulky and ill-tempered.

Nevertheless, the situation seemed to have changed a bit. Although Princess was still quite strict with them, she was less sullen.

But they still crashed a lot of planes every day.

Finkin, it’s your turn,” someone reminded him.

Finkin erected himself and said, “Discipline, Your Highness, I learned the importance of discipline!”

“And also responsibility!” Hinds shouted.

There was an uproar of laughter.

“I told Princess Tilly a long time ago that we should send these guys to the army and tame them first.”

“Suck it up. They’re all civilians.”

The other students exchanged murmurs. Apparently, the news that Finkin, Hinds and Good had been ordered to clean the bathroom for a month as a punishment had been spread throughout the whole school. However, students who used to be civilians simply made fun of them. Those who despised them most and would like to send them to the North Slope Mine were mostly soldiers from the First Army.

Tilly did not say anything but continued, “Next.”

Good replied solemnly, “Passion.”

Another flurry of whispers swept over the crowd.

“What nonsense he’s talking about?”

“Perhaps he couldn’t think of anything else…”

Good had thought Princess Tilly would not be satisfied with his answer, but she quickly turned away from him to the next student after a short pause.

After everyone supplied an answer, Tilly nodded and said, “You haven’t received much training, but you did learn a lot! Now, what you need to do is to apply what you’ve learned to the subsequent training. You have to be strong and use the flying techniques you’ve learned!”

“Yes, Your Highness!” everyone shouted together.

“Now, I’m going to divide you into two groups of three units to have a mock battle! The rule is very simple. If you could successfully confine the activity of the opponent party to your shooting range for 10 seconds without being shaken off, I take that you hit the target. You only learned firing at a fixed target on the ground before. Now, you’ll learn what an aerial battle looks like in reality!”

Everyone got excited about the news.

“Your, Your Highness!” a student yelled while raising his hand.

“Yes?”

“The gun is… unloaded, isn’t it?”

“What a fool,” Finkin laughed.

“Of course it’s unloaded,” Tilly said while shaking her head. “Actually there’s no gun… The one mounted on the plane is just a model, so you don’t need to worry that you’ll shoot your schoolmates after you pull the trigger.”

All the students guffawed.

“Plus, it’s far more complicated to shoot in the air than on the ground. Taking the aim doesn’t necessarily mean you’ll hit the target. Even with bullets, you’ll most likely miss the target,” Tilly said while shrugging. “Any other questions?”

Good now confirmed that Princess Tilly did have changed. She would not have had such a relaxed look in the past.

“I, I have a question,” Finkin said as he raised his hand and cast a look at the students from the First Army after he got the permission. “Your Highness, how do we know that we win? What if the other party doesn’t yield even if we successfully hold them back?”

The students had never fought a real aerial battle, but they had learned its basic idea in the class. If an aerial knight wanted to defeat his enemy, he should make every effort to take the aim and hold him back. There were machine guns at the rear. Yet due to the limited shooting angles, these machine guns were simply used to help the aerial knight to shake off enemies.

“I’ll make the judgement accordingly,” Tilly said and brought in two women. “They’re my special guests. They’ll watch your every move, so don’t you think you could cheat.”

“… That’s Ms. Sylvie.”

“The other one seems to be the butler of the Sleeping Spell..” Good heard the students from the First Army murmur behind him.

“The trainees over there are not only watching,” Princess Tilly continued. “Do you see the flags they’re waving? We have six planes, each marked with a number. Once you take off, they’ll use the color flags to indicate your status. Green means normal and red being shot down. If you see your number turn red, then you should leave the battlefield and return to the airport. Do you understand?”

“Yes!”

“Very well. Now, I’m going to divide the group.”

Surprisingly, Princess Tilly had already drafted a list beforehand. Good and Finkin were on the same team. Their number was two.

“This is it. I’ll leave you to decide who operates the aircraft and who fires. Team 1, 2 and 3 shall take off in 15 minutes. Don’t hover in the air. Then Team 3, 4 and 5 take off. Once all the teams are in the air, the mock battle officially begins!” Tilly said while clapping her hands. “Show me what you’ve learned!”

Good clenched his fists.

His heart was pounding frantically in his chest.

“Did you notice that?” Finkin said as he drew close.

Good exclaimed. Princess Tilly did not divide the group randomly. The first three teams were all constituted of civilians while the other three were comprised of students from the First Army.

Apparently, Princess Tilly wanted to know who was better!

“That’s perfect,” Finkin said as he rubbed his nose. “I’ve had enough with them. Since we’re aerial knights, let’s fight it out in the air!”

Good did not really care about the outcome of the mock battle. He only hoped that he could fly as much as he could so that he could enjoy the flight a bit longer. Good peered down at his trembling hands. They were resonating with him. He felt a warmth lance through his body as he thought that his hands would sooon reach onto the lever.

“I’ll be the pilot. You do the firing,” Finkin said as he patted Good on the shoulder.

“You know I won’t accept that,” Good returned instantly.

They stared at each other for quite a while before Finkin said resignedly,” Alright. We do the old way.”

There was a very popular method to resolve a conflict. Nobody knew where it came from. Somebody said it was invented by the Witch Union while the other believed it was a creation of His Majesty. Regardless, this method worked pretty well.

“Rock, scissors, paper!”

“I won!” Good said triumphantly as he withdrew his hand.

Finkin looked at his fist in disbelief and finally conceded gruffly, “I’ll let you fly this time. We’ll have a lot of opportunities in the training.”

The two men thus walked up to the biplane and boarded to the corresponding plane.

“You can do it!” Hinds said as he eyed them in a pretty ostensible manner on the runway. He was not listed, so naturally he wished them good luck.

“You’ll soon see that we didn’t train for nothing,” Finkin said as he pulled on the goggles and gave him a thumbs-up.

The stairwell were soon removed, and the propeller was set in motion as the handle started to spin rapidly

When the piston started to move and was connected to the gas, Good felt that the whole aircraft was injected into life.

“All clear. OK to take off!” the ground staff saluted.

Good raised his arm and returned a perfect salute. “Aircraft No. 2, go!”

The biplane slid onto the runway, accelerated, and soared into the sky against the sea breezes.

Chapter 1259: A Battle in the Air

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

In the roar of the machineries, the three planes of Team No. 1 took off in succession.

“Who do you think will win?” Tilly asked.

“… Well, do you want to make a bet? One bottle of Chaos Drink for the winner,” Sylvie asked hesitantly.

“That’s fine. Just make a guess.”

Slyvie looked profoundly relieved. “I bet on Team No. 2. They’re all from the First Army, right?”

“That’s right,” Tilly said with a nod. “Camilla, what about you?”

“I don’t really care, Your Highness,” Camilla Dary sighed. “Although these aircrafts look amazing, we need 30 aerial knights to fight 10 Devilbeasts. Even if we have twice the students we currently have, the result won’t change much. I don’t think you should put too much effort into it.”

“It’s just the beginning,” Tilly replied smilingly. “When I first came to Neverwinter, there were only a handful of plants along the river. Now, these plants stretch all the way to the Shallow Port. Plus, the Devil beasts haven’t changed a bit compared to 400 years ago, but these artifacts have upgraded a lot of times over the past half a year. Who knows what they’ll become of in the future?”

After a moment of silence, Camilla said, “You always have your reason, but you also have to take care of the Sleeping Spell. I’ve been here for too long.”

“Sorry. I made you worry.”

“No, Your Highness — ”

“I know,” Tilly said sincerely. “You should have left Neverwinter after the war up in the north, but you stayed because of me. Thank you, Camilla. I’m OK now.”

The two witches stared at each other for a few seconds, and then Camilla broke the silence and said with a nod, “I see. But I can’t manage the Sleeping Spell all by myself. Please pay them a visit when you’re available. Those witches are still waiting for you.”

“… They still don’t want to come to Neverwinter?”

“No. Some of them suffered too much, and they’re afraid to come.”

Although only a few witches chose to stay, it indicated that their dark memories of the past still had a certain influence on them.

Perhaps, they would never forget about this pain.

“I’ll go back after we win the Battle of Divine Will,” Tilly confirmed.

“What if we lose?”

Just then, the planes of Team No.2 flitted across the runway.

Tilly didn’t answer but simply gave Camilla a faint smile. “The battle has started… Come!”

…

“Hey, do you think Princess Tilly can really watch over the six planes at a time?”

Finkin yelled. Air currents seared through the plane and whistled around his ears. He had to shout at the top of his lung to ensure that his words were heard. Because of the wind, the cabin was extremely noisy.

“That’s Her Highness’ business!” Good hollered back as well. He noticed that four numbers out of the six had turned green, which meant that Team No. 2 was taking off.

Since they were not allowed to hover above the academy, the three planes of Team No. 1 all flew toward the sea. Good could not see where the fourth, fifth and sixth planes were at the moment, but undoubtedly, their opponent must have figured out where they were heading. They certainly would not follow them immediately, as it took time to rise and accelerate. It was not advisable to reckless enter the territory of the planes that had taken off first and get shot.

“I feel so nervous at the thought that Her Highness is watching me! If she knows how to take aims, she’ll look in the same direction as me. Doesn’t it mean that she’s right in my — ”

At that precise moment, the plane plummeted.

Finkin, who had been interrupted,bellowed, “What the heck are you doing? Can’t you fly better?”

“I’m saving you, you idiot! If Her Highness can aim the target as well, she can also see you gossiping behind her. Then you’ll feel very lucky to work in the mine!”

Finkin immediately shut up.

Good surveyed the surroundings through the crack between the wing and the body of the plane. He could only see a distant black dot drifting along the horizon. The other plane on the team was completely out of sight. Apparently, everyone was acting on their own.

Princess Tilly actually did not teach them how to fight in the air except for a few basic theories. He had to rely on his own judgement. Perhaps, even Princess Tilly did not know how to conduct an aerial battle, since this was entirely new, and they needed to start from scratch.

As there were no rules, he could fly to a spacious area and wait for his enemy to make contact with him.

After a moment of reflection, Good changed the direction and flew toward the Shallow Port.

“Oi, where are you going?”

“To the west. I’m going to fly round the plants!”

“Fly around? Why not just wait for them here?”

“Then we won’t be able to control the pace of the battle!” Good yelled as he made the turn. “Think! How are they going to fly?”

Good did not care about the result, but he knew that the winner could fly longer.

“How? They’ll rise and speed up, and then they’ll come after us!”

That was right. As they did not know when the second team would be ready to launch an attack, they had to defend themselves and get prepared, just like soldiers at the front waiting for their enemies to charge.

There was one way that could ensure him to get an advantageous position.

That was to draw the opponent’s attention to the ocean.

It was easy to spot the target running on an open field.

However, things were different in the sky. He could run in all directions.

“If they can’t see us but we can see them, then we can break the tie!” Good shouted. “You don’t think they’ve received less training than us, do you?”

“Haha, I see!” Finkin said as he patted Good on the shoulder heartily. “I thought I was clever. I didn’t expect that you play even dirtier than me! But I like it. Let’s do it!”

Good rolled his eyes. “Play dirty…” He was not sure if he should take it as a compliment. He thus started to descend while at the same time accelerating. The plane dropped behind the cliff, and its wheels brushed past the ships’ masts. The sailors on the ships all stared at the plane in astonishment.

When the plane streaked past the Shallow Port, a loud wave of cheers broke over the dock.

Those immigrants, however, all goggled at the sky, terrified. There was even a commotion when the refugees got off the ships.

“Don’t fly too low, otherwise the police will make a complaint, and we’ll have to clean the bathroom for another month again!” Finkin reminded.

“Don’t worry. I think that would do,” Good said as he slowly pulled the lever, and the plane gradually left the horizon and headed toward the industrial zone to the west of the airport. The industrial zone was enveloped by smoke all the year round, so their opponent was not likely to rise from there.

“Hmm?” Tilly, who was watching through the Eye of Magic, exclaimed in surprise.

“Did they… escape?” Sylvie asked since she also noticed something unusual.

“They probably don’t want to wait any longer,” Tilly said with a faint smile playing upon her lips.

Through the Magic Eye, Tilly could see everything clearly in the sky. The three biplanes of Team No. 2 had all taken off. Unlike Team No. 1, the students from the First Army did not fly to the sea to look for their opponent but continued to hover in the north before they headed to the south together.

It took them a long time to assemble but the three planes all stayed close to each other.

“Interesting,” Tilly muttered to herself. She did not teach the students how to fight in the air, nor did she remind them of the airspace and formations. In other words, they made their own decisions.

Beyond a doubt, no matter who won today, she would have some useful information regarding air combat to add to the Flight Manual.

“Just as I thought, they aren’t here,” Good said after he confirmed it was all clear. He pressed hard on the gas, and the plane crept up with an earsplitting roar. After the howl of the wind died down, he flew straight ahead toward the southeast.

There was no landmark in the sky. Even if the second team spot them, they would think that the tiny black dot they saw was but an eagle.

Plane No. 2 flew in a circle and returned to the Aerial Knight Academy.

However, just at that moment, the three planes of Team No. 2 entered the territory above the Swirling Sea and dashed toward the target closest to them!

Chapter 1260: Passion

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Tilly noticed that the first team dispersed as they saw their opponent approach. Plane No. 1 and Plane No. 3 flew in two different directions in an attempt to flank the second team.

Team No. 2 managed to maintain their formation and continued to approach Plane No. 1, which was the one closest to them.

As a consequence, Plane No. 1 was besieged by the three planes all at once.

Through the Magic Eye, Tilly could see the nervous look on the pilot’s face.

Under such circumstances when the second team was flanked, the pilot of Plane No. 1 could have shot down one of the three planes before the second team shot him down. However, the pilot was apparently in a panic, for he pressed upon the left pedal after a moment of contemplation and tried to avoid the upcoming attack. At this point, the two parties were only 500 meters from each other. The second team immediately changed the direction and started the chase.

The pilot of Plane No. 1 exercised all his efforts to shake his opponent off. Like Tilly had said in her opening statement, the pilot applied everything he had learned to this maneuver. This pilot must have worked very hard, for he seemed to have become quite proficient in plane operation after just one month of training.

Nevertheless, the students from the First Army were not bad either. They managed to stay close to the other team after Plane No. 1 dived and made a sharp turn. Since they outnumbered their opponent, they did not have to keep an eye on the other party constantly. The other party, however, had to watch every move of the three planes. As a result, Plane No. 1 dropped and slowed down. Seeing there was no way to escape, the pilot turned about abruptly and streaked toward the oncoming Plane No. 3.

The second team, in the meantime, found a perfect opportunity to shoot Plane No. 1. Plane No. 6 plummeted and zoomed toward the tail of Plane No. 1 at a downward angle of 30 degrees.

The machine gunner of Plane No. 1 had seen that the opponent plane was coming, and the pilot had tried his best to avoid the shot, but he could not escape the attack anymore.

It only took 10 seconds.

Tilly nodded in satisfaction and said, “Red flag for Plane No. 1!”

It was not until then that Plane No. 3 joined the team.

Plane No. 6 was still climbing, and the other two planes, Plane No. 4 and Plane No. 5, were both in a superior position.

It appeared that the first team had run into a disgusting dilemma.

— if, though, they excluded Plane No. 2 aloft in the air from the team.

Tilly rested her eyes on the area above.

“I saw them!” Finkin exclaimed as he poked out his head from the seat and leaned dramatically against the body of the plane. “Hang on. Plane No. 1 is down!”

“Are you sure?”

“The number on the airport has turned red, but they’re still fighting!”

“That’s because they haven’t noticed it yet,” Good replied, frowning. It seemed that his team members were weaker than he had anticipated. “What about Plane No. 3?”

“If I’m correct, that black dot coming this way should be it!” Finkin hollered. “Mate, they’re in a mess. It’s time to join them now!”

“Just a minute… Turn around. Do you see the sun?”

Finkin looked backward and was instantly blinded by the sunlight. “I was right! I knew you’d bean excellent pilot. We’re right in the sun. I can’t open my eyes!”

“That’s because you lost the game,” Good thought to himself as he shook his head and pressed down the lever. “In that case, let’s go!”

“Yayyyyy!” Finkin howled in excitement.

The roar of the radial engine overpowered the whistling wind. The plane shook violently as it zoomed against the air currents. Good felt his whole body tremble in exhilaration.

He was now a charging knight!

The whole sky was beneath him!

As the pilot of Plane No. 3 had directed all his attention to the slowest plane in Team No. 2, the other two opponent planes started to come after Plane No. 3. It was not until they darted toward their prey in the golden drops of sun rays that they realized there was another plane cracking through the air behind them. They should have ditched their team members and shot down Plane No. 3 first, but they hesitated, which earned Finkin time to take the aim.

By the time the two planes in Team No. 2 realized it, it was already too late. Good brushed past Plane No. 4 and swiftly turned to Plane No. 5. He had been aiming at Plane No. 4 when he was plunging, although he was not certain whether he could successfully shoot it down. Nevertheless, Princess Tilly made the rules, and he trusted her completely.

Good knew his team members could be knocked out of the team anytime, so he must be fast.

Four biplanes thus threw themselves in a bitter and intense battle, and the situation became precarious. Good could even see the livid face of the machine gunner on Plane No. 5. Although Good had explosed himself, he was much faster. After several rounds of chase and run, Good finally found time to take aim. While he was about to ask Finkin to fire, Finkin blurted out.

“The number for Plane No. 5 turned red!”

Almost at the same time, Plane No. 3 was shot down too.

Now, there were only Plane No. 6 and him left on the battlefield.

Perhaps, the pilot in Plane No. 3 was too nervous when flanked by the two planes from the other team and thus let Plane No. 6 slip and catch up with them.

“What the heck are those guys doing? They didn’t shoot any of the planes down!” Finkin complained gruffly as he turned the machine gun. “Now, it has become one against three!”

“We used them as a decoy in the first place,” Good said airily. “Well, there’s also another possibility, that is, that Plane No. 6 is a hard nut to crack.”

His prediction was confirmed.

No matter which direction he chose to go, Plane No. 6 immediately caught up without giving him a single chance to escape. He had to move constantly, otherwise the opponent would shoot him down before Finkin did.

“Damn it,” Finkin muttered irritably. “Can’t you fly a little faster?”

“I’m doing what I can!”

“We’ll be killed if things go on like this. Do something! How about flying to the port? We can take refuge from the sailing ships!”

“If we crash into the ships carrying refugees, what do you think will happen?”

“Er… we’ll be executed,” Finkin said, deflated. “Then forget it. At least, we aren’t the first ones that get kicked out. We’re doomed, unless there’s wind sending us up.”

“Wind…” Good muttered in a daze and suddenly came up with a solution. “You’re right. I know how to get our way out!”

“Huh?”

“Do you remember the upwind near the cliff?”

The wind from the Swirling Sea changed constantly, especially the one close to the beach. Because of the cliff, the air currents went around the precipice and turned into a gust of upwind. One could hear it whistling rymthically upon the cliff.

Finkin stiffened for a second after realizing what Good was talking about. “Are you crazy? You never know if there’s an upwind or not. If you get too close to the cliff, you’ll easily crash the plane!”

The upwind only confined to a certain area. Beyond that specific area, they’ll dissipate into the sea breezes. Due to the bumpy surface of the cliff, the wind could go in any directions. Therefore, it was even harder to maneuver the plane through the upwind than passing through the ships.

“I have to give it a shot. Just a little bit of wind and we’ll be able to shot up in the air!” Good said as he quickly dropped and zoomed toward the Aerial Knight Academy.

Plane No. 6 hesitated for a moment and also accelerated.

“How do you know when the upwind will come?” Finkin asked incredulously.

“The ships carrying refugees will tell me!” Good returned as he continued to drop. The plane was getting closer and closer to Plane No. 6. After a wide turn, it almost leveled the horizon. Many students would think that he had lost the game at this point, although the plane was still running at a tremendous speed. It was clear that he had nowhere to go.

He was now within the shooting range of his opponent.

“Clock the time!” Good bellowed.

“I think we still have eight seconds! Six, five, four — ” Finkin counted through his teeth.

In the meantime, Good was also keeping an eye on a ship coming toward the Shallow Port, yet he was not looking at the flag or the sail but the birds perched upon its mast. The flag and the sail were rippling in the air, so it was impossible for him to tell the wind power from them.However, the birds could capture the slightest change in the wind.

As though sensing something, the birds flapped their wings and descended from the mast before they flew toward the cliff. For a moment, they strongly resembled agliding “Seagull”. Good had noticed earlier that birdsliked to travel between ships and the cliff. It seemed that they could soar in the sky without necessarily flapping their wings!

The moment the birds reached the edge of the cliff, Good rose abruptly.

It was actually a very dangerous move because of the dramatic elevation angle. However, at this moment, the birds suddenly surged as though an invisible hand had been supporting them.

There came the wind.

In an instant, Good heard a piercing whistle.

Against the gust of wind, the plane shook tremulously. It again accelerated and, miraculously, shot up into the air and reversed.

The whole world turned upside down.

For a split second, time froze. Good saw Plane No. 6 flash below him, totally unprepared. The pilot sitting in there looked up at him in astonishment.

Somewhere in the distance, a pack of birds leaped out of the horizon, their white wings forming a stairwell leading to Heaven.

He had not lied to Her Highness.

His passion for flying grew every day after he joined the Aerial Knight reserve. He was addicted to flying.

This was what impressed Good most among all he had learned.

Now, the situation had changed.

Chapter 1261: A City Beyond Understanding

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Such a brilliant battle,” Sylvie commented involuntarily. U.p.dated. by NovelFull.Com

“Yes,” Tilly agreed smilingly and cast an airy look at Camilla. In the end, even Camilla was fascinated by the battle and started to watch the two biplanes attentively.

When Plane No. 2 successfully shook off its opponent with the help of the upwind, Tilly knew there would soon be a winner.

However, the result was not important anymore.

She saw what she wanted.

For example, when a plane was outnumbered and cornered, the dominant party took control of the air space and the pace of the battle.

Nevertheless, this was not an inflexible rule. The outcome of the battle was always subject to change depending on the dynamics between the two parties. By changing formations and tactics, the party in disadvantage could also defeat the party taking control.

Given that, teamwork seemed to be extremely important when fighting even more cunning Devilbeasts.

Another thing she had noticed was that the plane above had a better chance to win. Therefore, the best way to start a battle would be that one unit held the Devil beasts back while the other fired from above.

What she needed to work on now was the air force formations and how many planes that should be included in one unit.

But Tilly understood that training was different from a real battle. She still had to experience a real battle before she decided what to write in the Flight Manual.

Tilly was pleased that the students learned even faster than she had expected. Based on the current rate, the aerial knights could probably fight in the Kingdom of Wolfheart and the Kingdom of Everwinter by the time the “Fire of Heaven” went into production.

She would definitely not miss such a perfect opportunity to seek revenge.

The “Unicorn” was simply a trainer aircraft. She believed that Roland was now making a brand new fighter aircraft for her.

She should visit the castle and remind him once more after the training.

At this moment, the last plane finally landed on the airport.

The students and the spectators all burst into cheers and applauded.

“Now I know why you divided the group in this way,” Sylvie said quietly.

“I didn’t expect it would work so well. I thought I’d have to wait for another half a month,” Tilly said with a smile as she waved at Eagle Face and handed him a list. “Well, let the next group get ready.”

Tilly looked toward the north. Soon, she would have the demons to pay for what they had done.

…

The ship produced a long, deep whistle.

It indicated there was another ship coming in this way. Manfeld heard this kind of whistle every hour, and it became increasingly frequent after he entered the territory of Graycastle. Now, he could hear them pretty much every half an hour, and the interval between each whistle was getting increasingly shorter.

He had never known that Graycastle had such developed marine technologies.

It was commonly believed among the nobles in the Kingdom of Wolfheart that Graycastle was a country vast in territory with few resources. Its land was as infertile and thin as that in the Kingdom of Wolfheart. The Kingdom of Dawn was the wealthiest country on this continent.

However, it seemed that this was not true.

Stories could go awry in the retellings from one village to another, let alone that these rumors were circulated between two kingdoms. One thing that Manfeld could ascertain was that Graycastle had indeed defeated the church. This fact alone was sufficient to prove that the King of Graycastle did know how to play political games.

But he did not know exactly when he would arrive at Neverwinter, this mysterious city.

Manfeld yawned languidly at this thought.

The long voyage was more relaxing than he had thought. The ship did not immediately head to the next port after it reached the north of the Kingdom of Dawn. Instead, the crew cleaned the crowded cabin a little bit and asked passengers who suffered severe seasick to get off the ship and travel by land. The rest of the passengers thus had plenty of time to take a rest. The residents in the Kingdom of Dawn had even built many temporary buildings at the dock area as if they had prepared for the arrival of the refugees. Their services in collaboration with the Graycastle men were seamless. Had Manfeld not seen the flags of the Kingdom of Dawn upon the city, he would have thought this was a part of Graycastle.

Apparently, the two kingdoms had reached a sort of agreement. Manfeld was not sure at what cost King Roland Wimbledon had persuaded them to help him.

It had only taken him a week to recover from his injuries, and he had not used the strange pill given by the two ladies ever since.

Manfeld wondered how they were doing now. His hand reached for the pill in his pocket when he thought about the two women. Although they were emaciated and dirty, there was a hint of hidden beauty underneath their straggly hair. If they had put themselves together and dressed themselves up, they should have looked pretty stunning.

Manfeld hoped that the two women could reach the destination and become freemen. In that way, they could cut ties with their dismal past and live a brand new life.

Suddenly, Manfeld heard a strange buzz, as though something was flying above him.

Then, running footsteps came from the cabin on the upper level.

“Be quiet!”

“What are those guys doing? I can’t sleep!”

Someone complained at once.

Manfeld slid off his bed and peeped out of the porthole.

If he was right, those footsteps came in the same direction of the buzzing sound.

Nothing was changed. The sky was as blue as ever, and the vast ocean stretched away before him. A few big birds were chasing each other in the sky.

“Hang on. What kind of birds are they?”

Manfeld rubbed his eyes and could not believe what he saw. When the “birds” were perpendicular to the horizon, he could see their unusually sharp wings and tails, which made them look not remotely like real birds!

When they brushed past the ship, Manfeld could finally ascertain that this was not his imagination. They were not real but artifacts made of metal. What was more incredible was that the machines were manned!

For a moment, a phrase tried to take shape in Manfeld’s mouth and his lips parted like a dumb man’s. How could that be possible? He had gradually accepted the existence of the First Army and the steam-powered boats and had also somewhat foreseen what a prosperous city the king’s city of Graycastle would be, but this was beyond the scope of his understanding.

Suddenly, he had a strong feeling that Graycastle belonged to a different world from the one that the Kingdom of Wolfheart was situated at. It was actually different than all other three kingdoms. Otherwise, he should have heard about these extraordinary inventions.

Since when had the other three kingdoms fallen so behind?

When Manfeld was aghasted and confused, the ship whistled again. This time, it was a much longer whistle that indicated that the ship was about to dock.

He had arrived at Neverwinter.

Chapter 1262: A Conflict in the New City

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Keep in line. Don’t push!” a Graycastle clerk wearing a black uniform yelled as he pushed his way through the crowd. “Remember the number on your boarding pass and go to the corresponding checkout. Make sure you go to the correct one!”

Manfeld, still flabberaghasted, was pushed onto the dock.

He saw the whole port lie before him.

It was the largest port he had ever seen. The dock stretched away along the bank and disappeared at the end of the horizon. Unlike the damp, moldy port he usually saw, this dock was clean and tidy. The pavement was covered with white slabs. Thousdands of ships traveled back and forth. Even the port in the Kingdom of Dawn was incomparable to this one.

Many people gasped at this magnificent scene. However, Menfeld was still in such an immense shock that he was now emotionally numb after he had seen the flying iron birds.

Manfeld constantly looked backward in the direction he had come, in a hope of seeing the iron birds again. Instinctively, he wanted to convince himself that it was not a delirious illusion.

But by the time he reached the trestle, he had still not seen them.

Manfeld was a little disappointed.

“Please have your boarding pass ready and go to the corresponding checkout according to the three digit number on the pass!” Many people were shouting through a strange metal object at the refugees, their voice amplified by multiple times, so that everyone in the crowd could hear them clearly. “Please follow the guide and go through the security check. Welcome to the king’s city of Graycastle. We welcome every one of you!”

Manfeld calmed himself down and put away his thoughts.

He thought it was a very strange way to welcome new people because the refugees did not come to Graycastle willingly. Everything these Graycastle men had done in the Kingdom of Wolfheart was, in a way, a sort of dictatorship. Yet, surprisingly, he found himself a lot more self-assured after hearing these words.

The towering cliff suddenly caved in at this point and formed a natural outpost. The refugees formed a long line behind it and slowly proceeded to the checkouts in various directions. There were more than 10,000 people at the dock area, and apparently, not all of them were from the Kingdom of Wolfheart. What astonishing national power that was to bring so many people from the three kingdoms together in such a short period of time!

Just then, the refugees stopped moving, and Manfeld heard a commotion from behind.

Not only the people waiting in line but also the clerks in black maintaining the order were surprised.

Manfeld turned around and saw a colossal ship slowly dock. It was long and made of metal. There were no paddles on either side of the ship, its freeboard aloft and straight. Nobody would ever miss noticing such a superb ship. It was evident, however, that the Graycastle men was not astounded at the ship itself but the way it looked.

“Are they mental? I can’t believe that they use iron to build ships!” someone around Manfeld muttered in disbelief. “Don’t they know that iron will rust after in contact with water?”

“Perhaps the King of Graycastle wants to show off his wealth. The iron ship does look pretty nice. I didn’t believe that such heavy things could float in water before I saw the concrete boat.”

“What’s the point in making such a wonderful ship when it can only last half a month? I used to sail on the sea and know a lot about ships. Seawater erodes ships far more quickly than you could possibly imagine. Regular paints won’t last long. You see, this is what they’ve got in the end.”

Rusts could be seen all over the iron ship. Its body, which had once been polished and shiny, was now bumpy and damaged, which created a glaring constrast with the neat dock. The mast above was snapped and broken into several pieces. The ship was shuffling with great difficulties toward the dock like an exhausted, withered sea monster that had entered its decrepitude.

Did King Roland Wimbledon really intend to show off by building a ship like this?

The men in black immediately elbowed their way through the crowd for the sailors on the ship. Manfeld had a vague feeling that things were not that simple.

Peace was soon restored, and the refugees started to march forward again.

When it was his turn, the clerk only confirmed his name and number before he let Manfeld pass.

After 30 people passed the security check, a man walked up to them and said, “I’m a clerk working at the Administrative Office of Neverwinter. My name is Matt. I’ll assist you in settling down in the city for the time being. I know you must have a lot of questions, but please don’t worry. I’ll explain to you in detail on the way to the residential area. Now, please drink the Cleansing Water on the table first. It can cure the demonic plague if you’re infected. If you aren’t, just view it as a tasty beverage.”

“Do we have to follow you?” someone questioned. “We’re now Graycastle residents, too. We should be allowed to go wherever we want. Don’t you think so?”

“You’ll only become His Majesy’s subjects after you receive your identification cards,” Matt replied while shaking his head. “Usually, people can apply for identification cards after having one to two years of working experience, provided that they don’t break the Graycastle law. However, you’re all skilled workers, so you can immediately become an official Graycastle resident after passing the psychological test. However, the examination officer is quite busy. Since there are so many applicants, you’ll have to wait for two to three days.”

“Psychological test? Isn’t it just a screening process?”

“You’ll know it when you take the test,” Matt answered with a smile. “We focus on your present and future rather than your past. I became a city clerk after I passed the same test. Now, please drink the water and follow me.”

Manfeld thought this must be the “lie detector test” that the coachman had mentioned.

Matt did answer a lot of their questions that the refugees were most concerned about, such as what work they would have in the future, their salaries, etc. According to the policy implemented by the King of Graycastle, the refugees would be treated equally as the locals once they obtained their resident status.

Matt also shared his personal experience and told them how he had gradually adapted to the new life here, which greatly alleviated them.

When they entered a residential area in the suburb, a roar of laughter caught everybody’s attention.

Manfeld then saw some refugees corner a woman and slowly approach her. Many people saw the incident happen but nobody came up to stop them. Somebody was even egging them on, looking tempted to join them.

“Damn it. Why do these things happen everywhere?”

Manfeld had thought that Neverwinter would be different.

Frowning, he asked, “Did anyone inform the guards in black?”

Matt had told them earlier that the men in black had replaced the previous patrol team and were called the police. Manfeld was not sure whether they were reliable, but it seemed that there was no better way at the moment.

However, nobody took action. “Young man, don’t meddle with this matter. You’ll still have to live here for a few days before moving to the inner city.”

“That’s right. If those scumbags come to avenge, they won’t do you any good.”

“You — ” Manfeld said. His voice suddenly abandoned him. Then he looked toward Matt and said, “I’ll hold them back. You go and inform those guards!”

But Matt grasped his hand and slightly shook his head.

In an instant, Manfeld felt utterly disappointed.

He wrenched himself away and pronounced each word slowly, “I thought it’d be different here in Neverwinter from the other kingdoms, but I was wrong.” With these words, he rolled up his sleeves and rushed toward the crowd.

Chapter 1263: Future Work

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Excuse me, sorry. Excuse me!” Manfeld said as he elbowed through the crowd. The refugees who stirred up trouble immediately rested their eyes on him.

“Who’s this guy?” a man snarled. “I know you can’t wait, but you’ve got to until I’m done with her.”

He was the person who had just laughed. Manfeld soon figured out that he was the leader of the gang. It was almost impossible to rescue the woman from the hands of a dozen gangsters since he had no weapon. The only way was to beat the leader and take away the woman when the others were still in a shock at the resultant chaos.

Manfeld extended out his hands and walked a few steps forward as calmly as he could before he said, “I’m here to remind you that someone has already informed the guards in black. If you don’t run now, it’ll be too late.” In the meantime, he eyed the woman, in a hope that she would understand that he was not one of them. However, the woman was non-responsive. She simply tilted her head, looking utterly confused.

“Damn it. Doesn’t she know her situation?”

“Why’s she still so… composed?”

“What guards in black? Aren’t they just the patrol team?” the leader threatened, his face splitting into a nasty smile. “You never know whom they’d help in the end exactly. Hey, you little brat. You’re green, aren’t you?”

“Haha. From his look, he was probably a young lord.”

“So what? He’s now the same as us.”

“Get lost! Run as far away as you can before our boss loses his temper — ”

They roared with laughter. Just at that moment, Manfeld moved. He shouldered the leader abruptly and then punched him in the face. The leader soon fell to the ground.

Compared to Mick Kinley and his two trained servants, these gangsters were much easier to deal with. The leader did not even get a chance to struggle before he fell.

There was an uproar among the crowd.

“Sh*t! You f**k!”

“Save the boss!”

Manfeld got several hits in the back and legs but he did not care. He extended out one hand to the woman while using the other hand to block his face, and then yelled, “Come with me!”

Then, something extraordinary happened.

The woman immediately reached out her hand. Instead of holding his, however, she grasped Manfeld’s wrist and pulled him toward her.

“Oi, you…” Manfeld said irritably and suddenly saw an electric ray flashing across her body.

“Hang on… an electric ray?”

Before Manfeld realized what had happened, the flash became an arc that emanated an intense blue glow. It dashed toward the gangsters who rushed forward and, like a barbecue skewer, the electric arc went through them one by one. The mischief makers had no way to resist such an incredible force. Before they could even produce a short shriek, they all stiffened and fell backward to the ground.

“Now, that should work,” the woman said casually as she clapped her hands.

“Er… are you a…” Manfeld stammered as he gaped at the woman.

“Yes, I’m a witch,” the woman immediately admitted.

Manfeld had the impression that all witches should have been extremely beautiful and charming. However, when he studied this woman, he found her not remotely pretty. It was a very homely face, and she was as lanky as a little girl.

“Then, what should we do with them?” Manfeld asked as he pointed at the gangsters on the ground.

“I’ll call the police department and ask them to deal with them. Don’t worry. I only used 10% of my power, so they’ll wake up in half an hour, but they’ll be probably sent to the mine or the Furnace Area. I think they’ll probably stay there for half a month.”

Manfeld suddenly did not know what to respond.

He somehow had a feeling that she had planned this whole thing.

“By the way, I’m Sharon. May I know your name?” the woman asked and pulled Manfeld back to the present.

“Well, Manfeld…”

“You’re the first person I saw who came forward. Why?”

“Why what?” Manfeld returned as he rubbed where he had been hit. “Isn’t it a matter of course to stop crimes? I just didn’t expect that you actually didn’t need any help.”

“A matter of course?” Sharon echoed while twitching her lips. “If everyone thought that way, those onlookers wouldn’t have run away so fast.”

“But there’s always someone who understands it,” Manfeld said. According to the history book, all nobles used to be ordinary people. They maintained the order and developed the society.

“That’s right. There’s always somebody who knows right and wrong,” Sharon agreed with a smile. “You’re a new immigrant to Neverwinter, right? Are you interested in joining the police department?”

“Are you saying… to become one of the guards in black?”

“Yes. They crack down criminals and protect residents. I think it fits you. Also, they don’t always wear black uniforms. For example, like me right now.”

“Huh?” Manfeld was confused.

“Alright. I’ll have to report to the Administrative Office. Someone is waiting to receive you,” Sharon said as she waved her hand and then headed to the inner city.

“You know why I stopped you now, don’t you?”

Matt smiled to Manfeld after the latter returned to the team.

“What… what’s going on?” Manfeld asked, still quite puzzled.

“An effective way to deter criminals,” Matt said as he marched forward. “The residential area in the suburb wasn’t like that before, at least it wasn’t when I lived here. However, after more and more immigrants come here, this area becomes increasingly unsafe, and most of the crimes are targetting women. Of course, I’m not saying that you cause this because among them, there are also many migrants from the other parts of Graycastle. Since the number of refugees is overwhelming, the police can’t take care of everything. More importantly, if people only calls the police after the incident happens, the criminal may have already caused permanent injuries or harms to the victim by the time the police get there.”

“That’s obvious, isn’t it? With so many scumbags, no place can be safe,” someone muttered. “I think the King of Graycastle shouldn’t have accepted these shady people in the first place.”

Matt shook his head and said, “His Majesty hopes that everyone could be of use, especially when the Battle of Divine Will is coming. But this isn’t His Majesty’s idea but the witches’. They can use their power and kill time. In the meantime, they can also help maintain public order, so this method kills two birds with one stone.”

“K-kill time?” Manfeld thought in surprise and twitched his lips.

“Actually, it works pretty well. Any refugees could possibly be a disguised witch and attack people, and this deters those who want to commit crimes. Since the police department will punish all the criminals, chronic wrong-doers would probably think it over before taking action. With the help of the witches and the police, it’s much better than before.”

“I see…” Manfeld mumbled. It seemed that the men in black in Neverwinter were completely different than the patrol team. They were more like ideal knights that he wanted to be.

If Sharon had not lied to him, this was possibly an ideal job for him.

After they arrived at the temporary residence and got their own rooms, Matt said goodbye to the refugees. “I’ll come back tomorrow and show you around the Neverwinter city. It’ll be very helpful to get to know about the local culture. Also, please feel free to ask me if you have any questions.”

Manfeld wanted to ask how to become a policeman, but for some reason, he said something else intead. “On my way here, I saw some huge iron birds. I wonder if you could — ”

“Ah, I saw them too. If you stay in Neverwinter longer, you’ll know it’s not a big deal,” Matt interrupted him smilingly. “I was also very shocked at first, but you’ll get used to it. If you’re a talented man, you may be able to operate the machine yourself.”

“R-really?” Manfeld said. His heart skipped a beat.

“Naturally. Princess Tilly has put up a job post at the central square. She’s hiring new Aerial Knights.”

Chapter 1264: Persuasion

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

…

“Your Majesty, Your Majesty… Mr. Sander Flyingbird returned from the Swirling Sea! It seems… that they had big trouble!”

Roland was mildly taken aback by this unexpected news. After the meeting regarding the industrial expansion, he returned to the office and was about to finish the rest of his drawings when the news interrupted his train of thought.

Sander Flyingbird was Thunder’s alias.

“Where’s he now?” Roland asked as he stood up abruptly.

“In the castle hall. He said he would like to speak to you right now.”

“Send him in!” Roland ordered and then added, “Also, ask the kitchen to make some more tea.”

“As you command, Your Majesty,” Sean said as he quickly turned around and disappeared at the doorstep.

Nightingale asked apprehensively, “Do we need to inform Lightning?”

Roland shook his head and answered, “He should be OK, considering that he managed to get here. Let’s see what he’ll say first.”

It had just been half a year since Thunder had set off, and the commute normally took around three months. Since the fleet had also lingered at the Shadow Islands for a while, the actual expedition was actually a lot shorter than Thunder had planned. Thunder had predicted that this expedition would have at least taken a year to a year and a half. He had even wanted to see what the end of the Swirling Sea looked like and confirm whether the land depicted in the ruins was truly buried deep down the ocean.

Apparently, an overpowering and irresistible force had sabotaged the exploration plan that Thunder had prepared for so long.

Roland could not help looking out of the window.

Did it have anything to do with the Bloody Moon?

Thunder, disguised as Sander, immediately entered the office under the guidance of the guard. Roland could tell that he was in a rush, for he had not even put on the fake mustache as he normally did, and the flamboyant ornamental feathers had pretty much fallen off. Had Lightning seen him right now, she would have probably recognized him.

Nevertheless, he sustained no injuries, which was good enough for Roland.

“Your Majesty, nice to see you,” Thunder said as he bowed. “I thought I wouldn’t be able to come back again.”

Roland poured a glass of refreshing Chaos Drinks for him and said, “What happened? You took the best sailors at the Fjords with you this time, and I don’t think it was a storm or a tsunami that held you back.”

“Storms and tsunamis have signs, but thousands of Sea Ghosts don’t,” Thunder said, still feeling a little shaken. “Plus, I encountered monsters even more horrible than Sea Ghosts…”

Roland could resonate with his despair feeling. When numerous Sea Ghosts swarmed toward the fleet, and the seawater began to boil, any ships that failed to keep up would be dragged down to the bottom of the ocean immediately. In addition to the Sea Ghosts, there were also horrendous ships comprised of blood and flesh that could eject acids that traveled several kilometers. Anything that made in contact with the acid fluids would be instantly eroded, including iron and wood. It was almost impossible for the fleet to shake them off even if they had traveled at a full speed.

“The Sky-sea Realm…”Roland said darkly.

“Your Majesty, what’s that?” Thunder asked.

“This is how the demons call this civilization,” Roland answered and told Thunder about the demons’ double plan. The description of these monsters that consisted of ribs, flesh and inner organs was consistent with what he had seen through the God’s Relics. They could float in water like a ship but could also dive to the bottom of the sea.

“Are you saying that we invaded their territory?”

“Possibly, but this can also be attributed to the appearance of the Bloody Moon. There’s a possibility that these monsters become more active than usual and start to expand their territory,” Roland said. “Then what happened? How did the fleet escape?”

“In fact, we didn’t shake them off. The monsters started to attack each other,” Thunder said with a bitter smile.

“Attack… each other?”

“That’s right. They pursued us relentlessly as though they were never going to stop. By the time we reached the Sealine, we had lost half of our ships. Most of the survived sailors were on the verge of a breakdown after sailing day and night. Only the ‘Snow Wind’ you created still had strength to move further, as we didn’t need to adjust her sail or change her direction.”

“So, just when everyone was desperate and about to give up, a huge monster suddenly leaped out of the water and attacked another monster. It looked like that the two monsters were biting each other. Although they were both monsters, the first one was much stronger than the second one. It soon ripped the other apart with his auxiliary limbs and tentacles that sprouted from its body. Then, all the Sea Ghosts and monsters stopped chasing us, as though they were spellbound. We thus got a chance to cross the Sealine and return to the Fjords.”

Roland heaved a sigh and was also pretty shaken by the horrid story. “You were very lucky. It seemed that I got the right name for the ship.”

“What does it have anything to do with the ship’s name?”

“No, nothing,” Roland said while waving his hand. “So, what’s your plan next?”

Thunder, for the first time, looked a little weary. He said, “To be honest, many people are now too scared to have another undertaking. I don’t really care much about the loss of the ships, but the sailors at the Fjords, who have been sailing for their whole life, go livid in fear when they look toward the east. I believe that nobody wants to sail out to the Shadow Waters again in a long time.”

Roland fell silent. This was not totally unexpected. Like Thunder had said, one could predict storms and tsunamis and find a way to get away with them, but nobody would like to struggle to survive an irresistible force, as such a trip could no longer be called an adventure.

“Those big Chambers of Commerce asked me to deliver a message to you. They wish to buy a land at a high price in Graycastle where they can take refuge in the future,” Thunder sighed. “After all, nobody knows whether the monsters will come back or not. The ocean is a natural barrier for a lot of Fjords people.However, if our enemies could roam the sea, then the whole Fjords Island would be in a very dangerous position with literally nothing to defend itself.”

It was such a rapid change. Just one to two years ago, Roland had planned to use the Fjords Islands as the last retreat in case they were defeated in the war. Now, it appeared that the situation had reversed.

Had Roland still lived in Border Town with only an asset of 300 gold royals, he would have immediately given his consent. But now, as transactions were all carried out in the new paper currencies, the so-called “high price” became no longer attractive.

“What do you think?”

“If they plan to found a kingdom within a kingdom, then forget about it,” Thunder replied while shrugging. “You won’t allow “islands” like that in Graycastle.”

Roland smiled. Thunder was indeed the most outstanding explorer in the Fjords. “If they only want to survive rather than gaining power, then Graycastle will always be open to them.”

“I’ll take your message to them, Your Majesty.”

“You must be exhausted after this expedition. I have some afternoon tea. Please take a shower first and then tell me about your adventure. It’ll take a few days to repair the ‘Snow Wind’. You can stay here to recuperate and then head back to the Fjords.”

“Thank you,” Thunder said while placing his hand on his chest.

When Thunder was about to withdraw, Roland suddenly asked, “By the way, are you still planning… not to tell Lightning?”

“I …” Thunder was at a loss for words for a second.

“You said you’d reveal your true identity to her after this expedition. Although the trip wasn’t very successful, the Sky-sea Realm has indeed taken over half of the ocean. Fjords people are in a panic. It’s likely that you won’t go on a trip in a long time,” Roland said as he propped up his chin. “And I need people to fight the demons. I think Lightnings would like to see her father still alive. So, how about just staying here after you’ve taken care of your matters?”

Thunder lowered his head. After a moment of silence, he replied, “I’ll think about it, Your Majesty.”

Chapter 1265: The Witches’ Life

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Do you think he would stay?”

After Thunder’s footsteps died away, Roland asked Nightingale.

“I don’t know,” Nightingale said slowly. “But he was serious about the last sentence he said.”

Roland nodded in silence. Apart from Lightning, Roland wanted Thunder, the most extraordinary explorer in the Fjords, to stay also because of a personal reason, that was, Thunder could attract many Fjords people to Neverwinter, and he was the ideal man to command the fleet.

According to Agatha, the Red Mist probably had already permeated half of the Kingdom of Everwinter by now and might had also reached the border of the Kingdom of Wolfheart. Under such circumstances, he had to carry out his rescue operation from the coast and attack the demons from sides. Judging from the battle at the Northernmost Port, he believed that a powerful fleet was absolutely necessary to alleviate the stress of the army.

Although there were many merchant ships traveling back and forth, it was impossible to rely on them to fight the demons in the area covered with the Red Mist. Roland could definitely build several large ships, but what he urgently needed were sailors and a commander.

If Thunder was willing to help him, all these problems could be instantly solved.

But Roland also knew that he could not force Thunder to stay. He would have to let him think it over.

Roland thus went back to his work. Suddenly, the telephone rang.

It was from the Witch Building in the Castle District.

“Hello?”

“Your Majesty, it’s Wendy,” Wendy’s voice came from the other end of the line. “We found witches at the checkout at the Shallow Port.”

…

“Sir, where are you taking us?”

Thylane asked gingerly while holding Momo’s hand.

Not a long time ago, they had been waiting in the line like any other immigrants to pass the security. However, when they entered the registration area, they were taken to a heavily guarded room separately by the guards in black.

They immediately turned nervous.

They had heard that a few refugees had to go through a series of “special interrogation” when they entered some cities and would have to bribe the examining officers to avoid being punished.

However, the officer did not do anything but simply leave them alone in the room. He asked them a few strange questions and released them. After that, another man in black took them to the inner city.

“You don’t have to be so nervous. My name is Joseph,” the man in black said mildly. “You’re witches, aren’t you?”

Thylane was startled. She did not expect that Joseph would soon see through their true identities. She did not know how he had figured it out, for she thought that she was in heavy disguise.

“Why… did you say that?”

“I don’t know anything about magic, but the witches told me,” Joseph said while scratching the back of his head. “I know they use a special stone to detect magic power. As for where I’m taking you, I’m taking you to the witches’ residential area, of course. You must be tired, right? Don’t worry. Ms. Wendy will take good care of you.”

Thylane and Momo exchanged surprised looks.

They were astonished that Neverwinter had so advanced technologies to detect witches. Had the church and the nobles in the Kingdom of Wolfheart also possessed such technologies, they would have been captured and killed years ago.

Also, it appeared that people in Neverwinter did not discriminate witches at all.

Their master had told them about this city in the far west of Graycastle as well as its ruler, Roland Wimbledon. They had also heard a lot of rumors before they had boarded the ship. Nevertheless, what they had heard from their master was very different from those rumors. Their master described the King of Graycastle as an arrogant and vile tyrant who hired witches to satisfy his own wicked desire, while people on the ship believed that witches were treated in the same way as ordinary people in Neverwinter.

That was the reason they had decided to move to the south.

As the Kingdom of Wolfheart was so far away from Graycastle, nobody knew what life in Neverwinter truly looked like. Therefore, they planned to conceal their witch identity and see what was going on first before taking the next move. They did not expect, however, that they were soon exposed.

Luckily, people here treated them just as normal residents.

When they reached the outer ring of the Castle District, a red-haired woman came up to them with two smiling little girls.

“I’ll take it over from here.”

“Yes, Ms. Wendy!” Joseph said and administered a salute. Then he waved at Thylane and Momo and quickly left.

Thylane started to study the woman named Wendy attentively.

“My name is Wendy. I’m the superintendent of the Witch Union of Neverwinter. These two are my assistants, Ring and Grayrabbit,” Wendy said with a smile. “Can I have your names? Although from the list I have, I see that your names are Thylane and Momo, I do want you to pronounce your names in person.”

Thylane instantly felt a lot at ease. It had been a long time since she had met such a nice person. To her, Wendy looked more like a noble than those true ones. She was mature and elegant, who reminded her of someone depicted in a portrait.

“I’m Thylane,” she replied in a low voice.

“Momo,” her companion also pronounced her own name.

“Good names,” Wendy commented as she held the two witches’ hands. “Welcome to Neverwinter. From now on, this will be your new home. Come. I’ll show you around and take you where you’re going to live in the future.”

They passed the fence and the yard before Thylane noticed that the Lord’s castle was actually not the highest building in the city. Behind that stood a more magnificent edifice. Between these two buildings lay a large, lovely garden carpeted with grass. Several beautiful ladies were chatting leisurely.

This was perhaps the dream life she had been longing for.

“Are they also… witches?” Momo asked involuntarily.

“Yes,” Wendy said with a nod. “You’ll see more when they’re off work.”

“Er… off work?”

“It means finishing working,” Ring explained. “In Neverwinter, witches, like everybody else, have work to do every day.”

“Then what about them…”

The little girl twiched her lips and said, “Like ordinary people, some are hard-working while some are lazy.”

“Didn’t your sister tell you that I have good hearing?” a girl with pointy ears said as she turned around and walked up to them smilingly.

“Ah… Lorgar, I was not talking about you,” Ring explained while waving her hand. “I was talking about — ”

“Hey, new members to the Union?” Another person joined the conversation as she ambled over. “Hello, I’m Mystery Moon, the captain of the Neverwinter Detective Group! Whatever ability you have, feel free to join us. How does it sound? Are you interested?”

“I was talking about her,” Ring said as she covered her face in embarrassment.

“Really? Were you introducing me?” Mystery Moon said while resting her hands on her hips. “Remember, the Detective Group is dedicated to solving problems using your brain. If someone asks you to join the Exploration Group, please ignore them. They only want people with great physical strength and never take personal qualities into consideration. This wolf girl is a perfect example.”

“Hey, do you want to have a taste of my fist?” Lorgar snarled while baring her teeth.

“Look, this is the proof!” Mystery Moon said as she hastily made an attempt to block Lorgar’s upcoming attack.

“So embarrassing…”

“Well, can I go back to my reading?” some other witches murmured.

Thylane gaped.

It appeared that the life here was a little different than what she had pictured.

Chapter 1266: The Past

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Wendy stroked Thylane’s head smilingly and said, “Believe it or not, Mystery Moon used to be even shyer than you.”

“Ah — S-stop!” Mystery Moon begged. “This was something a long time ago.”

“Really? I’ve never heard of them,” Lorgar said while pricking up her ears.

“At that time, she always came to look for me after everybody fell asleep. Therewere so many interesting stories that it’ll probably take memore than one day to — ”

“Stop!” Mystery Moon yelled. “What’s your condition, Sister Wendy?”

“Don’t worry. I won’t say anything… But Scroll complained to me yesterday that she has been so busy in the Administrative Office lately, and someone hasn’t cleaned up the file room for a long time…”

“I’ll go right away. We’ll see each other again tonight! Now, please excuse the Detective Group!” Mystery Mooneven blinked at the two new witches before she withdrew.

“That was boring,” the wolf girl said while twitching her lips and crossed the yard with the others. “I’ll go help her as well because I’m such a nice person.”

Grayrabbit elbowed Ring after all the witches left and muttered, “I think Lorgar doesn’t want to be labeled as a ‘lazy’ person, so she went to offer help.”

“Er… really?”

Momo, however, at this point, burst into a laugh.

Thylane was a little surprised. The smile faded away instantly, but it was the first smile since Momo had escaped from her master.

“You’ll like it here, although it can be a little too noisy sometimes. But you’ll get used to it,” Wendy explained gently. “Come, I’ll show you your room.”

Thylane was utterly astonished after the tour.

She had never imagined such a comfortable room. Although it was not spacious by any means, it was equipped with everything. Even the mattress was soft and clean. Thylane had seen a noble’s bedroom before. In fact, although shackled, she had been staying in her master’s bedroom for years. Nevertheless, the bed and the cotton fabrics here were far better than those in her master’s room.

When Wendy urged her to try the bed, Thylane could not help sighing comfortably. She almost succumbed to the fatigue that had been constantly trying to take her over during the trip, and, for a second, she did not want to get up.

Momo also felt the same way.

Wendy explained that the mattress was supported by hundreds of springs, which was whyit was so soft.No matter what your sleeping position was, the bedwould be able to support your body perfectly.

Thylane did not know what a spring was, but she somehow understood that it was made of steel, a material normally used to make armors. She was not sure whether she should say this was a creative innovation or a pure waste of resources.

The mattress was just one of the amazing things here.

For example, water automatically came out from the tap.

The mirror in the bathroom reflected every single hair on her body.

There was soft anti-slippery floor.

The lamp was powered by magic.

Even the simplest wooden furniture looked somewhat different. Thylane did not know what made them different, but they were excellent. Compared to the noble’s grand mansion, this room felt more like a”home”.

Wendy said, “The Witch Building went through several refurbishments. In the past three years, many sisters helped with the rennovations. Some of the technologies applied to the Witch Building are also applied to the Castle District and the new residential area. Of course, if you want to be the first person toexperience the latest technologies,the Witch Building would be the best option.”

“Can we really… live here?” Momo asked hesitantly.

“Yes, but you’ll have to join the Witch Union first.”

“Is it optional?” Thylane asked in surprise.

For a moment, Wendy looked sorrowful. “Because many of us suffered a lot in the Witch Cooperation Association. Well, let’s not talk about this. Anyway, it’s up to you. Do you remember the questions the officer asked you at the customs?”

Thylane nodded. At that time, only she and Momohad beentaken to that room, so she had been nervous for quite a while.

“These questions are only put to witches. People who possess magic power can bring more damage than ordinary people if they have an ill design. Once they confirm that you pose no threat to Neverwinter, you can live anywhere in the city. In fact, apart from the Witch Union, there’s also a similar organization called the Sleeping Spell, which was founded by escaped witches. The leader of this organization is King Roland Wimbledon’s sister.” Wendy paused for a second and then resumed, “Of course, you can also choose not to join any organizations and live on your own. I’ll also help you settle down, in my own capacity, of course.”

“But our abilities…”

“That isn’t the point. The point is what life you want to live,” Wendy said with a smile while shaking her head. “If you don’t mind it, can you tell me your past?”

Thylane felt a warmth steal through her.

She felt that she could trustthis red-haired woman.

Even if this was just an illusion, she did not want to walk away.

Perhaps, everything would disappear in the end, but now, she wanted to stay here a bit longer.

Thylane bit her lip and slowly divulged her past experience.

Before she had become a witch, she had been just the same as any person in the village. After she was awakened, like so many witches, she was banished, hated and persecuted. Just when she was about to give up, she heard about the Bloodfang Association and believed it might be somewhere she could settle down. Having a strong desire to seek protection, Thylane survived the relentless pursuit of the church and arrived at the Archduke Island where she contacted theagent of the Bloodfang Association.

She had never expected that what awaited her was an even more terrible disaster.

The Bloodfang Association not only turned her away but also sold her to a noble in the Kingdom of Wolfheart. In the next few years, she had been sold several times before she met her master, who used her ability as an entertainment. The “magic pill”could delay not only pain but also other emotions such as anxiety and pleasure.

Nevertheless, the pill could not eliminate pain or provide treatment. Once the effect of the drug faded away, the pain would all come back and become even more intense. If a person sustained serious injuries in the first place, the second wave of pain might be fatal.

Her previous master thus treated her simply as a plaything. He took her pill toindulge in more intensesensual pleasures. In addition to that, he also asked her to serve other nobles as a way to bond with them. This was how Thylane met Momo and some other witches betrayed by the Bloodfang Association.

It was not until that point that she realized that the so-called “home for witches” was a fraud jointly created by the Bloodfang Association and the nobles. It was easier to wait for witches to contact the association themselves than going out to seek them voluntarily. Later, to Thylane’s great horror,fewer and fewerwitchesshowed up in this “secret party” after the church invaded the Kingdom of Wolfheart. Finally, there were onlyher and Momoleft.

Then she overheard from one noble that the church ordered the nobles to hand the witches over to the church or execute them in private, and she quavered at the various ways of execution.

Thylane thus decided to leave with Momo when the city descended to chaos caused by the Church of Hermes.

Their escaping method was to make the nobles overdose the “magic pill”.

Chapter 1267: The Invitation

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The so-called “magic pill” would be only effective when the magic was injected into a physical pill. Thylane had never told these nobles that she could actually induce her power into any object. The reason she chose pills was that it was easy for her to control her power, but it also made the nobles forget about the true nature of her ability.

In that party, Thylane had applied her ability to all the food and drinks. This was the only situation where the nobles would put their guard down.

It then appeared that people could also die of extreme pleasure as they died of pain. By the time the nobles realized what had happened, it was too late. They fell to the ground while holding their chests painfully as their bodies spasmed. Even those who did not overdose were also seriously impaired, their strength gone, with a mesmorized and dreamy look on their faces as though they were enjoying the most blissful moment in their life.

The girl slaves in the room all fled in a fright, and the guards outside could not stop them. Thylane and Momo thus escaped from the mansion.

They hence commenced their arduous journey as refugees.

When they heard about the immigration campaign to Graycastle, the two witches decided to try their luck at the Sedimentation Bay.

“I see…” Wendy murmured as she pulled them to her bosom. “You must have suffered a lot. I promise it won’t happen to you again.”

“Don’t… don’t you despise us?” Thylane asked while biting her lip.

“Why so? Just because of your miserable past?” Wendy said quietly. “The church treated me like that too. I have no reason to blame the victims. Instead, it is those nobles that I should put blame on.”

“But our abilities… may bring misfortunes to people,” Thylane said while clenching her fists.

“That isn’t up to you to decide.”

“But once you take the pill, you’ll never forget the sensation it has brought to you. You’d like more. In the end, you just want to indulge in the pleasure with no regards to anything else… If we stay, I’m afraid…”

“You fear that the king can’t control it and will view you as demons?” Wendy said. “Rest assured. Our king… How should I phrase it? He isn’t like any ordinary king. He’s an eccentric but nice person.”

Thylane was stunned for a moment and echoed, “An eccentric… but nice person?” This was the first time that someone used such words to describe a royal.

“It means that you’ll never know what he’s thinking. You can’t view him as a normal person. Therefore, there’s no point in worrying about the consequence now. Trust is the most important thing to build a relationship,” Wendy said. Her voice suddenly became extremely soft. “He also saved the witches from the Witch Cooperation Association in this way.”

After a moment of silence, Wendy looked toward Momo and asked, “You said ‘our’ abilities. Does Momo also — ”

This time, the two witches hesitated for a long time before Momo spoke, “My previous master didn’t want me to use my power, so he took away my magic eye after I was awakened.”

Wendy had noticed that Momo had covered half of her forehead with a dirty rag. She had thought that it was a branding scar underneath, but the truth was indeed much worse than she had expected.

Momo then took off the cloth and revealed her hollow socket.

“But they don’t know that I still have my power. By removing my eye, I only lost half of my vision. Only the God’s Locket of Retribution can completely block my power.”

Wendy heaved a sigh. Only Extraordinaries could integrate their magic power with physical bodies. Momo was definitely not an Extraordinary. The presentation of her ability was through her “vision”, so the loss of her eye was just unfortunate collateral damage.

“Those nobles didn’t really take Momo’s ability seriously at first until something happened. Then her master removed her eye,” Thylane said in a low voice. “They called Momo the Child of Hell and inflicted various punishments on her. She barely survived.”

Wendy caressed Momo’s scarred socket and said, “What did you see exactly? Could you tell me?”

Momo lowered her head and answered, “… A number.”

“What?”

“A countdown number that tells when you’ll die.”

It took Wendy a while to understand the implication behind it. She gasped.

“The incident Thylane mentioned — ”

Momo nodded and said, “My prediction became true. The noble labeled with the number one diedthe next year.”

Wendy fell silent.

She now understood why those nobles had done such horrible things to her. Nobody would like to know when they would die beforehand, especially when they had only a few years to live. Even Momo herself would not want to know that answer.

“But… is the prediction really so accurate?” Wendy questioned after a moment of reflection. “Anything could happen.”

The two witches were both mildly taken aback.

“What’s the matter? Did I say something wrong?”

“No…” Thylane said while waving her hand. “I just feel… that you’re quite different from others. I didn’t expect that you would first ask about our abilities.”

“Hmm, so, what did you expect?”

Thylane replied in embarrassment, “You’d push Momo away and ask her whether she has used her ability. Then you’d drive us out of the castle and order us to stay as far away as possible.”

Wendy burst into laughter and said, “You can’t judge a person by her ability. The key lies in the person who uses it. Themore we know about the ability, the better we can use it in the future.”

“Do you think… that my ability will also be useful?” Momo asked in disbelief.

“I don’t know, but His Majesty once told me that every ability is useful, only it takes time for some abilities.”

Momo remained motionless for a long time before she said slowly, “I can’t predict accidents. I once saw animals still have many years to live before they were slaughtered. However…”

“What?”Wendy pursued.

“Some of the numbers have different colors… I don’t know what they represent for, but I have a feeling that they’re telling me something.”

“If you join the Witch Union, you’ll probably soon know the reason. Every newcomer should learn and practice their abilitiesfirst. Then they’ll have to do various tests. Only when theyknow well enough about their abilities can they upgrade.”

“Upgrade?” Thylane asked in confusion.

“You’ll see later. The awakening is just the beginning. You’ll have a lot to learn,” Wendy said while extending out her hands. “How does it sound? Did you make your decisions?”

Thylane and Momo looked at each other.

“If you can accept someone like us…”

“Then we’d like to join the Witch Union.”

Momo and Thylane also reached out their hands, slowly, tentatively and hopefully, and then held Wendy’s hands.

Chapter 1268: Party

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Welcome our new members! Cheers!”

A long table was placed in the yard before the Witch Building in the evening, and a raucous party began. Wendy and Scroll made toasts and drank for the two new witches.

“Cheers!” all the other witches rejoined.

Thylane and Momo raised their glasses in bewilderment.

Thylane had not expected that Wendy would immediately force her to have a hot shower after she joined the Witch Union. She put on new clothes, including underwear, socks and shoes. Before she could thank Wendy and confirm that everything she had experienced today was real, she was again taken back to the yard. This time, however, the back yard had looked completely different.

“You should say ‘cheers’ and drain your glass,” Lorgar said as she showed Thylane what to do. “Like this…”

“Ch-cheers,” Thylane imitated a little clumsily. She closed her eyes and raised the glass.

A loud wave of applause broker over the back yard.

Someone even whistled in the crowd.

“Lorgar is pushing people to drink again,” Lily said while twitching her lips. “Who says that you must drain the glass at one shot? I think she just likes revelries.”

“But this is the strawberry white wine brewed by Evelyn. I’m impressed that the new girl can actually compete against the wolf girl,” Mystery Moon said while clicking her tongue. “She must join the Detective Group.”

“That’s why all your team members are drunkards and lazybones. A perfect match for you.”

“You’re a member too!” Mystery Moon returned while sticking out one finger.

“I — I’m not! You still owe me ￥10!”

“Forget about it. Let’s scrach it out and start all over again.”

“Stay away from me!”

Thylane burped loudly. After finishing one whole bottle of wine, her vision blurred. She had been forced to drink with nobles in the past, but no wine was as spicy as this one. The wine was not bitter at all. Instead, it was mellow and much more tasty than ales.

But the biggest difference did not lie in the wine but in her current feeling.

Watching the wolf girl refill her glass in excitement and the laughing witches around her, Thylane, for the first time in her life, found that drinking did not necessarily have to be painful. She wanted to join the others and relax herself.

Just at that moment, a tall lady walked up to her with a glass in her hand.

“Welcome to Neverwinter. My name is Annie, also from the Kingdom of Wolfheart. I also went to seek the Bloodfang Association for protection.”

Momentarily stunned, Thylane asked, “You were also sold by the Bloodfang Association?”

“Yes, but I escaped in the end. Many witches traveled from the Kingdom of Wolfheart to Graycastle. For example, this one…” With these words, she pushed one witch who looked pretty shy to the front. “This is Iffy. She used to be a member of the Bloodfang Association, but she didn’t know that Heidi Morgan was selling witches at that time. Fortunately, the association is now over.”

It took Thylane a while to learn how the Bloodfang Association had been founded. It appeared there were also many other witches like her and Momo who had been forced to travel to Graycastle because of the betrayal by Heidi Morgan. The abhorrent Bloodfang Association had, in fact, been disbanded two years ago.

At these words, Thylane felt profoundly relieved.

On their way here, Thylane and Momo had had numerous nightmares where they had been caught by the Bloodfang Association and sent back to the nobles. Now, hearing that this organization was gone, they did not need to worry about it anymore.

“Sorry,” Iffy said while lowering her head. “If I could stop Heidi back then, nothing like this would have happened…”

“This isn’t your fault,” Momo said while shaking her head. “Even if you tried to stop her, you couldn’t stop those nobles.”

“Exactly. It doesn’t matter whether the leader was a witch or not. If not Heidi, someone else would have also done it,” Thylane agreed. She knew perfectly well how avarious people were. Once they benefited from the deal, they would not easily let it go.

“See? I told you that they wouldn’t blame you,” Annie said smilingly. “Now you’re in Neverwinter. Don’t hesitate to let me know if you encounter any problems. Even Iffy has no problem in living here. She’s pretty slow at many things. I think you’ll be just fine.”

“Cheers,” Annie said while raising her glass.

“Cheers,” Thylane returned quickly.

“It’s my turn now!” Lorgar exclaimed, a rosy flush on her cheeks.

“Don’t forget about me!” Lightning rejoined. “I’ve come of age and can drink now!”

“Coo, coo, coo!”

“No, you can’t. Pigeons can’t drink.”

“Coo?!”

“Oi, eat something with the wine.”

“Nana, you haven’t come of age, so don’t follow them!”

The back yard was filled with laughter.

“It has been a long time since we had new members. Now we suddenly have two. It appears that everyone is excited,” Scroll commented at the end of the long table.

“I did the right thing to show them the Witch Building. Now I gradually understand why His Majesty did that,” Wendy said with a smile. “Even if they first contacted the Sleeping Spell, I would also have a way to win them over. His Majesty calls it sugarcoated… something along that line.”

“You’re more and more like a leader,” Scroll joked. “I remember at first, you found it hard to manage. Now, you even intend to compete with Princess Tilly.”

“It’s an analogy. You were a leader back in the Witch Cooperation Association, so you have experience,” Wendy said while pouring herself a glass of Chaos Drinks. “But to be honest, I’ll never be tired of this kind of party.”

“Unfortunately, we can’t join them,” Scroll said, shrugging.

“I don’t mind it at all. I would like to always protect and guard them, if possible,” Wendy said quietly.

Both of them became silent. They watched the noisy witches while savoring the delicious food. For them, they did not necessarily have to talk to understand each other, for they had been working together for years.

Then, suddenly, a familiar voice said to them, “His Majesty wants to see the witch called Momo after the party.”

Nightingale revealed herself from the Mist.

Wendy immediately understood Roland. Her smile instantly faded away. “Well…”

“Take her to him,” Scroll spoke. “You knew this would happen when you wrote down her ability. His Majesty is always the most curious one among us.”

After a moment of silence, Wendy replied, “Alright.”

“If you don’t want to know the answer, you can leave now. I think His Majesty will understand.” Scroll paused for a second and then went on, “Whatever that answer is, we’ll always support him, right?”

“… Yes,” Wendy confirmed to Scroll as much as to herself. “Whatever that answer is.”

Chapter 1269: The Eye of Time

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

After the glitters of lights in the back yard went out, Roland met the witch Wendy had mentioned in her report.

She looked pretty young and extremely thin, around 16 to 17 years old at most. Apparently, she did not eat well. Although she had already taken a shower, her tawny hair was straggly and unkempt. What caught Roland’s attention was the black eye mask over her face. Although she had already put on a new one, the eye mask did not really sit well on her face.

“Your Majesty, this is Momo,” Wendy introduced.

Wendy’s words jerked the girl out of the trance, who scrambled to kneel down and bowed even lower. “Your, Your Majesty…”

“Please help her up,” Roland said as he put down the drawing and said mildly, “Don’t be nervous. It’s not a formal meeting or anything. I just want to see your ability.”

Momo looked frightened as she straightened up. “Your Majesty… I’m afraid…”

“I know. Not everyone will be satisfied when they know when they’ll die. Some people will even take it on you after they know the answer,” Roland comforted. “But I just want to know when that is. No matter what the result is, I won’t blame you. I promise.”

Normally, he should have seen Momo after Wendy tested her ability. However, as Momo’s ability was so special, he could not help. His curiosity was too strong to overcome. In fact, after the Battle of Soulagainst Zero, there remained a suspicion in Roland’s mind that he could not confirm.

But now, he finally had an opportunity to do so.

“Your Majesty…” Momo replied through clenched teeth. “Aren’t you… not scared at all?”

Roland knew he would have never thought about when he would die in the past because he had believed such a question was meaningless. Knowing how long he could live would only create unnecessary fear and worries. However, as he was now the king of the state, he felt great responsibility be placed on his shoulders. He had to think further. If Wendy’s report was accurate, the date of his own death could be very useful information. It might be viewed as a “top secret” that would not be so easily divulged in his previous world. He would thus feel very regretted if he did not obtain this informationwhen provided with such an opportunity.

Roland smiled. He knew Momo would not understand his thought, so he said, “Even if I’m scared, the answer is still there.”

Momo clenched her fists. After what seemed to be quite a long hesitation, she replied, “Since you insist, then please excuse my impertinence.”

“Your Majesty,” Wendy said after taking a deep breath. “Please excuse me.”

Roland stared at her for a moment before he said, “… I thought you and Scroll wanted to know it more than anyone else.”

“I can’t be that calm like you. However, like Scroll said, whatever the result is, we’ll always be with you.”

After Wendy shut the door, Roland turned around and asked, “What about you?”

Momo was stunned.

“Do I have to answer?” Nightingale said, whose sudden appearance really startled the little girl. “I want to know everything about you, both good and bad.”

Roland was amused by the big difference between Nightingale and Wendy. “So, let’s begin.”

Momo’s eyes shoveled from Nightingale to Roland in surprise and then took off her eye mask decisively.

When she looked up again, a jet of red flash appeared in her socket.

It was an eyeball made of magic, which looked extremely creepy against the scarred face. Roland could imagine what it looked like when her real eye overlapped with the magic eye. People in his previous world must like this type of strange pupil very much. However, in this era, it would be only viewed as the eye of devil.

“Any luck? Did you see anything?”

Momo looked toward Roland, and her eyes widened. The red flash quavered as though swaying in invisible wind. In a few seconds, the flash was extinguished. She stepped a few paces back andslumped onto the floor.

Roland noticed perspiration on Momo’s face.

“What’s the matter?” he asked as he stood up.

Nightingale strode over to Momo and helped her up. “She lost too much power.”

“Can she only inspect one person at a time?”

“No… I’ve never seen such things before,” Momo said, panting. “I saw a lot of numbers flicker but they all disappeared. They were in various colors… It took a while for them to finally stabilize.”

“What’s that number?” Roland asked.

Momo swallowed hard and replied with some difficulties, “17… It’s red.”

“How come?” Nightinagle asked in surprise.

Roland’s heart skipped a beat. Just like he had speculated, the winner of the Battle of Soul could obtain everything, provided that the winner possessed magic. Only magic couldincrease his lifespan and afford him power. Extraordinaries and hugedemonic beast hybrids all relied on magic to sustain theirphysical bodies. Without magic power, he would not benefit anything from the victory of the battle.

17 years was a lot shorter than Roland had thought. Although he knew the old Prince Roland did not have a strong physique, he had not expected that the latter would be that weak. Had years of debauncherous life consumed him?

“Maybe… I should take another look,” Momo said as she struggled to rise.

“No, that’s fine. Please go take a rest,” Roland said while waving his hand. “You’ll faint if you overuse your power. Plus, we haven’t figured out how your power functions. There’s no point in taking another look.”

“But Your Majesty…”

“I told you that I just wanted an answer. You don’t need to blame yourself,” Roland talked over her decisively. “Have a good rest. From tomorrow onwards, Wendy will start to test your ability and teach you how to control your power. If I want you to take another look, we can do it later. Also, can you keep this just between us?”

Momo stared at Roland for a long time, still quite astonished, and then nodded vigorously.

After the girl left with Wendy, Nightingale returned to the office and walked up to Roland who was standing before the French window.

“Do you regret knowing it?” Roland asked while turning around.

“Are you kidding me?” Nightingale returned gruffly. “I never regret. Now, what are you going to do? You only have 17 years left.”

“It’s better to know it now than later. Plus, this is probably not the final result yet,” Roland said while watching the flickers of lights outside. He found himself strangely calm and peaceful. “The soul container from Taquila may be able to retain minds. Once we figure out how magic power works in general, we can probably even build a new body in the future.”

“But there should be a ‘future’ in the first place,” Nightingale said, frowning.

“That’s right. Therefore, the first thing we should do is to win the Battle of Divine Will,” Roland said slowly.

He currently had no retreat anymore.

Chapter 1270: A Battle at the Front

Translator:Transn

Editor:Transn

In the king's city, City of Tusk, in the Kingdom of Wolfheart.

This city, which had been ravaged by the church, had yet to fully recover. From above, the outer city still lay in ruins. Nevertheless, compared to the Broken Tooth Castle that had been completely destroyed by the demonic plague, the outer part of the city looked much better. At least, there were not piles of decaying human remains down the wells and drainage facilities.

Just a few months ago, this place had still been under the ruling of the Tusk Family, a branch of the royal family of the Kingdom of Wolfheart. Iron Axe had initially planned to evacuate the towns and villages before he dealt with the nobles. As such, he had not interfered with the relentless battles between the Tusk, Token and Redstone Gates Families immediately. However, the sudden appearance of the Red Mist forced him to adjust his original plan. As the Tusk City was the central city that connected the south and north of the kingdom, he had to seize it to let the troops retreating from the Kingdom of Everwinter through.

It was a fairly quick and boring battle. Even without the support of the Longsong Cannon, the five temporary units, which totalled 500 soldiers, soon breached the well-fortified Tusk Castle and the Tusk City with the mortars and the anti-demon grenades. The local lord, Hilburke, was shot dead when he was supervising his army. The city thus fell even before the nobles launched a proper counterattack. The other nobles thus all surrendered, which officially ended the dominance of the three major families in the Kingdom of Wolfheart.

As a commander who had been following Roland since the first battle in Border Town, Iron Axe knew the military strength of Neverwinter better than anyone else. Five years ago, they had still been struggling to defeat the Longsong Duke; but now, the First Army could flatten any kingdom on this continent on His Majesty's order.

They had far outstripped those nobles.

However, this did not give Iron Axe any self-contentment, nor did it relax his mind.

He understood the unbridgeable gap between the human race and the demons.

As the Red Mist continued to spread, the First Army was forced to constantly retreat from the Kingdom of Everwinter to the Kingdom of Wolfheart. Casualties increased every day. As the army was not able to build a permanent defensive line, the units were often caught unprepared by the enemies. Intelligence showed that the demons frequently appeared on the path that the troops had to pass, despite that they had confirmed several times beforehand that the road was clear.

The constant defeats would definitely lower the morale among the soldiers. Iron Axe knew that he should have directed the army to the Cage Mountain and given the troops a good rest. However, His Majesty's order superseded everything. As the king needed people, he had no choice but to keep advancing despite the surging casualty rate.

There was no other way except fighting back.

They had to punch the demons in their ugly faces! Only in this way could they shake them off and raise the morale.

Iron Axe thus picked the Tusk City as his temporary stronghold.

"The demons are putting their guard down," Brian reported as he looked through the telescope. He had returned from the Southernmost Region to the Sedimentation Bay on Roland's order with 1,500 Mojin warriors. This was also the first formal Sand Nation army in the history of Graycastle.

"They started to put their guard down at the border the Kingdom of Everwinter," Iron Axe agreed with a nod. "Edith was right. Erecting the Obelisk on the ridge of the continent can be both good and bad. Although the ridge is a perfect hiding place, the demons can't easily march down to the south from there."

He could see dark, crimson clouds spread across the sky as he gazed upon the north from the watchtower of the castle. The Red Mist had already crossed the border of the Kingdom of Everwinter and the Kingdom of Wolfheart, and was now pressing slowly toward the Tusk City.

Right below the clouds was Goldwater Town, which had been half enveloped by the Red Mist. Nevertheless, surprisingly, Iron Axe did not see a single Fortress-like Monstrous Beast. Only very few Devilbeasts were hovering in the sky, as though they had been completely abandoned by their peers.

This would have never happened at the early stage of the war.

After several fruitless fights, the General Staff had formed a basic idea of what the demons were planning on.

The intention of their military operation was, in a way, the same as His Majesty's, which was to take more populated cities and have the men there serve them. Therefore, the demons were making every effort to stop the First Army from taking refugees away.

To seize men's territories as fast as they could, the demons normally used the Fortress-like Monstrous Beast to circle out a small Red Mist zone to enable their troops move from one area to another swiftly like frogs, and then attack the city before the Red Mist completely spread out.

By the time the demons took most of the cities in the Kingdom of Everwinter, they had advanced significantly slower. This indicated that as their territories expanded, the demons found it increasingly hard to manage the cities they had taken.

It was actually pretty easy to understand why it had happened.

It took time to force men to work and manage encampments. As the territories expanded, the demons' troops were further scattered. Another key factor was that the demons did not really need to send their main force to attack humans. With sufficient Red Mist, they just needed to dispatch a unit to destroy one unit of the First Army. It was thus totally unnecessary to assemble a large army.

Given that, after the demons reached the border of the Kingdom of Everwinter, there were fewer attacks from them. Perhaps, the demons did not necessarily reduce their total force. However, as the Red Mist had expanded significantly and stretched away for several hundred kilometers, it was almost impossible to monitor the whole area without increasing the force.

This was exactly what Iron Axe had observed.

"Sir, all the 'supplies' shipped from Neverwinter have arrived at the Tusk City," a soldier ran up to the watchtower and reported.

"Finally!" Iron Axe exclaimed in excitement as he turned around to face Brian and said, "Let's go take a look."

They thus walked out of the castle and saw several hundred iron barrels at a clearing in front of the city gate. These barrels were round, about half as tall as a man, one cubit in width, without a single crack on the surface.

"Sir, what are they?" Brian asked as he studied the barrels up and down, looking utterly confused. They did not look like regular containers since there were no handles. They did not look like weapons either. Numerous battles had told him that fixed explosives were far less powerful than cannons. It was a little too unrealistic to use these barrels to fight the demons off.

Brian pushed the barrels but they did not budge at all. Apparently, these barrels were filled with something. Nobody would like to spend time and effort shipping hundreds of heavy iron barrels to the front unless they were extremely important.

"This is His Majesty's new invention. You were still in the Southernmost Region helping His Majesty expand his territory when they were being tested, so naturally you don't know," Iron Axe replied smilingly. " These barrels will be the key to this battle. If they really work as perfectly as they did in the test, we would then be able to catch the demons off guard even in a mobile warfare!"

Chapter 1271: The Fiery Sky

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Jodel was observing the Tusk City through a peephole of a deserted house in the Tusk Castle. Due to the difference in elevation, he could only spy a small area outside the city gate. This would be the first stronghold they had to seize after the battle broke out.

In this operation, Mojins would advance first.

This did not mean, however, that Brian thought Mojins were disposable. In fact, they had earned this opportunity.

The general rule in the Southernmost Region was to prove oneself through power and strength, and attain resources through victories.

Jodel was from a small clan in the oasis. As the Silver Stream Oasis gradually shrank, his clan was on the brink of extinction. That was the reason that he had risked himself dealing with northerners in the first place. But now, all the clansmen had relocated to the Port of Clearwater, the permanent oasis that they had dreamed about. It was a reward from the chief for the victory of the battle against the Wildwave and Cut Bone clans.

Jodel requested to join this battle simply because he wanted to kill as many enemies as possible in exchange for greater rewards. He did not really care about who the enemies were. Fighting demons was actually better than living in fear of hunger, thirst, and uncertainty of the future.

Jodel believed that most Sand Nationals had the same feeling.

“Did you find anything?” someone asked him from behind.

“No, except that the Red Mist gets thicker. I can’t see anything,” Jodel said as he blocked the peephole quietly and turned around.

The one who put questions was Farry, the youngest soldier in the unit. Even his gun was taller than him. A deep scar ran the length of his face from his forehead all the way to the corner of his mouth, making his young face look a little grotesque. Jodel remembered his outstanding performance during the training, despite his young age. Even some of the most experienced warriors found it hard to beat him.

Jodel was surprised that Farry had yet made his name in the small oasis. He had actually never heard of him before.

“We’ve been waiting for two weeks, right?” Farry complained. “It’s so boring getting stuck here with hundreds of people.”

“Didn’t Sir Brian say that the demons have flying Devilbeasts? In order not to attract the demons’ attention, we have to wait,” Jodel answered. “Haven’t you hunted before? It’s common for us to wait for half a month to ambush a sandworm. Be patient.”

According to the operation plan, Iron Axe had sent around 2,000 people to the northern part of the Broken Tooth Castle where these soldiers dispersed and hid themselves. Another 1,000 soldiers were sent to the inner city in the south as a reserve unit. Their hiding spot looked no different than a ruin from outside, but the inside was pretty spacious. Its upper level was used for scouting while the lower level served as a temporary residence. Soldiers were supplied with water and food. Bedrooms and washrooms were separated. Although there was, inevitably, some odor, it was much more sanitary than where they had lived during the hunting event.

Jodel did not quite understand why Farry suddenly started to complain.

“You don’t understand,” Farry returned hesitantly as he glared at Jodel and slumped against the wall. “What do you think these iron barrels are used for? The demons have come, but they haven’t done anything but digging and burying.”

“I have no idea… but it’s the chief’s invention. I’m not surprised.”

He had seen too many marvelous tools and weapons in the past one year.

“I hope this isn’t a new Pill of Madness,” Farry muttered.

Jodel had heard of the Pill of Madness before. He was about to ask Farry for more details when someone poked his head out from below and said, “We’ve got a message from the rear. We’re going to launch an attack soon. Get yourselves prepared.”

Farry let out a deep sigh and said, “Finally we can do something. I’ll go right away.”

Jodel was more cautious. He asked, “What’s the signal? Is it what we’ve planned?”

“That’s right,” the same person replied to him. “When you hear the explosion, advance.”

“It’s about the time,” Iron Axe said as he put down the telescope and turned around. “Now, connect it to the power.”

“Yes, sir!” two soldiers from the explosion unit shouted and immediately began to operate the hand crank generator. The third soldier put his hand on the lever.

It was finally the time to test out what they had been preparing and planning for such a long time. The Red Mist had already spread throughout the entire king’s city of the Kingdom of Wolfheart. If the First Army continued to retreat, the demons would soon seize the Broken Tooth Castle eventually. Like the king’s city of Graycastle and Silver City, the king’s city of the Kingdom of Wolfheart and the Broken Tooth Castle were also adjacent to each other. The Broken Tooth Castle formed a natural barrier for the Tusk City. It was said that the king’s city would remain intact as long as the Broken Tooth Castle did not fell. However, at the moment, they had to use the Broken Tooth Castle to give the demons who had occupied the Tusk City a heavy blow.

Iron Axe had noticed that all the demons were equipped with a breathing device, which was quite a burden for them. Except for the Mad Demons that were pursuing the refugees, the other demons pretty much confined their activities to the area permeated with the Red Mist.

This gave the First Army a great opportunity to launch a counterattack.

“Sir, the explosion unit is ready!”

Iron Axe ordered heavily, “Ignite the explosives!”

As the soldier pressed the lever, a jet of dazzling red flash suddenly rose into the air above the northern part of the Broken Tooth Castle. More than 500 iron barrels were ignited at the same time. Golden flames lit the sky and the king’s city.

Everyone heard the ringing explosion.

However, this was just the beginning.

The barrels actually contained the slimes of the rubber worms created by Kyle, mixed with inflammable oil and accelerants such as powdered aluminum and magnesium. The mixture itself was not hazardous when it was solid, but when they were sent into the air and spread out like a mist, the slimes would become fatal. As the slimes were immediately burned off, the reaction resembled an explosion. In a split second, the air around the explosives was heated up to nearly 1,000 degrees, and the expanded air currents further inflamed the fire.

Just at that moment, the chain reaction occurred.

The explosives should have showered down at the ground. However, as the temperature exceeded the absolute threshold, the explosives continued to spread out like red orangey lightning and formed a giant net above the city. The flames, amazingly, started to move onwards!

Iron Axe was also shocked by this incredible scene. Then he suddenly came to the realization that the fiery rain had ignited the Red Mist. In an instant, the rapidly spreading red “lightning” infiltrated the air, and the giant net had now transformed into a massive shade!

After that, there was a more intense explosion.

The fiery shade suddenly broke as a gigantic fireball soared into the sky like a hatched fiery bird.

The sound produced by the fireball was much louder than the previous blast created by the iron barrels.

Iron Axe even saw that the air around the king’s city distort.

The earth began to quaver!

Chapter 1272: Beneath the Flames

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

As soon as he heard the first explosion, Jodel and his unit filed out of their hiding place according to the instruction.

However, no sooner had they trooped out than an ear-splitting boom came from the north. Dust was stirred up, and they almost fell as the ground shook violently.

Jodel managed to steady himself and looked toward the Tusk City in surprise. As he was standing on the lower land, he could only spy an orange fireball punch the air as thick smoke spiraled up. The Red Mist around the fireball was lit up, and the sky was aflame.

The Sand Nationals looked horrified.

They could only think of one phrase at this moment: the wrath of the Three Gods!

“Don’t be afraid,” Jodel yelled through clenched teeth and waved his arm. “This is a weapon created by the chief to fight the demons! It’s the demons that should be scared not us!”

His words jerked everyone out of the trance.

“That’s right. This is Heaven’s fire summoned by the chief!”

“Don’t just stop there. Move!”

The unit resumed to run. People came out from behind the wall, the windows and the collapsed houses. They soon joined the advance team and swarmed toward the Tusk City like a tidal wave.

Jodel was running at the very front of the unit.

Although he had completely submitted to the chief’s ruling, he still believed that Sand Nationals were more suitable to fight than northerners, especially for warriors from small clans like him who had grown up in a barren oasis and been used to struggling to live. He could use not only bows and swords but also flintlocks. After receiving further training from Brian, he could now shoot fixed targets accurately and also fire on the go.

This was a perfect time for him to demonstrate his power.

He not only wanted to be the first one that entered the city but also the first person to gain the victory.

He wanted his name to be remembered by the entire army!

However, when the troops ascended and gained the city wall of the Tusk City, a smothering heat wave greeted them. For a second, Jodel thought he had returned to the desert blazed in the summer sunlight in the Southernmost Region.

His skin was basking in the burning air, and he could hardly open his eyes.

Neither could the soldiers following him.

The whole unit was thwarted by an invisible wall and slowed down. Some northerners at the front even retreated in embarrassment and crouched down below the slope, in an attempt to protect themselves from the heat.

Jodel forced himself to march forward, but he immediately realized that something had gone wrong.

The fireball in the air was extinguished. A thin strand of smoke was still coiling. The thick veil of the Red Mist was now missing one corner, as though a giant beast had bitten it off. There was thus one blank area in the sky free of the Red Mist.

Through the wide open city gates, Jodel saw heat waves rolling at the end of the horizon, and the buildings on the ground looked distorted after the impact. The wooden houses all collapsed during the explosion, their blackened pillars sprouting out like the devil’s claws. The demons, however, did not come up to stop them or disperse in various directions. In fact, there was not a single demon in his view.

Jodel suddenly felt it hard to breathe in the scorching heat, and his body started to protest. His step became increasingly heavy.

“Darn. Why do I suddenly get so weak?”

The city wall was within his reach, but in a second, he lost all his power, and his vision blurred.

Jodel stumbled and then fell to the ground.

That last thing he saw was the contemptuous look on Farry’s face as the latter dragged him out of the way.

This battle exceeded Iron Axe and the General Staff’s expectation.

They had expected that the north of the king’s city of the Kingdom of Wolfheartwould be ablaze. The flames would have not only burned all the houses but also the Red Mist outside the city. Then the Tusk City would have been isolated temporarily, and the demons without the breathing device would have been in a panic.

After that, the ambush unit should have raided the demons and finished the rest of the enemies off. Although Iron Axe did not know how many demons there would be, based on the past intelligence, the demons would normally assign troops according to the population of the city. The demons definitely knew that the Tusk City had been evacuated. Therefore, during the first few days after the appearance of the Red Mist, the number of the demons should have been no more than500. In other words, the First Army should have gained a very advantageous position in terms of number and strength.

Nevertheless, they were not relying on this battle to eliminate the demons, for the soldiers had to hide themselves in the underground passages and ruins to avoid the scrutiny of the Devilbeasts. As such, they could not use any heavy weapons. It was not hard to suppress the demons with the rifles and the anti-demon grenades, but it was difficult to pursue them with only light weapons.

The main goal of this battle was to lower the demons’ morale and make them realize that human beings could fight back even while they were retreating. In this way, the army would be able to alleviate the stress of the retreating unit.

Nevertheless, the battle simply ended after the explosion.

The fire wall did not appear as planned. Instead, the heat waves as a result of the earth-shaking explosion barred the ambush unit from entering the king’s city. Many soldiers were burned and had even passed out. As such, it was impossible for them to continue with the operation.

Of course, it did not necessarily mean that they had failed. They could easily imagine what the inner city looked like judging from the heated air outside.

No written records had shown that demons had a higher tolerance to heat than men.

The only thing that Iron Axe felt regretted about was that he could not see the outcome of the battle at the front in person. As he had no idea when the temperature in the city would drop, he had to leave to avoid getting burned.

“Sir, all the troops except us have withdrawn from the Broken Tooth Castle,” Brian said as he walked out of the headquarters in excitement. He had not participated in the test of the new weapon, but he would remember what it had done in this battle for the rest of his life.

“Very well. Let’s retreat,” Iron Axe said while nodding. “I think it won’t be long before the demons notice us. It won’t be so easy to escape when they come after us.”

Just as Iron Axe had predicted, the next day, a demon unit arrived at the Tusk City on the Devilbeasts, the leader of which was none other than the Sky Lord, Hackzord.

Chapter 1273: The Demons’ Guile

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

20 hours later, Hackzord received a report saying a fireball blasted in the Kingdom of Wolfheart, which caused substantial damage to the supply unit. At that time, he was still in a city in the west of the Kingdom of Everwinter, whose lord had just pledged allegiance to him.

To be honest, Hackzord did not really want to deal with such a trifle. However, the report stressed that the explosion was exceptionally powerful. He thus decided to come to take a look in person.

Hackzord dreaded dealing with human beings, but he was the only one capable of this job at the Western Front. Not everyone was as smart as Ursrook who would like to learn various things, even though they appeared to be useless. Most of the Upgraded viewed humans as low lives and certainly would not invest their time in learning their language.

His commanders were very loyal to him and were all outstanding warriors. However, they also despised the mankind. They would have probably ripped men apart had he sent them to negotiate with human beings.

Nevertheless, men were submissive and meek animals. Although they were weak, they were somewhat clever. Hence, they could replace many Inferior Demons at the early stage of the war. It was, therefore, not advisable to exterminate them immediately.

This was actually all Valkries’ fault.

She should have been the perfect Senior Lord to communicate with human beings, but she wasted her time in the Red Mist Pond. Hackzord felt that his patience was running out.

When he arrived at the Tusk City, however, he immediately realized that something had gone terribly wrong.

The Red Mist was extremely thin as though it had been wiped off the sky. The city had been devastated. Remains of houses and blackened wooden frames could be seen everywhere.

As he dropped, Hackzord felt the high temperature and greeted a pungent smell.

He soon discovered where that smell came from.

A group of strange Inferior Demons curled themselves up on the street, their burned skins peeling off. Apparently, they had died in the fire. What puzzled Hackzord was that there were no visible signs of combustible materials around them, apart from some bricks and mud. Hackzord did not know how the fire had started.

He saw more than one burned Inferior Demon.

“Totolock, take ten people with you and search for the human army. Report to me immediately after you find them.”

“Yes, master.”

“Siacis, look into this matter and see if there’s anyone still alive.”

“Yes, sir.”

The two Upgraded soon heeded his order. Hackzord strolled along the street toward the northern area where his army sustained the greatest damage.

According to the report, one supply unit comprised of Inferior Demons was attacked. These poor Inferior Demons, who had never had a chance to upgrade themselves, were pretty much like laborers and slaves in the human society. At that time, they were shipping obsidian and a secondary Red Mist Pond to the Tusk City, for the purpose of building a campsite for the Junior Demons and the Upgraded.

From the remains at the scene and the scattered obsidian, it was obvious that the Inferior Demons suffered the blow while they were working, for some of them still stayed in the last position when they died. The fact that there was no sign of a fight indicated that human beings had not confronted the supply unit directly. The explosion had ended as quickly and unexpectedly as they had occurred.

Hackzord thereby judged that this was a trap of the enemies rather than the work of an organized army under the scrutiny of the Bogle Beasts. Totolock might not find anything during this search.

This fact made Hackzord feel increasingly uneasy. He would rather see the human army swarm toward him than hiding in the dark. He did not really care about those Inferior Demons, but he could not accept any failure at the Western Front. If the main force encountered a trap like this, the result could be disastrous.

Without a doubt, human beings, once again, used “fire” as their weapon. Hackzord was familiar with fire. In the past Battles of Divine Will, they had also used fire to attack the cities occupied by the human race. They rarely used it simply because the Red Mist could easily get burned at a high temperature.

But it was his first time seeing self-combustible fire.

Unless the whole city had become a furnace.

But how could it be possible?

If the mankind had the ability to achieve such an incredible transformation, he must inform the king of the potential danger at the Western Front.

“Hang on… Fire?”

An image suddenly flashed across Hackzord’s mind. It was an image he had captured when he had been searching for Kabradhabi’s memories in the Realm of Mind. A bright fireball blasted in the air like the rising sun.

Was this weapon what Kabradhabi had seen?

Hackzord shuddered involuntarily.

While he was lost in thought, Siacis’ voice came to him suddenly, “Sir, I’ve figured out what happened. There were 350 Inferior Demons in the supply unit and around 10 Primal Demons that guarded them. I haven’t found anyone that survived, but I think I know how those low lives did that.”

“Really? Then tell me.”

“Please follow me.”

Hackzord thus followed Siacis to the northern city wall where some Primal Demons were digging something. Around them lay a few black metal fragments. A little farther on, Hackzord saw some tumbled chariots. After they had developed powerful and flexible symbiotic demons, these old-school war machineries were obsolete and only served as transportation tools.

“Look,” Siacis said as he extended out his tentacle and grasped one fragment that were clearly melted down. “If we put them together, we could roughly see the shape of a vessel. These vessels spread out in a line along the city wall, and there were around hundreds of them. I believe those low lives put snow powder and combustible materials in them, in an attempt to cut the retreat of our supply unit, and then launch the attack.”

Hackzord was now very familiar with humans’ weapons, and he had indeed obtained a lot of them in this battle. Both “fire forks” and “fire bolts” required combustible materials such as snow powder to be effective. They were much more complicated than weapons powered by magic. Because of this, most of these weapons had pretty complex structures, which was something that Hackzord had not seen 400 years ago.

“If this was just an ordinary fire, why did it cause so much damage?”

“Sir, the fire wasn’t ordinary. At least, its temperature was much higher than an ordinary one. However, I don’t think it was self-combustible. The key, in my opinion, may lie in the chariots.”

“What do you mean?” Hackzord pursued. Siacis was a psychic, so he possessed a greater insight than the other Upgraded. That was why Hackzord brought him to the battlefield.

“When the snow powder was ignited, the heat was transmitted to the chariots through the city gates. The chariots are usually used to ship heavy equipment rather than the storage tanks for the Red Mist. The chariots thus exploded and further broke down the Red Mist,” Siacis hissed while waving his nimble tentacle. “You know that everything would burn at a certain temperature, including us.”

Hackzord was a little relieved after hearing Siacis’ explanation. No matter what combustible materials they were, the fragments of the giant iron barrels made him feel settled a lot. It seemed that human beings needed to make a lot of preparations beforehand to make this kind of explosion happen. They could not throw the explosives at their will. Hackzord thus believed that these traps would not pose a threat to the main force of his army as long as he took precautions.

Hackzord certainly did not think it easy to inspect a city occupied by human beings in a short period of time. Suspending the transportation of the Red Mist Pond and the storage tanks would not stop a second explosion either. He could not entrust this matter to the simple-minded Primal Demons and Inferior Demons.

The best way was to have human beings attack each other.

“Sir, what should we do next?”

“Don’t enter the city just yet. Let men inspect the city for us,” Hackzord said quickly. “I can’t get more Inferior Demons from other locations. Let the Snow Reflection Castle make up the loss. I believe Earl Marwayne would love to serve me.”

“Also, shouldn’t we obtain some of the enemies’ weapons?” Hackzord went on. “Many noblesloathe the Graycastle men. Give them an opportunity to avenge themselves.”

Chapter 1274: Ambition

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

A thin veil of Red Mist dropped down from the crest of the Impassable Mountain Range. Marwayne Parker had thought that it would be as intolerable as the mine, where the air was impregnated with dust. Surprisingly, however, he felt fine.

If he took a deep breath, he could sense a hint of cool wetness in the surroundings. The demon commander had told him that the Mist contained the essence of a life form. It would not cause human beings any harm but would instead strengthen them. Only witches, their mortal enemy, would suffer a fatal power rebound.

Marwayne was not sure whether he should trust the demon commander, but from what he could see at present, the Red Mist seemed to be harmless, except that it obscured his view sometimes. After a month, he had completely got used to living in an environment permeated with the Red Mist.

“My lord, the Sky Lord sent an ambassador.” Just then, a guard entered the study and reported, “He’s waiting for you in the yard.”

Marwayne nodded silently and said, “Ask him to wait for a moment. I’ll be there right away.”

“Yes, my lord.”

Marwayne smiled after the guard closed the door.

Every time he heard others call him lord, he felt exhilarated. He had thought it would be his last when the demon had crossed the abyss and invaded the Snow Reflection Castle a month ago. However, the demon had set him free.

After abandoning his prejudice against the demons, Marwayne found the Sky Lord was quite communicative. In a way, he was easier to deal with than the Graycastle men. At least, the Sky Lord would not strip the nobles of their lands without any reason.

The demons did not require him to pay taxes, nor did they loot his lands and usurp his power. As long as he pledged fealty to them, he could retain what he had now and also have a chance to gain more rewards. The demons could be rude, but they did not really prejudice his personal interests. After the Sky Lord asked him to rule the three cities near the Snow Reflection Castle, he became even more satisfied with the status quo.

The Snow Reflection Castle was a fortified, isolated island. Nobody could easily invade his territory, but he could not expand his domain from here either.Marwayne had thought he would remain as an earl for the rest of his life. He had not expected, nevertheless, that he would elevate to dukeon the doomsday.

Now, he ruled the entire northern region of the Kingdom of Everwinter and was, veritably, the Duke of the Northern Region.

Marwayne covered his mouth and forced himself to keep up a straight face. He closed the window and walked downstairs.

The demons had indeed killed dozens of his guards and hundreds of his subjects, but no war did not have bloodshed. Nobles also competed for lands through wars. As he was currently the ruler of four cities, his army expanded a great deal. As for the loss of population, he was sure that in a few years’ time, with sufficient lands and food, there would be more people in his domain.

He should also hang those who were pointing behind his back and accusing him of submitting to the demons out of fear.

Marwayne immediately saw the ambassador sent by the Sky Lord and the giant monster lying beside him as he entered the yard. To be honest, he did not know how to distinguish these demons. Unlike Hackzord, these demons were disgusting and barbarian. Had they not been sent by the demon commander, Marwayne would not have spared a look at these savage beasts.

“What can I do for the Sky Lord?”

The ambassador produced a stone from the pocket of his mount and opened his large, crimson mouth. Then he blurted out a word, “Listen!”

It was again magic voice transmission.

Marwayne stepped a few paces back involuntarily, for he could not stand the terrible breath of the ambassador. He forced himself to suppress his revulsion and said, “I’m listening.”

The stone flickered, and then a familiar voice reached his ears.

“How do you feel like being the ruler of a region? I hope you haven’t forgotten your promise, Mr. Duke.”

“Of course not, Your Excellency,” Marwayne replied quickly. “I’m at your service.”

“Very well. I believe that your subjects have got used to our presence after a month. Now it’s time to build an army and help us build a campsite. I want the campsite to be built in the Kingdom of Wolfheart rather than the Kingdom of Everwinter, and I need at least 2,000 people. Well, the more, the better, naturally.”

Marwayne wondered if Hackzord wanted heavy labor. He estimated that it was not going to be hard to fulfill this order. Therefore, he replied, “Leave it to me, Your Excellency.”

“I did pick the right person,” the Sky Lord commented in satisfaction. “Also, what about the research on those weapons? Can you duplicate them?”

“Well…” Marwayne faltered. “We can use them, but it’ll take a few more days to replicate them. I summoned the best blacksmith in the Northern Region and asked every one of them to forge a part. It was not very successful. I believe the witches are involved in the creation of the weapons. The blacksmiths told me that these weapons are not likely made by ordinary people.”

“That’s what I thought,” Hackzord said. Luckily, he did not blame Marwayne. “Even if that’s the case, you should also use them to resist the Graycastle men. This is my second order. Send people to Graycastle to stop them taking refugees. I’ll give you the rest of the weapons we obtained.”

“But I don’t have knights anymore — ”

“Then recruit them!” Hackzord talked over him. “Don’t you men like to recruit people? You tend to grant lands to others and ask them to serve you. Don’t be too cheap. If you succeed, you may become the King of Everwinter.”

Marwayne quavered. He had been dreaming of becoming the King of Everwinter. He had never anticipated that his ambition would come true in this way. Marwayne placed his hand on his chest, trying to slow down the frantic pounding of his heart. It took him a great deal of efforts to steady his voice. “Yes, Your Excellency. I’ll do my best to carry out this mission.”

“Be fast. I want to see the result as soon as possible.”

“I won’t let you down.”

The flicker disappeared.

“I, come, a week later,” the ambassador again blurted inarticulately.

With these words, he clambered onto the winged monster, raised his arm, and rose into the air. The winged monster howled and flew toward the outer city before it quickly disappeared from Marwayne’s view.

Marwayne’s face was, however, soon, covered in the dust that the monster had kicked up.

“Sh*t!” He coughed. Had all the demons acted like the Sky Lord, men would not have viewed the demons as monsters from hell.

Marwayne summoned the old scholar at once after he returned to the castle. Although this aged scholar had wetted his pants last time at the city wall, Marwayne could not find anyone else that could help him.

After relating Hackzord’s order to the old scholar, Marwayne asked, “So, what do you think?”

“My lord, this is a perfect opportunity!” the old scholar exclaimed while holding Marwayne’s hand. “I dedicated my whole life to the Parker Family, and I remember your father always wanted to expand the Snow Reflection Castle. Now, you not only did that but also got a chance to become the King of Everwinter. You must not let this opportunity slip!”

“I think so too, but do you really think those knights can defeat the Graycastle men?” Marwayne asked. “You’ve seen how ingenius those snow powder and bolts are. It’s impossible to replicate them, and the demons might not be able to obtain many of them. What if we run out of the weapons?”

“No, my lord. We don’t have to directly confront the army from Graycastle,” the old scholar said while shaking his head. “The Sky Lord doesn’t plan to do that either. He said ‘stop them taking refugees’. As far as I know, the Graycastle troops are quite scattered. Once we have adequate weapons, we may stand in an advantageous position! If we successfully crush a few units, the Graycastle soldiers will become hesitant. In fact, I just thought of an excellent idea!”

“Really? Spit it out.”

The old scholar then whispered his thought to the duke.

Marwayne’s face lit up.

“That should work!” Marwayne said while nodding vigorously. “In that case, their strength will become their weakness. Let’s do it!”

Chapter 1275: The Pharmaceutical Industry in Neverwinter

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

In Neverwinter, Graycastle.

Two days later, Wendy sent the test results of the two new witches to Roland’s office.

“I have to say that their abilities are very… complicated,” Wendy said as she handed in the reports. “It was my first time seeing that there are so many variables in one ability. This is just a part of the test result. If you want to have the full report, you probably need to wait for another few days.”

“Hmm,” Roland said as he put down his work and reviewed the report with great interest. “I believe that the Taquila witches are also interested in them, right?”

Wendy replied with a nod, “They asked Phyllis to conduct the test for the Chosen One immediately. Unfortunately, the light beams of the two new witches are quite weak. They definitely aren’t the keys to the Instrument of Divine Retribution.”

Roland was profoundly relieved after hearing this news. He had just approved the nationwide electricity plan, and all the magic cores were currently being converted into Mystery Moon’s power. Had the Chosen One suddenly appeared at this moment, Celine would have been pretty resentful. It would take a few decades to restore the Instrument of Divine Retribution, and it would definitely not be a pleasant experience monitoring the device every day.

Roland had heard from Honey that the Senior Witches from Taquila had recently developed a new hobby of “sunbath”. Instead of lying sprawled across the field under the sunlight, they actually crept out of the cave at night and lay there until the sunrise. Since direct sunlight could cause harm to the carriers, they generally did not like coming out of their hidings. Roland did not understand why the Taquila witches suddenly started this new activity, but at least, he could tell that they felt quite relaxed.

This was undoubtedly a good sign.

Roland quickly turned to the last page of the report.

Thylane’s ability mainly affected a person’s mood, and it would only take effect after that person took the pill. Like most attaching magic type, her ability would lose its effectiveness after a certain period of time, and its lasting power normally depended on the size of the object and how much magic Thylane invested in the first the place.

The test result showed that the “magic pill” could alter literally every emotion that a man could feel, including but not limited to happiness, pain, fatigue, tiredness, anxiety and fear. Once the power of the pill faded away, those suppressed emotions would come out altogether.

Roland somehow figured out why the magic pill could do so many things but the light beam was weak. The magic power, in a sense, was a nerve block that delayed the nerve conduction and the transmission of hormones temporarily. Its mechanism was very similar to that of some drugs in the modern society, except that the latter had very serious side effects and could be addictive as well.

Nevertheless, the light beam was not the only factor that determined the value of one’s ability. Thylane’s “magic pill” would definitely create a lucrative market and bring Roland immense wealth that could shock the entire pharmaceutical industry if he sold the drug in his previous world.

Mental illness was usually far more complicated than physical injuries, and it was normally harder to cure. Thylane’s magic pill could not eliminate symptoms but could delay them. As long as he took control on individual dose, the pill could minimize the impact of many diseases. Patients, for example, would feel less tired and anxious, and thereby live a normal life. All the negative emotions could get out when the patient was fast asleep. In that way, he would be able to “absorb” negative emotions without even realizing it. Once people felt well rested and calm, their bodies would repair themselves a lot faster.

The magic power could also help with some fatal injuries. People tended to lose their consciousness when experiencing excruciating pain. A lot of times, the injured was not able to properly handle their injuries in a timely fashion and thereby missed the best time to receive treatment. If they could treat themselves immediately before the paramedics arrived, they would have a higher chance to survive. The paramedics would then just need to deal with the shock and pain coming after and help the patient overcome the very first few days after the injuries, which were usually the hardest and most crucial.

Also, there were other witches who could help with injuries. Roland remembered that Tilly had once told him about a witch named Della on the Sleeping Island who could alleviate pain. Hero from the Witch Union could transfer diseases to other living beings. Although he was not sure whether Hero could also transfer negative emotions, he could ask her to give it a shot.

The key was that without Thylane’s magic pill, neither Della nor Hero could be of much help. Soldiers could get injured anytime during a battle, and witches could not always come to their rescue. In fact, many First Army soldiers killed in action had died on their way to the hospital because they had lost their consciousness and failed to give their wounds an emergency treatment.

Now, this situation might be changed.

Wendy’s report stated that Thylane’s ability could either positively or negatively influence a person’s emotions in general, but she could not choose what specific emotion she would like to apply her ability to.

This was also what a new witch needed to learn. She had to understand and learn how to accurately control her ability. Roland trusted that Wendy and Agatha would teach her. Once Thylane learned how to apply her ability to a certain emotion, all the current problems would be solved.

Roland could already see a prospective pharmaceutical industry from the report. This giant industry would definitely be more economically profitable than Chaos Drinks.

As for the other witch…

Roland ran his fingers through the form in the appendix on the last page and lapsed into thought.

“Your Majesty, this is…” Nightingale apparently also saw the sections of the form in various colors. She looked up at Wendy and said, “Are you sure the report is accurate?”

“Most of it is accurate. I can’t really collect a large sample in such a short time,” Wendy replied. “The only thing I’m certain now is that the number could decrease and increase.”

In short, the strange number Momo saw was the remaining years a person had at the current stage. The color of the number represented its future trend. Wendy recorded the numbers for the residents in Neverwinter that she and Momo had observed in great detail in her report and found that the color of the numbers for Neverwinter residents was significantly lighter than the refugees in the temporary residential area.

She thus concluded that the color of the number was subject to change under the influence of different factors, including hunger, health and disabilities. The deeper the color was, the lower the number would be. She also provided an example in the report that the number for a refugee from the Kingdom of Wolfheart had increased from five to seven after he had drunk the Cleansing Water.

If Momo’s prediction was accurate, then this refugee must have carried some infectious disease, for at first, he would have only lived for another five years. However, after he drank the Cleansing Water, the situation had changed, and Momo reassessed his condition.

Although Wendy did not know what the color represented for at present, she viewed it as an unhealthy condition.

“Your Majesty…” Nightingale said apprehensively.

“It’s better than what we thought, isn’t it?” Roland comforted. “At least, the number could go up, as long as we use the right method.”

Wendy wanted to say something, but in the end, she remained silent.

Roland thus returned to the report. It appeared that there was a huge difference in the numbers between various parts of Neverwinter. The average number in the North Slope Mine area was the lowest among all, and that for refugees was a little higher. The numbers in the Witch Building and the Sleeping Spell were 10 to 20 higher than the other areas, which reflected that the awakened witches did live longer than ordinary people on average.

Chapter 1276: An Overlooked Ability

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Roland took out a piece of paper from his desk and roughly estimated the average age of the residents in the urban area and the temporary residential area. He then concluded that the average age of Neverwinter residents were between 40 and 50, while that of the latter was around 35. He could already tell many problems from these numbers.

Generally speaking, it took a long time to increase men’s lifespan. Apparently, the life in Border Town in the beginning should be no better than the refugees’. However, in just five years, the lifespan of the local residents had increased significantly, to which Nana and Lily made a great contribution.

“We’ve collected data of 1,000 people within just two days. I don’t think Momo looked at each individual one by one, did she?” Roland asked.

“No. If she has sufficient power, she can see the numbers of all the people in that area,” Wendy replied quietly. “But she hasn’t done that before, neither does she know her limit. She thinks that her ability is like a curse. She can see when they’re going to die but can’t do anything about it.”

“Like she’s watching people around her die,” Nightingale commented after a sigh.

Roland, however, thought it totally wrong. This was definitely not a curse or a misfortune! When the development of a country reached a certain level, every single policy could exert a profound influence on the nation. Roland certainly had to abandon that outdated management style, and that was the reason statistics was so important.

Every modern organization should develop a well-functioning system to collect, observe and track the data change and make adjustments to their policies accordingly. A statistical analysis of the residents’ average lifespan was an indispensable step in this process.

It would normally take several decades to found such a well-organized department and recruit enough employees to conduct the survey without Momo’s ability, for people would never know how long a man could live after he was deceased.

Currently, except for Neverwinter, the other cities in Graycastle only had a secondary city hall to execute orders, and they were always short staffed. It was, therefore, almost impossible for them to conduct the census in the communities.

In fact, the establishment of such a complete information system was largely attributed to Scroll’s hardwork. Only when they could delegate literate people to grass root organizations such as local communities could they say that a fully-developed government had been established.

Momo’s ability, however, could help Roland skip all the preparation work and develop a national statistical system right away from scratch, even though she only knew a little about her ability at the moment.

Once Wendy figured out what those different colors indicated, possibly hunger, disease, environment, etc., he could then easily build a huge database that predicted the future trend of the population. With proper management, Roland believed that the kingdom would benefit a lot from Momo’s ability.

Those nobles in the Kingdom of Wolfheart never knew what they had missed.

Roland had already viewed Momo as an honorous clerk of the Administrative Office, and she could possibly become a minister in the future.

“By the way, did you get Nana’s treating schedule?” Roland asked as he closed the report.

Wendy answered with a nod, “She’sworking today. Do you want to see her?”

The hospital was indeed the busiest place in the city, especially after a major war. Unlike Anna, Nana Pine did not have to stay in the laboratory all day, but she was fully booked every day. It was said that there were hundreds of people on the waitlist, and that number was steadily increasing.

Her busy schedule was also partially due to her ability. Nana would exhaust her power within only 15 minutes when she treated a person with a broken limb. As such, she would not treat anyone that had lost a body part larger than a palm now. All these people would be granted a certificate of disability. Only after Nana came of age or upgraded could these disabled men jump the queue and receive treatment. They would need to show their certificates of disability to enjoy this privilege, of course.

Speaking of upgrade, Nana would enter her adulthood in the Months of Demons this year. However, the first thing that came to Roland’s head was when Nana had held that injured chicken and indignantly accused him of inflicting pain on the poor creature. Roland remembered that she used to study in the same school as Anna.

“Alright. Let’s go take a look.”

Momo had not expected that Wendy would treat her with great hospitality instead of banishing her after knowing about her ability.

She and Thylane thus moved to the Witch Building and became members of the Witch Union.

Every night after dinner, there would be some other witches visiting them, althoughThylane and Momo could not match the faces to their names. The food here was heavenly delicious, and someone also taught them how to use the facilities in the room and told them what they should pay attention to in the Castle District. Within just two days, they had changed their previous idea about the world completely.

It was so nice to be alive.

When Momo learned that she could see again, she threw herself into Wendy’s arms and cried.

This was the only place where she had the liberty to cry.

“Don’t worry,” Wendy consoled her while patting Momo on the back. “Nana rarely lives in the Witch Building, but she’s also a member of the Witch Union. She’s around the same age as you and would love to treat you.”

On the day of her appointment, Momo followed Ring to the hospital early in the morning. On her way, Ring explained to Momo Nana’s background. Unlike her, Miss Pine was from a noble family. She had great power and was called Miss Angel by Neverwinter residents. In other words, she was a person Momo looked up to.

Momo could even see Nana in her mind’s eye that the latter must be a smiling and elegant lady wearing pretty clothes whom everyone adored.

Momo was thus very nervous when Ring led her to Nana’s room. She lowered her head, feeling somehow ashamed and embarrassed.

“Is this the patient I’m treating next?” a silvery voice reached her ears.

“Yes, she’s Momo. Like you, she’s also a witch,” a familiar voice responded. Momo looked up and, surprisingly, found the person was none other than the king!

And then she saw Miss Angel that everyone was talking about.

It took Momo all her efforts not to scream.

Nana Pine was wearing a white robe, with only a pair of eyes left in the air. Her clothes were far from being pretty. Instead, she wore even simpler than civilians.

What truly horrified her was the fresh, dripping blood on her chest!

Chapter 1277: Out of Darkness

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Ah, don’t worry. This isn’t my blood,” Nana said as she took off the robe with Ring’s help. “The previous patient broke an arm when operating the machine, so it’s a little messy.”

“R-really?”

“That’s right. Come here. Let me take a look at your eye.”

“She’s so confident and strong. Is she really of the same age as me?”

Momo swallowed hard. She took off her eye mask carefully and slowly approached Nana.

“Right. Just like Wendy said. I should have sufficient magic power to cure you,” Nana mumbled after a preliminary examination and handed Momo a bowl of liquid medicine. Then she patted the bed next to her and said, “Lie down after you drink it. It’ll only take about 10 minutes.”

Momo heeded Nana’s words, and, to her astonishment, saw the latter take out a knife.

“Your, Your Majesty… Wendy…” Momo said while looking at the two spectators helplessly. She was almost going to cry.

“Well, Nana,” Wendy said. “Can’t you take things slow and give our new sister a bit time to get used to it?”

“But this is the normal procedure,” Nana refuted in surprise. “If I don’t cut the old wound open and remove it, my magic won’t work.”

“That’s true, but you can first have a small chat with her…”

“Well, in that case… how about talking about my previous patient? I feel it easier to cut a limb with a saw than an ax.”

“No, not this….”

“Correct,” Roland rejoined. “A saw can ensure a clean cut, but I don’t think it’s going to be easy to cut a big bone, like a thigh bone, with a saw, right?”

“Neither for a scull. Those female nurses are no stronger than me by any means. If Anna could help me, that would make my life a lot easier.”

“My fault. But it’s simple. I can design an electronic one for you later. How does that sound? I assure you that you can break a bone within a second.”

“Your Majesty, please stop!”

“Ahem, sorry, I can’t help when it comes to technical issues…”

Their voice gradually drifted off.

Momo turned away and, dimly, saw Nana talking to the king and Wendy while gesturing with the knife in her hand from time to time, as though she was going to do an experiment on her.

Cut? Saw? Ax?

Her eye lids became increasingly heavy as sleep crept over her. “Sorry, Thylane, I probably wouldn’t be able to see you again after this treatment.”

“Ah, she’s asleep now,” Roland said after he noticed that Momo had closed her eyes and fallen asleep.

Nana raised her scalpel and nodded at the two. “Now, I’ll start.”

Nana thus made a cut into the socket, removed the old wound and cleaned up the skin around it. Soon, blood oozed out and soaked the gauze. During the whole process, her arm remained stationary except for her fingers and wrist. She had to complete this initial step manually. Her nimble operation was the sole result of a long-term training and practice.

“Amazing…” Wendy muttered under her breath.

“I have to be fast,” Nana said while twitching her lips. “When I was in the field, I only had half a minute for each individual patient. If I couldn’t give them an emergency treatment as fast as possible, I might not be able to save other patients.”

“That’s why she’s become so swift,” Roland thought to himself. “You’d pass out at the sight of blood in the past, and those chickens — ”

“Your Majesty!” Nana exclaimed in agitation while rolling her eyes. “Don’t ever mention it! You were the culprit.”

“Alright,” Roland conceded while waving his hand.

“Plus…” Nana paused for a second and said, “I like the way I am now. At least, I’m much stronger, right?”

For a split second, Roland seemed to see the little girl he used to know again.

Roland stroked Nana’s head involuntarily and said, “Of course.”

Several minutes later, Momo’s eye was cured.

“The sleeping fern will lose its effect in two hours. Such little amount won’t cause harm to a witch, so she’ll be OK once she wakes up,” Nana said while looking toward Wendy.

“Thank you,” Wendy said smilingly with a nod.

“By the way, how much magic power do you still have?” Roland asked casually. “Could you take a look at me?”

Wendy’s expression immediately changed, and Nana grasped Roland’s arm in a sort of trenchant manner.

“Are you hurt?”

“No… I just feel that my nose is running lately.”

“Then you should go seek Lily,” Nana said gruffly as she withdrew her hand. “I took a look. There’s nothing wrong with you.”

“That’s what I thought,” Roland said while averting his eyes as Wendy cast him a suspicious glance.

It appeared that Nana was not omnipotent. Roland was not sure if she could cure those”underlying illness”, as these invisible diseases were not, technically, injuries.

Anyway, he had to do some research later.

When Momo slowly opened her eyes, a slope of orangey red clouds slid into her view. The clouds soaked in golden rays gradually faded to purple and drifted off in the distance. She could hear the rustling of the grass in the breezes, and occasionally, a few leaves rose into the air and brushed past her cheek.

Everything was so peaceful and sweet.

“I’m still alive…”

Momo thought.

But Momo soon noticed something unusual. Her vision seemed to have expanded, and the distant scene had become clearer. She raised her head and found Thylane look into her eyes smilingly. The latter said, “You finally woke up.”

It was not until then that Momo realized that she was sleeping on her friend’s legs, and they were currently right in front of the Witch Building.

“How long did I sleep? Where’s Wendy?”

“She brought you to me and then left,” Thylane said while shrugging. “You slept for the whole afternoon, although Wendy said you’d wake up in two hours. She told me that it was normal even if you didn’t wake up in time. It’s a sign of recovery. You’ll feel better after waking up. How are you feeling? Can you see with your new eye?”

Momo sat up and studied the surroundings curiously. She had thought that half of her world would be submerged in the darkness forever after her eye had been removed. She had never expected to see the world in its entirety again.

“Thylane, what should I do?” Momo muttered.

“What’s the matter?”

“How are we going to repay them for their kindness?”

Thylane was stunned for a second before she burst into a laugh. She looked up at the sky and said, “I don’t know either, but Wendy told me to work hard. This is how we can repay them. By the way, Wendy already told me what I should do in the future when you were asleep. I’ll work with Nana Pine who just helped you, and provide medical services to Graycastle.” At these words, Thylane scratched her nose and said in embarrassment, “Although I still don’t know how I can help treat patients…”

“But my ability…” Momo said while clenching her fist.

“Wendy mentioned you as well.”

Momo looked up and burst out in surprise, “Really?”

“Yes!” Thylane confirmed while nodding. “It’s His Majesty’s idea. He wants you to work in the Administrative Office with Ms. Scroll and help with the operation of the kingdom.”

“Huh?” Momo could not believe her ears. “Can I?”

“You need to ask yourself,” Thylane said in amusement and pushed her at the back. “I haven’t even figured out how I’m supposed to work here, but I think as long as we keep studying, we’ll know one day.”

“I’m not as confident as you…” Momo muttered in a hushed tone. “Do you think we can live here forever, like living in our home?”

“In fact, I also asked Wendy the same question.”

“Yes?”

It took Thylane a while to reply this time.

“She said of course we can, because it’s already our home.”

Chapter 1278: A Historical Moment

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

A week later, Roland received two pieces of good news.

One was that Iron Axe had repelled the demons with the napalm and thereby held the demons back temporarily.

The commander-in-chief described the explosion of this new weapon in his letter in great detail. The blast was even more spectacular than the test. In fact, human beings had already used fire to repulse the demons back in the first Battle of Divine Will, where they had set the forest on fire at the rear. The massive wildfire raged for several days and dispersed the Red Mist in the sky, which, in the end, helped human beings gain a small victory.

The demons thus learned their lesson and destroyed the forests, meadows, and even farms to avoid future disruptions of the Red Mist. They also built small stone towers similar to outposts in the area covered in the Red Mist just in case. With sufficient Red Mist on the campsite, they could then keep fighting even when the rear was ablaze.

Without a doubt, Iron Axe and the General Staff were inspired by the previous battle and developed this plan.

The strength of napalm was its portability. It could burn in the thin air, and it was extremely hard to extinguish with water. Roland had not expected, however, that the fire would result in such a magnificent explosion in the whole city.

Roland wished that Summer could reconstruct the scene. If he could find out the reason why the explosion had occurred, he could possibly exterminate the demons using the napalm.

However, the Tusk City should have already been enveloped by the Red Mist again by now. It was almost impossible to get into the city for a second time.

Also, Roland’s heart ached at the fact that he had consumed more than 500 barrels of napalm all at once. It was not hard to produce fuels, as he would simply need to invest more manpower. However, the key to produce napalm was to mix the slimes of the rubber worms with animal blood, and only the Ministry of Agriculture could farm rubber worms.

Nevertheless, the refugees from this battle were most important to Roland. Roland heaped praises on Iron Axe in his letter and also sent another 100 barrels of napalm to the front.

The second piece of news was that the plant assembling the”Fire of Heaven” had finally assembled the first biplane.

Roland immediately visited the plant in person after receiving the news from Anna.

This brand new plant was built at the same time as the Aerial Academy. Compared to the steam engine plant built with slabs and bricks two to three years ago, this plant was designed for technologically demanding products. The steel frame provided the plant with a spacious area, which enabled workers to assemble and repair a dozen planes at a time. The plant was equipped with adequate illumination devices. The floor was tiled with polished slabs, and the whole plant looked phenomenal.

Even Tilly was impressed with it when she entered the plant.

Lay men might view it as a palace.

Roland also invested the best equipment and hired many elites for the operation of this plant. He had sent the most experienced managers and workers, and equipped the plant with the third generation machine tools powered by electricity to meet the production need. As such, the plant consumed most of the electricity in the industrial zone. Thanks to the Mystery Moon devices, otherwise he would have had to suspend the operation of all the other plants to keep this one running.

In a way, this new plant displayed all the technologies developed in Neverwinter over the past five years.

Barov had told Roland that Neverwinter residents took pride in working here.

When the new plant was in operation, each workstation would be responsible for assembling one part. The plane assembly would start from the first workstation to the last. Workers would start with the frame, and then wings, then parts, then skins, and finally to the testing stage.

However, the plant was far from ideal. There was only one”Fire of Heaven” waiting to be assembled at the workstation closest to the exit at present, and the other workstations were all empty.

“Is everything OK? Did you have any problem?” Roland asked as he walked up to Anna.

“I have tons of problems,” Anna answered while shaking her head. “I don’t know how many parts and materials workers had wasted before they successfully produced this plane.”

Roland was amused at the resigned look on Anna’s face.

He had foreseen the difficulties when he had made the decision to create planes. It was practically impossible to learn about new materials and techniques in a short period of time, despite that he had tried his best to simplify the production.

For example, he had, specifically, created an assembly line to produce various drive rivets and break mandrel rivets for the single riveted joints on the plane. Compared to traditional double riveted joints, single riveted joints were much easier to assemble.

Roland had also numbered all the parts of the plane and drawn out every assembly step like those model assembly kits in his previous world. He had even installed user-friendly portsf or parts that could be easily mixed up to reduce the possibility of assembly errors as a result of carelessness.

Despite all his efforts, the workers only managed to produce one plane in the past half a month. Obviously, the assembly task was too hard for them to handle.

“Do you need my help?” Tilly asked suddenly.

“No, that’s fine…” Anna said while shrugging. She would only shrug and be less”lady-like”in front of a few people. “Roland asked me to supervise the workers, so I must solve the problems all by myself, no matter what they are, although I did want to give up a lot of times.”

Tilly smiled and said, “So, you’re actually very happy, aren’t you? Finally, there’s one real plane.”

Anna curled up her lips and replied, “I know you’d see through me.”

“If we have one plane, we’ll have a second. Once all the workers have learned about the assembly process, we’ll soon have more qualified planes,” Tilly said as she glanced at Roland. “If you could praise her now, that’d be even better.”

“I never expect him to praise me,” Anna said while twitching her lips.

“Huh?” Roland was dumbfounded. What had just happened? Why did they suddenly switch the subject from the plane production to him?

Just then, a guard trotted to Roland and reported, “Your Majesty, the first ‘Fire of Heaven’ is ready. We can start the celebration ceremony anytime.”

Roland thus rested his eyes again on the biplane and saw two logos on the light gray body, one the coat of arms of the royal family and the other a knight holding a spear while spreading out his arms. The whole plane looked extraordinary, but Roland felt that something was missing.

He pondered for a while and suddenly realized what had missed. Then he waved his hand and said, “Get the ribbon!”

Soon, a bright red ribbon was tied to the plane, with a red ribbon flower attached to the propeller at the head of the jet.

Roland then nodded in satisfaction. Now, the “Fire of Heaven” was ready to meet its audience.

After that, he made a speech, cut the ribbon, and took a photograph with Anna, Tilly, and all the workers who had participated in the design and manufacture of the plane, as well as the brand new aircraft itself, which was now numbered 001 and parked behind them.

“Now, look at me. One, two, three!”

Soraya summoned the magic brush and recorded this historical moment.

Chapter 1279: Conspiracy

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Your Excellency, Frost Town is right there at the front.”

A knight reported.

Marwayne Parker raised the telescope and observed the town. This town was situated at the southwestern border of the Kingdom of Everwinter and the Kingdom of Wolfheart, surrounded by mountains. One could see the view of the whole town anywhere from above. Due to the geographical advantage, the lord here did not build any castle in the town.

There were many towns like this one on the border of the two kingdoms. Marwayne would have paid it no notice in the past. But now, the town held a special place in his heart.

“Has the scout come back?”

“Yes. He only paid townsmen several silver royals for the information,” the knight said triumphantly. “There’s a unit of Graycastle soldiers here. Not many of them, only about 40 to 50 people, and they show up every now and then.”

“Why aren’t they stationed here?”

“The road beyond the border is treacherous, and it’s rumored wild wolves often come out around that area. Refugees can’t cross the border without guards.”

Marwayne immediately knew what he should do.

The Red Mist did not spread out along the border. In fact, the area covered in the Red Mist was in the shape of a semicircle that kept expanding. Currently, the Red Mist originating from theKingdom of Everwinterhad traveled beyond the king’s city of the Kingdom of Wolfheart. Therefore, Marwayne was more comfortable to conduct a battle in his own country than having an expedition.

Frost Town was on the border of the Kingdom of Wolfheart. As it was not very accessible to the public, refugees would seldom enter the Kingdom of Wolfheart from there. Compared to those major cities with advanced transportation facilities, Frost Town was as insignificant as a mosquito.

This was exactly what Marwayne wanted.

This meant that the Graycastle men would not notice his movement, and the information given by the scout also confirmed his theory.

Just like the old scholar had said, the demons would deal with those difficult Graycastle men themselves. What he needed to do was just to stab them in the back. Whatever the outcome of the battle would be, once people learned about his role in this battle, they would fear him.

Of course, the old scholar had developed more sophisticated plans to defeat the Graycastle men. If their schemes were successful, he believed that the Graycastle men would eventually slow down their movement, and then the Sky Lord would trust him even more.

“Let’s head back. It’s time to call a meeting and discuss the operation.”

Within half a day, Marwayne had returned to the closest town and patrolled into the previous lord’s mansion triumphantly. This mansion used to belong to an unknown baron who used to rule this area, but he had fled upon the arrival of the demons and the Red Mist, so Marwayne took his residence as a matter of course.

Although Frost Town was not under his jurisdiction yet since Marwayne only had the authority over the four cities in the Northern Region, he believed that the Parker Family would continue to expand their territory.

Soon, all the nobles gathered here and waited for Marwayne to break the silence.

The duke surveyed each one of them and memorized their countenances and expressions. There were 45 people in the room, most of whom were knights, although some were barons. The person with the highest rank in this room was the previous lord of the Northernmost Port, Viscount Narnos. These nobles lost their lands and subjects to the Graycastle men and immediately pledged allegiance to him after being promised that they would receive rewards. The number of the soldiers in this army had exceeded 300, including all the guards, squires and henchmen.

With so many people and a carefully-planned scheme, Marwayne believed this would be a perfect opportunity to defeat the Graycastle soldiers. More importantly, it was his first time using the enemies’ weapons. The reason that the Graycastle men had flattened the nobles in the Kingdom of Everwinter was that they used weapons much faster and far more powerful than snow powder. Without the support of the Sky Lord, nobody would have been willing to fight the Graycastle men, even if the number of the soldiers doubled.

“I wonder if you’ve prepared yourself for the upcoming battle?” Marwayne asked after clearing his throat. “I think everyone has learned how to use the firearms, right?”

“We just need to load the gun, take aims and pull the trigger, don’t we?” Viscount Narnos said indignantly. “Even savages know how to use them. I see no reason that we can’t. The captives didn’t tell us how to use the weapons until we tortured them. They were pretty reluctant to disclose the information. These weapons are really not a big deal!”

“That’s right. The weapons are ingenius indeed, but they’re much easier to use than swords,” a knight rejoined. “I also interrogated the Graycastle men. They just joined the army two years ago, and it only took them a month to learn how to use the firearms. However, I spent five years learning how to use swords.”

“Those low lives are foolish, and that’s why it took them a month. I would only need three days to master it,” another person spoke, and all the others guffawed.

“I’ll let them know they’ll be nothing without firearms!”

“They rely on witches to produce firearms. I think the King of Graycastlebeated the church simply because the church was too busy dealing with the Kingdom of Everwinter and the Kingdom of Wolfheart at that time.”

Marwayne suddenly realized that those infuriated nobles were usable. They had been holding a grudge against the Graycastle men for a long time. Although he had only built this new army a week ago and hardly knew anybody, at least, they were acting in concert for a common purpose, and everyone was eager to seek revenge.

“But the number of the bolts named bullet is limited, so each of us only has a few,” the knight said while spreading out his hands. “I hope that everyone could go easy on them and fire at a close range.”

Marwayne cast the knight a glance of approval. His name is Fueler, a local from the Western Region. Marwayne knew that he was pretty smart, and it appeared that Fueler had already grasped the key to the victory. Marwayne was thinking of recruiting him later for his own use.

“Don’t worry,” Marwayne said confidently. “The Graycastle men don’t have many bullets either. The northwestern part of the Kingdom of Wolfheart is mountainous, which restrains their mobility. Also, they’ll let us approach them. Their goal is to get refugees out of here, isn’t it?”

Everybody sneered.

That was right. Since the Graycastle men came here for people, they would definitely not abandon the lambs that voluntarily came up to them. However, they did not know that wolves could also hide among those innocent lambs. It only took a second for a hunter to turn into a prey. By the time the Graycastle men discovered the danger, it would have been too late.

Then, they could disguise themselves as the Graycastle soldiers and looted the towns on their way back. In that case, people would stop believing the Graycastle men, and this immigration campaign would, as a matter of course, fail.

“I’ve let the Graycastle men know that we’ll go with them. I believe we’ll soon hear back from them. Let’s fight this battle out, and all the resources and food gained from this battle will be yours!” Marwayne proclaimed as he rose. “This is a great opportunity to avenge yourselves and gain lands and wealth! You have my words. It’s time for the Graycastle soldiers to pay for what they have done, everyone!”

Chapter 1280: Disguise

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

When Fish Ball ascended the crest of the mountain, his view suddenly expanded.

Orange flowers carpeted the field and formed a glaring contrast with the road that meandered through the mountain. Wind rustled the flowers and refreshed the exhausted travelers.

Against the sea of flowers loomed a small town, which was the destination of their trip, Frost Town.

It was his sixth time climbing over the mountains.

Although Fish Ball was the leader of the machine gun squad, he was also a soldier of the First Army. After receiving the instruction to expedite the evacuation process, like many soldiers, Fish Ball came to rescue refugees.

He had not encountered any demons so far on this route, possibly because the Red Mist had not reached here or because the demons did not really want to waste their time on those refugees. Anyhow, the more people he brought to Neverwinter, the better.

There were nearly 1,000 people following him.

According to common practices, the army would first pitch their tents outside the town and get in touch with the refugees before they sent them to Neverwinter in group. The First Army had warned the residents during their first visit not to travel to the south alone, as the trip could be dangerous. They asked the residents to wait for the Graycastle army to retrieve them.

Nevertheless, not everyone would listen. In fact, Fish Ball had met many desperate refugees who had run out of food on their way. For those who were less fortunate, they simply died in the mountain on their own.

But this time, Fish Ball found that things were a little different.

From the mountain, he, surprisingly, saw many people in Frost Town.

“Did some major city fall?” the squad scout Hanson whistled. “So many refugees in just around 10 days. We’ll be very busy in the next few days.”

Fish Ball also felt excited. Only about 1,000 people had departed for Neverwinter over the past one to two months. It seemed that the number of the refugees this time would exceed that of the previous trip.

Although Fish Ball did not understand why these refugees chose to come to this small town down the valley instead of other more accessible cities, he still had the obligation to send them to safer places.

At this thought, the army sped up.

Going downhill was apparently much faster than going uphill. About half an hour later, the unit reached the encampment in Frost Town. Many refugees had noticed them, and they soon swarmed up to the street and rushed toward the army.

“Well, they’re in… such a haste,” someone joked.

“Didn’t we tell them to wait in town?”

“Perhaps they ran out of food and want some from us?”

Most of the soldiers held the same opinion.

“If there’s a catastrophe in a neighboring city, then it makes sense that these people don’t have food,” Fish Ball commented and quickly made the decision. “But it’s hard for us to count them and maintain the order. We have to stop these people. I need ten soldiers to help me set up the checkouts. The others shall keep them in order.”

Fish Ball knew there would be serious consequences if they failed to stop the refugees. If they all rushed forward at once, those refugees would be no different than bandits.

Most of the time, there was a very thin line between refugees and bandits.

“Yes, sir!”

The soldiers were soon dispersed. All of them grasped their guns.

As the refugees slowly approached, they could see them more clearly.

Fish Ball raised the amplifier and turned up the volume to the maximum. “This is the rescue team of the First Army of Graycastle. Please stay calm and stop right away to wait for further instructions. We have ample food and medicine, but you’ll need to cooperate. Again, stop where you are, otherwise, we’ll take hard measures!”

Some people hesitated but soon resumed to run, as though something were pushing them from behind.

Fish Ball frowned. He then asked his team member to fire into the air as a warning.

Just then, Hanson whistled.

“Hmm.”

“What’s the matter?” Fish Ball asked.

“Leader, they look a bit strange…” Hanson said while watching through the telescope. “Have you seen any refugees take a roll of cloth with them before?”

“A roll of cloth?” Fish Ball echoed in bewilderment. He grabbed the telescope from Hanson and saw about 300 meters away, these refugees were running toward them. He could roughly tell what they were wearing and carrying. Like Hanson had said, most of them were carrying a roll of cloth on the back or at the waist. It was indeed very strange.

Refugees would normally take all their belongings with them, and the First Army would usually ask them to abandon heavy luggage and take light items that would not cause inconvenience to the trip, such as gold royals. Generally, the army would not interfere with refugees’ personal affairs. During the past two months, Fish Ball had seen various strange personal items, but it was his first time seeing rolls of cloth.

The more he looked at them, the more strange they appeared.

These refugees were all in rags, but surprisingly, they were all wearing shoes. Their clothes were not old or worn at all. Instead, it appeared to Fish Ball that the clothes had been made look old just very recently.

Now, the two parties were only 200 meters away from each other.

“Bang!”

His team member again issued the warning.

The crowd was immediately dispersed, and the next moment, Fish Ball froze to the ground. The shot frightened some refugees at the front, who unrolled the cloth and revealed the rifle that the First Army usually used underneath!

Soon, all of them revealed their weapons from underneath their cloth. They were carrying all kinds of weapons, including swords and tridents.

Fish Ball suddenly realized that this was a trap!

“Retreat to the encampment!” Fish Ball yelled at his team members. “Run!”

No sooner had he finished than the disguised refugees started to fire.

Bullets whistled past Fish Ball and exhaled dusts and earth. The other nine soldiers from the First Army finally realized what had happened and hurried to the campsite while lowering their heads.

The unit had camped their several times. Although there were no trenches or blockhouses, they had built fortresses. These fortresses constructed with sand and stones were designed to fight demons, but now, they had to rely on them to avoid the attack of the refugees.

By the time Fish Ball reached the fortresses, all his team members had crouched down. They were now utterly outnumbered, for there were more than 40 enemies while they only got nine people. Fish Ball’s heart leaped to his throat when he thought of the possibility that all of them would be shot dead unprepared on the battlefield.

He seized Hanson’s arm and said, “Go see how everyone’s doing, now!”

Hanson immediately left, and Fish Ball held up the gun and aimed at the running “refugees”.

No… they were not real refugees but nobles that had submitted to the demons!

Only the demons could obtain so many weapons from the First Army!

“Damn it!” Fish Ballswore under his breath. He had never expected that his own kind would disguise as refugees and set up such a nasty trap. Did they not know who they were helping?

In a few minutes, Hanson came back, which was faster than Fish Ball had thought. Hanson reported, “Everyone’s fine, except one soldier. He’s got minor injuries, but he can still fight.”

Fish Ball stiffened for a second. “Just one person?” He remembered that the “refugees” had shot quite fiercely.

“Yes,” Hanson confirmed, looking hugely relieved. “We’re pretty lucky. Now, everyone has returned to their positions. We’ll fight to the last!”

Chapter 1281: A Deadlock

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“That’s right. Fight to the last.”

The campsite was against hills, so it was impossible to retreat to the crest against the gunfire. As each rescue team acted separately, they would not get reinforcements anytime soon. Considering the precarious situation, Fish Ball judged that the best way to repel the enemies was to hold onto this encampment.

Not only far outnumbered, most of the soldiersonly brought food and clothes with them. There was not even a single HMG on the campsite, so they were not able to defeat the enemies with advanced, long-distance weapons.

This was going to be a “50 to 1,000” situation.

Fish Balladmitted that he was scared at this moment, but he was no longer the coward who used to only think about escapes. As the unit leader, he had the obligation to get his whole team out of the dilemma.

He must have those refugeespay the price before he died here.

Apparently, his team members were also thinking the same thing, for they were now letting the enemies approach them. Currently, the two parties were less than 200 meters from each other.

Since they had limited ammunition, the most efficient way to kill the “refugees” was to shoot at a close range.

In the meantime, the enemies would also fire more accurately as the distance between the two parties shortened. This method was, therefore, a double-edged sword, and at present, willpower determined everything.

Fish Ball waited for nearly a minute for the enemies to approach. Finally, they were at 100 meters from the First Army soldiers. Within this distance, he could already see the faces of these traitors through the telescope. His suspicion was thus confirmed. Unlike windswept and weary refugees, most of them looked poised and self-assured. There was not the slightest sign of reluctance in their act of demeanor.

He did not have to worry about having innocent blood shed anymore.

Fish Ball aimed at the enemy at the very front and pulled the trigger.

His team members also fired at the same time.

In an instant, gunshots rented the air above the encampment. As the enemies at the front fell, the rest of them all slowed down and began to shoot at the First Army as well. Fish Ball was not sure whether these refugeeshad learned to use the firearms by themselves or they had received some sort of training from the demons. Anyway, both parties started to shoot each other.

Just at that moment, the enemies pushed a few two-wheeled trailers covered with cloth to the front.

Fish Ball was familiar with this type of transportation tool. Compared to a carriage or a mule, a trailer was more often used for moving and carrying heavy cargo. He had thought that the enemies used these trailers simply to make themselves look more like refugees, and he was surprised to see that they had not abandoned those props yet.

It was not until the enemies uncovered the cloth that Fish Ball realized that it was a Mark I type HMG underneath!

The enemies began to fire.

The rain of bullets immediately suppressed the attack of the First Army. It appeared that the bullets thatthe enemieswere usingwere all tracers, and the HMG was much more accurate than bolt rifles. The whole encampment was thus stirred. Dust and mud flew in all directions. Thanks to the fortresses, the soldiers from the First Army were still able to fight back.

Fortunately, the enemies did not fire from far away but carried the HMG along as they charged. The machine gun was, therefore, only around 200 meters away from the defensive line. Since the First Army was fairly scattered, the enemies had time to position.

“Hanson!” Fish Ball yelled.

Hanson gestured that he understood and ran toward the edge of the fortresses while carrying his gun.

The First Army seldom ran into a disadvantageous position because of the lack of weapons. According to the Operation Manual, once the army was short of ammunition, the soldiers should immediately request for the support of the artillery at the rear or concentrate on suppressing the enemies’ gunfire. Apparently, in the current situation, the only thing that the unit could do was to shoot directly to deter the enemies.

While the enemies were reloading the HMG, Fish Ball and his team members fired ferociously to distract the enemies. Hanson also successfully shot down the gunners on the trailers. Those who attempted to clamber onto the trailers were immediately shot dead one by one.

Without the support of the HMG, the charging enemies were soon repulsed, and the battle went back to the beginning.

“Damn it. Why haven’t they taken the campsite yet?” Marwayne complained irritably as he looked up at the sinking sun while stomping impatiently. “Viscount Narnos, your guys are all cravens, aren’t they? What takes them so long to crush a unit? If they can’t win by the end of the day, we’ll let the Graycastle men escape right under our noses!”

As the commanders, the nobles did not have to fight at the front in person like their squires and mercenaries. Plus, the Graycastle men never followed the rules of war between nobles. They never reserved their power or exchanged captives. The nobles knew perfectly well the arrogant attitude of the Graycastle men. Charging at the front would not bring them any honor or respect but only a miserable defeat.

“They’re doing their best, and your men aren’t any better than mine either,” Narnos retorted indignantly. “You have the greatest army, but they’re all at the rear. If your main force moved a little bit forward to the front, we would have taken the encampment a long time ago.”

“You — ” Marwayne was at a loss for words. He rested his eyes upon the front again and promised to himself that he would seek revenge later.

“Once I become the King of Everwinter, you’ll pay for your insolence!”

However, right now, Marwayne knew that hemust win. Otherwise, the Sky Lord would abandon him.

He did not understand why the battle took so long.

Everything went well as planned. To fool the Graycastle men, they did not set up the ambush in the townor surround their encampment but awaited in this valley so that both parties would have a clear view of the opponent’s force. He had considered every single detail of this operation to make sure that they would not blow their cover. He had even killed all the townsmen who might possibly give away their true identity.

In fact, just as he had planned, the Graycastle men did not raise any suspicion until they were several hundred meters from each other. The nobles had far more firearms and soldiers than their opponent, and this battle should have ended in a second. Whydid they still not gain the campsite?

Even if every one of the Graycastle soldier possessed a weapon, there were only 50 of them, but the alliance army of the nobles had more than 200 guns!

Marwayne was indebted to a belief that the Graycastle soldiers should have been vanquished under such an unfavorable condition.

But the reality seemed to be exactly the opposite.

The alliance army could not move any further from the hill, and for many times, they had been repelled by the gunfire of the Graycastle soldiers. Their attack, however, had not weakened the Graycastle men at all, as though the enemies were possessed of an unusual power that enabled them to operate several guns at the same time.

The flintlocks that Marwayne had put great faith in were almost ineffective. They not only failed to break the spirit of the Graycastle soldiers but a lot of times, they wounded their own soldiers. From the top of the hill, Marwayne could see bodies litter around the flintlocks, so nobody had the courage to operate them anymore.

If things went on like that, everything he had dreamedof would remain as a dream.

The Kingdom of Everwinter did not possess technologies to produce bullets. If he could not obtain sufficient ammunition after this battle, he would have no chance to win the Graycastle men again.

“Don’t worry, your lordship,” Fueler comforted. “As far as I see, the enemies fire less frequently now, which indicates that they’re running out of ammunition. Just in a few minutes, we’ll fight this battle out in the traditional way. Remember that the Graycastle men only have flintlocks, but we have everything.”

“But in that case, we won’t be able to get more ammunition from them,” Marwayne thought to himself in anguish. He would have to ask the Sky Lord for more. The most pressing task for him now was to eliminate these Graycastle soldiers as soon as possible. Marwayne thus summoned a guard and ordered, “Tell them that the reward I promised earlier will double if they win this battle, and the first one who enters the enemies’ campsite will receive 100 gold royals!”

Chapter 1282: The Battle Is to the Strong

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Fish Ball noticed the change in the situation.

He was now betting his life on this battle, but, surprisingly, the enemies were weaker than he had expected.

When he had been fighting against the demons on the Fertile Plains back then, he could hardly breathe, and all he could do was to fire. His entire body had gone numb. However, at present, he could still keep an eye on his team members and the enemies, and had the ability to think about what step the opponent would possibly take next.

As the enemies were repelled several times, their move significantly slowed down.

The First Army shot less frequently. To save ammunition, they only fired when the alliance army charged. The last shot was about an hour ago.

The consequence would be unbearable for the alliance army if this “deadlock” continued under the current circumstances when there was no reinforcement.The First Army was on the higher land under the protection of the fortresses in a more advantageous firing position.

Fish Ball did not understand why the commander of the enemies chose to stand with his arms folded. Unlike a traditional battle where soldiers had to fight at a close range, this battle was apparently more dangerous and intense, for the soldiers could be shot anytime. The commander’s indifference would definitely have a negative impact on the soldiers’ morale.

In fact, the alliance army had commenced to retreat.Fish Ballhad witnessed that some soldiers had retreated somewhere around 100 meters farther, and the whole frontier was on the brink of a collapse.

This fact indicated that the alliance army had just been built temporarily. The soldiers, in general, lacked trust and cooperation.

In addition to that, Fish Ball had also noticed that the enemies were not really good at using flintlocks. They were simply imitating the First Army in a very clumsy way, failing to make the best of use out of the weapons.

Otherwise, the First Army would not have been able to hold up for so long.

It was incredible that out of the 10 soldiers, only five sustained injuries, and nobody was killed.

He could not attribute this outcome totally to luck anymore.

“Can someone pass me some bullets? Mine ran out!”

“Same here. I only have one cartridge left.”

“Leader, what should we do next?” Hanson trotted up to Fish Ball while bending his head. “No enemy is around the machine gun anymore. Shall we retreat tonight?”

Fish Ball stared up at the sky. It was now around 5:00 in the afternoon, and the sun sank faster than usual in fall. Within one hour and a half, darkness would creep in. By that time, it would be a lot safer for them to operate, and they could possibly even turn their back against the enemies.

However, Fish Ball always hesitated when it came to a retreat.

It was true that thefiring accuracy would significantly drop at night, but the First Army would not be able to use the firearms either. More importantly, if the enemies launched an attack again and came after them, could they successfully repel them once more?

Hadthey currently had sufficient ammunition, they could have then probably retreated before the enemies got prepared fora second attack. However, if things went on like this, the nobles would soon notice that the First Armyshot less frequently andtherebypredict their next move.

Also, two people sustained relatively serious injuries, which further slowed the unitdown.

Fish Ball could not abandon his team members.

He hesitated for a while and finally made up his mind. Then, he said, “Ask everyone to come here. I want to say something.”

A moment later, Hanson brought the other team members.

The enemies seemed to have not noticed that the First Army had confined their shooting range. They were still lying on the ground on their stomachs while firing occasionally. Fish Ball was thus more certain about his decision.

He briefly talked about the current situation and then surveyed the whole team. “His Majesty often says that an attack is the best defense. If we could defeat these nobles, we don’t need to worry about them coming back anymore. However, if we retreat now, we’d leave them a chance to fight back. So, it’s time to make a choice. We could either let the enemies determine our fate or control our own destiny. I want to hear your opinions on that.”

“Leader, do you mean… that we shall attack them instead?” Hanson asked in surprise. “They have far more people than us.”

“I thought about that already. They do outnumber us, but most of them don’t want to fight anymore. They just haven’t realized it when firing at a distance. If we could quash their most powerful troop, we could possibly break their spirit!”

“But we don’t have much ammunition left…”

“According to the Operation Manual, the First Army doesn’t always rely on weapons,” Fish Ball said solemnly.

A silence descended on the campsite. Hanson was the first one to speak. “I’m with the leader.”

“Me too, leader. I want everyone to stick together.”

“Whether we leave or not, we should always act together!”

“Issue your command, leader!”

The soldiers shouted.

Fish Ball nodded solemnly. He would not have made such a decision had this occurred in the past. After serving in the army for four years, he did feel that something had changed.

“I see that you aren’t a craven now.”

A bright, silvery voice came to him.

Fish Ball took a deep breath and proclaimed slowly, “Everyone, install the bayonet!”

Although their weapons had upgraded from the traditional flintlock to the bolt rife, and the structure of the gun had changed a lot, the bayonet had always been there, only that it now functioned better.

The soldiers thus all drew out their swords and inserted them into the grooves.

Fish Ball slid the last clip into the bore, raised his arm and yelled, “Follow me!”

He rushed out of the fortresses first.

The other team members followed at his heels and streaked toward the enemies closest to them!

The enemies had apparently no idea what was going on. Many of them did not even rise but simply shot at the First Army mechanically.

Fish Ball was prepared to get shot, but the pain he had been waiting for did not come. It was not until they had covereda distance of 100 meters that the enemies finally stood bolt upright, rooted to the ground, with their rifles in their hands, totally dumbfounded.

Fish Ball stabbed the enemies with his bayonet in the way he was trained.

“Go!”

His team members followed and rushed toward the enemies.

The air was filled with the soldiers’ shoutings.

Fish Ball stabbed one soldier, shot another dead, and then turned around to stab the third one until he noticed that there was no enemy around him anymore.

The alliance army had started to flee.

They had probably never anticipated that the First Army would come out of their campsite at this moment and fight at a close range. They could not stand the intense battle anymore.

The battle was to the strong.

The alliance army was soon flattened after several weak attempts of resistance. The panic was infectious. When the soldiers at the front began to retreat, the ones at the rear all dropped their weapons and fled. Many people fell, rolled down the hill and hit the soldiers running at the front.

The First Army thus easily obtained the HMG and started to fire at the running soldiers. The enemies moved their two legs as fast as they could. Had the First Army had enough ammunition, these soldiers would probably have not been able to escape.

Fish Ball did not stop until his two legs gave away.

The enemies on the hill all knelt down, raised their arms and yielded. The nobles at the rear were the first ones to leave. Fish Ball could not see a single one of them now.

He clenched his fists, feeling a sense of achievement steal through him.

Before he could savor the victory, his team member rushed toward him andpushed him down to the ground. “Leader, we won!”

“Long live His Majesty!”

“Long live the First Army!”

Multiple hands reached out to him, and Fish Ball was thrown up in the air.

Yes, they had won.

Nothing was better than seeing everyone alive.

Fish Ball spread out his hands in the sunset and also yelled with his soldiers in excitement.

Chapter 1283: The Source of Information

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

At the Sedimentation Bay in the Kingdom of Wolfheart.

The news of the victory of this counter ambush soon reached Iron Axe.

Iron Axe immediately dispatched a letter through the carrier pigeon, in which he not only heaped praises on Fish Ball for his excellent leadership skill but also instructed the unit to stay safe while waiting for the reinforcement.

Although the enemy in this battle was simply an alliance army organized by nobles, their quick reaction and outstanding performance set a great example for the whole army. Advertising this unusual victory would definitely raise the morale of the First Army in a more significant way than continuing to retrieve refugees, especially when the whole army was in the process of retreating.

Not a long time ago, Iron Axe had actually received two pieces of bad news, one of which was that the soldiers in the Red Mist area were thwarted by the local nobles who had agreed to help the demons.

According to the report, these knights from the Kingdom of Everwinter were currently attacking the units responsible for retrieving refugees. Apparently, these knights, being also human,were better at hindering the evacuation campaign than the demons. As it was quite dangerous for the First Army to advance to the depth of the Red Mist area, most of the time the soldiers simply stayed outside the Red Mist zone. As such, there were fewer people actually helping evacuate the cities.

The other bad news was that the demons’ attack became more fierce. First of all, a large number of Devilbeasts flew out of the Red Mist zone in the southeast and off to the Archduke Island. Then, the garrison on the island got prepared for the upcoming war and suspended the service of marine transportation.

However, the Devilbeasts, incredibly, disappeared from the sky above the two outposts and reappeared above a temporary evacuation unit on the island. Very unfortunately, however, the unit had just been informed that the Devilbeast would head to the east and was, therefore, retreating as fast as they could at that moment. They thus ran right into the demons.

Although the unit resisted ferociously, they were vanquished. Iron Axe had yet received a full statistical report, but the reinforcement told him that nearly 2,000 refugees had been attacked. The army had lost at least 100 people.

Considering the substantial loss, Iron Axe had no choice but to slow down the campaign.

The two incidents created a chain reaction. The General Staff had indeed foreseen the possibility of a betrayal by the nobles, but they had not expected that it would happen that fast. The noble families in the Kingdom of Everwinter had been fighting for nearly two years for the throne, but they now, ironically, united together because of the demons.

It was obvious that the immigration campaign was drawing to its end. Now, the First Army needed to recuperate and defend the Red Mist zone on the border.

There were approximately 5,000 soldiers at the Cage Mountain and the Sedimentation Bay, which was not even 1/6 of the total force. Iron Axe did not know what the demons’ military force was. Before he had that information, he could not lose any more soldiers.

What Iron Axe was worried about most was that the demons might attack the unmanned areas before the First Army assembled. In that case, they would not only lose these new territories but also those they had occupied.

There was no such things as armored train that could serve as a “mobile fortress” in the Kingdom of Wolfheart.

Just then, a soldier entered the study and reported, “Sir, the chief of the General Staff, Ms. Edith Kant, just arrived at the port.”

“Really?” Iron Axe said while knitting his brows. This was such good timing, for he was just hoping that Edith could give him some advice. “Great. I’ll meet her at the port.”

At the dock, Iron Axe saw that the Pearl of the Northern Region was surrounded by a group of clerks in the General Staff. Everyone looked profoundly relieved at the sight of her. For a moment, they had completely forgotten how she used to torment them.

Within a year after she assumed the office of the chief of the General Staff, Edith was widely acknowledged and highly respected among her subordinates.

Iron Axe was impressed with the great difference between Edith,the daughter of a former duke and the nobles in the Kingdom of Everwinter and the Kingdom of Wolfheart.

“Mr. commander-in-chief,” Edith said while staring at Iron Axe after she bowed. “It has been a long time since we last saw each other. I hope my clerks didn’t create you too much trouble.”

“They all did a good job,” Iron Axe replied as he administered a military salute as a return. Since he and Edith had the same rank, their communication was always straightforward without any unncessary formalities. In fact, apart from Roland and Lady Silvermoon, Edith was the only person that Iron Axe was willing to speak with voluntarily.

“In other words, they didn’t give you any pleasant surprise?” Edith said while shrugging and then turned to her clerks. “It seems that your performance isn’t very satisfactory.”

Iron Axe curled up his lips. Miss Pearl of the Northern Region always had a sharp tongue. He thus said, “If we could win the war, they aren’t that bad.”

Edith did not insist on the topic but said, “By the way, I brought the new weapon created by His Majesty based on the latest intelligence. Are you interested in it?”

Iron Axe’s face lit up. He replied immediately, “Of course. Please lead the way.”

They thus went to the heavily guarded unloading area, which had already been sealed off by the soldiers. Huge wooden boxes were coming off the ship and were placed neatly at a corner.

Many cases had been open, revealing the weapons covered in parchment paper.

Iron Axe soon noticed a small cannon.

“That’s the one,” Edith said with a smile. “This 75mm-caliber cannon is the most expensive firearm among all. His Majesty wants it to fill the blank between the mortar and the Longsong Cannon. No witch is required for its shipment. A horse or two people would suffice. Also, it’s portable, and another person can carry the shells.”

“This reminds me of the original field artillery,” Iron Axe said with a nod and immediately figured out what this light weapon was used for. Compared to the anti-demon grenade and the mortar that had a relatively short shooting range, this new cannon could be used to attack the robust Spider Demon. With this weapon, the soldiers at the front could immediately take some measures against the Spider Demon without necessarily building a battlement for the artillery.

“As for the new rifle there, it’s a semi-auto weapon,” Edith explained as she proceeded. “The testing result is pretty good. Two or three rifles could be as powerful as a heavy machine gun. You must know the person who created this. He’s the battalion commander of the Artillery Banttalion, Van’er. Although His Majesty later modified the weapon, the gun is named after Van’er.”

“But this is only a substitute. We’re currently in the process of producing a real automatic gun and will send you the final product once it’s ready.”

“The one farthest to you is the latest anti-demon grenade. It’s caliber is much larger than the previous one. I believe that the Ministry of Chemical Industry has improved it.”

The group was gradually dispersed. By the time Iron Axe reached the edge of the dumpsite, only he and Edith were there.

“What’s the matter? Did the battle not go well?” Edith asked suddenly.

It was a second later before Iron Axe realized that Edith had separated him from the crowd deliberately.

“You knew?”

“You wouldn’t have greeted me at the dock in such a haste if that wasn’t the case.”

“I know I can’t fool you,” Iron Axe sighed and told Edith the recent news and what he was worrying about. “Before the transportation resumed, we still need a few months to assemble the army and gather ammunition. The demons could attack us anytime. Even if Miss Sylvie, Lightning and Maggie come, they can’t monitor everything. The war is about to begin, but we have little information of our enemy. This isn’t a good sign.”

“I see,” Edith said meditatively. “I can’t do anything about the transportation, but it isn’t hard to gather intelligence.”

“You had an idea already?”

“You can put that way. You’re only thinking about the First Army, and that’s why you feel it difficult.” Edith said slowly, “The demons used nobles to attain their ends, but they’ve also created us an opportunity. As long as those cities are not evacuated, we would be able to infiltrate the enemy!”

Truth seemed to suddenly dawn on Iron Axe. He said, “You’re not talking about the First Army soldiers, are you?”

“Of course not. Soldiers are not good at those stuff. Rats and civilians are better options. I prefer natives, so they won’t easily expose themselves. There are tons of ways to have them work for you,” Edith said smilingly. “By the way, didn’t you receive a black card earlier? Try to contact them.”

Chapter 1284: Infiltration

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

When Roland received the report jointly written by the commander of the First Army and the chief of the General Staff, he immediately thought of the spy movies he had watched.

This was apparently a very feasible plan.

He even thought more about the plan than Edith.

Spy was an ancient profession, and it had various names in different times, but the spy Roland was familiar with were those in WWI and WWII. Early intelligence collection was simply a two-way communication without a systematic organization. As the government tightened their control over people, spies and agents found it increasingly hard to escape the scrutiny, and that was the time when a well-organized system was established.

This also meant that in a feudal country ruled by nobles, spies could be anywhere. Once those agents received some professional training and learned cunningtricksto protect themselves, they would never be found even if the whole city was turned upside down.

They were like shadows slinking in the city, whosepresencenever raised the awareness of the people who received their tips. Even Nightingale would fail to get anything out of them upon an interrogation.

Roland thus approved the proposal at once.

However, he was not planning to entrust this task totally to Edith. This, nonetheless, had nothing to do with trust. Intelligence collection could be time-consuming. He would rather Edith focus more on the big picture of the planthan a specific project.Otherwise, itwould be a total waste of Edith’s talent.

He would need a professional to deal with this matter.

Roland spread open a letter and put Hill Fawkes at the top.

The Kingdom of Dawn had been quite peaceful recently. This former ringmaster must be very bored at the moment.

After Nightingale handed the letter to Honey, Roland started to consider about another thing.

That was an intelligence gathering network.

Before, he had only needed to take care of the war and political matters within Graycastle. However, ever since the expedition to Taquila, it had taken the carrier pigeon a much longer time to commute. Thanks to the support of the “Seagull”, Roland was still able to receive information in a timely manner.

Nevertheless, they were now waging a war in the Kingdom of Wolfheart and the Kingdom of Everwinter, and Rolandnoticeda significant delay in communication.

For example, the report he was currently reading had been written a week ago and had been shipped by sea. Although animal messengers would make things a lot faster, he would still need to wait for at least two or three days. More importantly, Honey did not have a lot of messengers that could fly more than 1,000 kilometers. She could only control the behavior of the animals but not change it.

Plus, Honey was not powerful enough to support the communication throughout the entire Western Region even for short-distance messengers, let alone the communication throughout the whole nation and beyond Graycastle. There was actually a limit in the number of the animals she could control. Therefore, how to efficiently deliver messages was also a huge problem that needed to be solved after this intelligence gathering network was established.

Roland knew very well that the ultimate solution would be radio communication.

The telegraphtechnologies were simple, but like telephones, the communication through telegraphs relied largely on reception. Normally, the signal could only cover a distance of 100 kilometers without a repeater like an electron tube that could amplify signals.

However, if he couldinvent an electron tube, he would also be able to create radios. There was no electromagnetic pollution in this era. The sound produced by tuned electromagnetic waves was very similar to the crying of a baby. He would only need to erect an antenna on the top of the Impassable Mountain Range to receive messages thousands of kilometers away.

If he could successfully create radios, it would only take a few minutes to transmit the report from the front to his office. If every soldier in the army was equipped with a portable radio, that would be even more helpful to the war than the Radiation Project.

Nevertheless, Roland had no idea where to start and how.

Perhaps, it was time to ask the Design Bureau of Graycastle to work on more projects.

Roland entered the Dream World at night. After he sent Zero off to school, he drove to the construction site of the Clover Group in the southern suburb.

Garde was indeed an efficient businessman. He fulfilled his promise at once. Not only did he authorize Roland to manage the plant, but the plant was refurbished as well. The rusty wall was painted, and the facilities were renewed.

Had the Clover Group not insisted on demolishing the apartment building, Roland would have loved to deal with Garde and conducted more business with him.

He parked his vehicle and found the yard outside the plant look a bit strange. Normally, few people came here, but today, there were a lot of workers.

He also hearddeep, heavyroar of machineries.

Roland quickly passed through the crowd and saw a queer catepillar machine in front of him. Only the lower part of the machine was currently completed. There was nothing special about the catepillar and the wheels per se. What attracted these workers was the distinctive steam-powered piston at the top and another tractor that produced steam.

Roland burst into a laugh.

So that was Master Xie’s idea. To minimize the impact of the imaginary boiler and water tank, he installed this part of the machine onto a tractor so that he could test out both of them at the same time. The tractor not only had to run on its own but it alsoneeded to power the catepillar machine. Th principle was so similar to that of the “solar torch light” that would only work when there was light.

“Ahem… hey, boss,” Master Xie, having realized the awkwardness of the machine, greeted Roland in embarrassment.

Roland praised him heartily, “Good job. This is exactly what I want!”

He came here to check the progress of the project. Last time when he had come here,Master Xiehad onlycompleted theframe of the tractor. But now,the tractorwas finished. Master Xie indeed had put a lot of efforts into it.

“R-really?” Master Xie said while scratching his scalp. “Are you sure your collector friends are interested in this kind of thing?”

“Did you make the parts of the tester with machine tools?”

“Yes, I can assure you about that,” Master Xie replied quickly as he massaged his hands. “But I bought the tractor, the boiler and the water tank. They’re all second-handed, and it cost me around ￥300,000…”

“Money isn’t a problem,” Roland dismissed his concern while waving his hand. The Clover Group would pay everything. “As long as they were manually made, my friend will be satisfied. Keep up the great work. Once the deal is successfully closed, I’ll double your salary as a bonus!”

Chapter 1285: Five Pairs of Road Wheels

Translator: Transn __ Editor: Transn

Master Xie’s face instantly split into a bright smile, but the woman next to him heaved an almost inaudible sigh.

Roland naturally noticed her. After he started to absorb the magic cores in the Dream World, his power continuously grew, and he also became more sensitive about the subtle changes around him. Although few people noticed the woman, Roland still caught sight of her in the corner of his eyes.

This woman was the secretary and fiancial adviser sent by Garde. Her name was Qingqing, and she had just graduated from a very prominent university. Qingqing was a pretty, talented and efficient worker, a gifted woman, so to speak. Only she knew that the Clover Group bore all the expenses incurred by this project, and the “actual boss” did not have to pay anything.

Perhaps, Qingqing thought Roland was taking advantage of the corporation, so she did not have a very high opinion of him.

Roland, however, did not care about that. He simply needed to give her a raise as well so that she would not complain anymore.

“Of course, this is the joint work of all the staff,” Roland said while smiling at the secretary. “If we succeed, I’ll double the salary for everyone in the plant!”

“Yes, quite right. You’re very considerate, boss,” Master Xie rejoined while nodding vigorously.

“No… This is not what I meant….” Qingqing had not expected that Roland would see through her mind. Abashed, she said, “I was just wondering when the corporation could profit…”

Roland waved his hand and said, “We will one day. Don’t worry. All of my friends have great ambitions. The corporation will definitely profit from this project. Just wait for the raise.”

“Awesome. Awesome,” Master Xie said as though he had realized his long-term dream. All the wrinkles on his smiling face were smoothened.

“By the way,” Roland said while looking toward Qingqing. “I have a new project to work on. Come with me to the office.”

“Boss,” Master Xie stopped Roland when the latter was about to leave. “Do you have any other requirements for this tractor? For example, the style and the color?”

It appeared that Master Xie really believed that Roland was making props. Roland shook his head in amusement and said, “As long as it functions well, I don’t care about such things very much. But…”

“Please go ahead.”

“If possible, I wish the final products could have five pairs of road wheels.”

“Not a problem at all,” Master Xie promised while patting his chest. “I thought about the mobility of the machine when I designed it. Place the matter in my hand.”

As all the workers in the plant ran out to watch the testing of the tractor, the whole plant became exceptionally quiet. Roland noticed that Qingqing had distanced from him after they entered the workshop. She had moved a little farther from him, and the distance between the two increased from the initial two meters to five meters.

Roland was quite amused at her action. It seemed that Garde had not told her that Roland was actually a martialist. Otherwise, she should have known that when a martialist attempted to sexually harrass a girl, the girl would not be able to escape even if she was 50 meters away from the former.

But Roland did not care about his personal image among his employees, as he only wanted his workers to work hard.

Roland sat straight in his seat after getting into the messy office. He jumped right into the business and said, “Well, I have a friend…”

_ “Here it goes.” _

Qingqing thought to herself. Every time he talked about a new project, he started with a friend of his. Who would like to squander thousands of hundreds of dollars on tons of rubbish? Qingqing knew that some wealthy people did have strange hobbies, but the boss in front of her did not look remotely like a successful entrepreneur from an affluent family. She was confident of her own judgement.

She graduated from a top university and knew a lot of wealthy people, but she had never seen anyone dress so simple as the boss. True rich people always treated themselves well even if they wanted to keep a low profile. They might purchase clothes by an indie brand, but what they wore and used must be expensive andof good quality. Many young people tended not to, in fact, exhibit their wealth to the public, but this Mr. Roland was wearing the cheapest clothes normally sold by street vendors, without wearing any accessories. Even his vehicle was a battered mini van. He was not keeping a low profile at all…

He was simply poor!

How was that possible that he had wealthy friends?

Qingqing was hired by the Clover Group, the biggest corporation in this city, right after her graduation. She wanted to add some impressing work experience to her resume, but she had not expected that her boss would send her to this small factory to look after so many weird projects. She even started to suspect whether Mr. Garde was scammed, or whether he intended to use this plant to do some shady business.

She was astonished after hearing Roland mention radio communication. Qingqing massaged her forehead while letting out a sigh. This kind of walkie-talkie only cost less than ￥100 online, and they could also directly purchase an antique telegraph machine without necessarily making it by themselves. However, Roland wanted to produce them from scratch like the tractor. Everything must be hand-maded, including all the parts.

This was purely wasting money!

“I don’t need professionals. New graduates or people who love radio technologies would do. You can set up a room outside the plant as their office so that I don’t have to travel back and forth,” Roland explained in detail. “Whatever equipment they need, just approve it. Remember, however, that all the parts should be produced here. They don’t have to be perfect though. In fact, the worse the quality is, the better. Make them as desolate anddilapidatedas possible. My friend likes that kind of stuff.”

“That’s different than giving a raise. I’ll have to report to Mr. Garde.”

“That’s fine,” Roland said indifferently. “I think he’ll agree.”

Just then, his cell phone rang.

It was from the Martialist Association.

Roland picked up the phone after Qingqing left.

“Hello, Mr. Roland,” Rock, the Defender’s calming voice came over the line. “I have a new task for you. Are you available to pay a visit to Greenleaf Sanatorium this afternoon?”

SincetheDesign Bureau of Graycastle entirely relied on Rock’s support, Roland could not refuse the request.

AsRoland had eliminated the magic creatures coming out of the Erosion last time,the Fallen Evils had been pretty quite recently as if they had sensed the danger and withdrawn from this city. As such, the Taquila witches did not find many Fallen Evils to fight.

Roland believed that thingswere not that simple.

The Fallen Evils were aiming for the Forces of Nature of the Awakened, through which they could further weaken the Dream World.With the attack of the Prism City and the beginning of the Martialist Contest, many martialists had gathered here, so the Fallen Evilshad no reason to leave.

It would save Roland a lot of time if the Association obtained new information regarding the Fallen Evils.

Chapter 1286: The Other World

Translator: Transn | Editor: Transn

“How are you feeling?”

Fei Yuhan asked as she entered Room 402 with a stack of books in her arms and placed the books on the nightstand.

Valkries said with a nod, “Thank you. I can walk now. The doctor says I’ll fully recover in a week.”

“That’s good. You really have excellent self-repairing ability even as a martialist,” Fei Yuhan said with a smile.

“Really?”

“The influence of the Force of Nature on each person is different. Not every martialist could recover within one month when his leg bones are crushed like yours. You probably haven’t seen any martialists sustain such severe injuries before, so you don’t know your potential.” Fei Yuhan paused for a second and said, “You should be one of the top martialists in your city, right?”

“Why do you think so?”

“My master often says that the strong one is strong in every aspect. The fact that you recover so fast means that you have a strong body and a great immune system. People like you were born to be a martialist, like me,” Fei Yuhan said flatly. “We may see who’s stronger once you recover.”

“That’s the reason you asked me to join your team?” Valkries asked, a little resigned. “You’re the genius in the Association. I don’t think you could learn anything newfrom me.”

“That’s fine. You’ve been lying in bed for a long time. Practicing with a good martialist can help you regain your power. Fallen Evils would not sympathize you because you had injuries before.”

Valkries nodded after a moment of silence and then said, “Alright then. Thank you.”

“Not a problem,” Fei Yuhan returned while curling up her lips. “By the way, I went to downtown yesterday and bought some desserts from the Cargarde Peninsula. I put them in the bag on the top of the books. I hope you like them. The food in the hospital isn’t very tasty.”

At that moment, Valkries noticed that Fei Yuhan swallowed.

People from theCargarde Peninsula did eatregular food, but it was rumored that they could not distinguish the good and the bad. Only the food grownin their native towncould satisfy their special need. Fei Yuhan had once tried their “unique” food but discovered that she could not take it.

Only a few people appreciated the taste and claimed that they were the most delicious food in the world, although the public did not really buy the idea. Therefore, only a few shops were specialized in selling food from the Cargarde Peninsula. After all, not many people lived there.

“Thank you…” Valkries said while trying not to reveal her true thought.

“That’s nothing. I’m the captain, and it’s my duty to take care of my team members,” Fei Yuhan said while waving her hand. “By the way, you do like reading.”

“Yes, I tend to do some reading when I’m bored.”

“That’s a good habit. There’s no entertainment in the sanatorium except books. If you want more books, just let me know.”

“Thanks.”

There was then an awkward silence, except for the rustling sound of the book when Valkries flipped over the pages.

Fei Yuhan looked out of the window at the scenery outside. It was a nice and clear day. A few willows dipped into the water, and the lake rippled slowly in the breezes. A group of swans were sliding across the lake, leaving white reflections in the water.

This was indeed a nice place for convalescence.

However, Fei Yuhan was watching Valkries in the corner of her eyes constantly. From the reflection on the window, she could see Valkires’ every move.

Fei Yuhan was not a kind-hearted girl and had no interest in forcing people to fight with her.

She requested a duel simply because she had discovered a month ago that this person might know Roland.

That was not quite accurate. More precisely,Valkries knew Roland, but Roland regarded her as a different person. Roland was actually testing whether she was the person he knew when he had asked those weird questions in the hospital. Fei Yuhan was pretty sure that her speculation was correct.

However, what bewildered her was that Roland had not revealed any sign of hostility against Valkries during the conversation. He was, instead, pretty relaxed, which indicated that whether Valkries was an acquaintance of his or not, she constituted no threat. Nevertheless, Valkries was, on the contrary, pretty nervous. Although she quickly concealed her emotion right after everybody enteredthe room, Fei Yuhan still sensed it.

What was her relationship with Roland and what had made her react so weirdly?

There could have been an intertwined, complicated romanticrelationship between Roland and Valkries. For example, the ardent love between the two, for some reason, turned into virulent rancor, or Valkries had undergone a series of plastic surgeries and now sought revenge after ten years had passed by, or Roland was regretted abandoning her and now wanted to be with her again. But Fei Yuhan thought that this was highly unlikely. Valkries was too good at controlling her facial expression. HadFei Yuhannot discovered it at the beginning, she would have probably be fooled too. She did not think it was a simple love story.

Fei Yuhan had been observant as a kid. After she was awakened, this ability also sharpened accordingly. Because of this, she did not have many close friends, and people were sort of afraid of her. That was why she alwayslooked so aloof and distant. She could know what others were thinking withjust aglance.

However, Roland was different. Fei Yuhan could not see through this new hunter, nor could she figure out his relationship with Valkries. Apparently, the two were hiding something, and she could not help finding out this secret.

Her suspicion was further confirmed after she talked to Valkries.

This martialist from the Cargarde Peninsula looked no different than ordinary people, but she had some strange behavior. If she had known Roland earlier, than it might explain her oddity. But after Fei Yuhan dug a little deeper, she found something incredible.

She had brought Valkries some food from her native town a few days ago, but the latter did not look particularly excited about that, although she had indeed eaten them all. However, this time, Valkries’ attitude had completely changed. This indicated that Valkries had not known what the food from her native town tasted like. She ate them simply because she was curious. What a horrible fact!

It did not make sense that aperson from the Cargarde Peninsula had not eaten food from there.

Also, Fei Yuhan had never seen Valkries play with her phone in the past one month. It was very strange that she never touched phones that so many young people were addicted to.

As for those books…

Valkries requested for many history books from the liabrary. Although reading was a good habit, Fei Yuhan did not think sheherself could read a book for a whole day without doing anything else.

The change in Valkries’ preference of food might be attributed to the lack of appetite. Being not so interested in phones might be ascribed to her quiet personality. History was probably one of her hobbies. However, there were just too many coincidences. Fei Yuhan somehow had a feeling that Valkries was familiarizing herself with this world.

She would have probably dismissed this ridiculous assumption in the past. However, when she thought of the fact that Roland had been addressed “Your Majesty”, she suddenly had a bold idea.

This idea terrified her, but she could not help thinking about it.

Everything would make sense if she thought that way.

Someone not belonging here had sneaked into this city.

They were from the other world.

Chapter 1287: Uneasiness

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

How many of them were there? What was their purpose? Were they awakened? What did the other world look like?

Fei Yuhan had no idea.

From what she saw now, they were at least not enemies. Roland had indeed killed a lot of Fallen Evils and was truly fighting against the Erosion.

The joint mission last time provided the best example. She would never forget that someone had said “Your Majesty, everyone has been knocked out” before she had lost her consciousness. She had obviously noticed that Roland was dodging her, which further confirmed her suspicion.

In other words, if these people harbored ill designs, she would not have been still alive. Roland could have killed her after he had exterminated the magic creature andhad the magic creature take allthe blame. Nobody would have ever suspected his version of the story.

Fei Yuhan thus believed that Roland was helping this world.

That was the reason that she did not report the incident to the Association. Plus, she had no solid evidence at this point.

Both Roland and Valkries were concealing their real identities. Although she did not know why, she would like to put up a show with them and keep an eye on the two people.

Just then, the telephone rang.

“… I see. Got it.”

Fei Yuhan hung up the phone and nodded at Valkries. She then said, “Mr. Rock asks me to do something for him. I have to go.”

“That’s fine. I know it’s important.”

“See you tomorrow then.”

“By the way…” Valkries stopped Fei Yuhan as the latter reached the doorstep. “Captain, could you bring some books regarding technologies to me tomorrow?”

“Something like encyclopedia?” Fei Yuhan said thoughtfully. “It shouldn’t bea problem, but there are many types of them. I don’t knowwhether I can find the one you like.”

“That’s OK. Anything is fine with me,” Valkries said pleasantly. “Thank you.”

“No worries.”

Fei Yuhan’s smile gave way to her normal cool look after she closed the door.

Valkries did not like history only.

She was learning about this new world.

Valkries sighed after Fei Yuhan withdrew.

She knew that she was a little too hasty, but she had no better choice. Fei Yuhan was the only person who could help her understand this world. If she had taken things slow, she would have probably wasted a whole month in bed.

If Hackzord’s plan worked out well, the Western Front Army should have already stepped their foot onto humans’ territory. Currently, he must be in a hot rage for her “disappearance” when he most needed people.

To be honest, Valkries had a complicated feeling at the moment. On one hand she wished that Hackzord could wake her up at the Red Mist pond with no regards to the possible consequence that she would lose most of her memories in the Realm of Mind and might even sustain severe head injuries. On the other hand, she still wanted to linger in this world a little longer.

The reason was pretty simple. The further she probed into this world, the more unsettled she felt. It would be actually a relief if she forgot all about this. Whatever secret Rolandwas holdingback from her, as long as she obtained the legacy shard in the real world, human beings wouldnot be able to resist them anymore. What they possessed now would be eventually inherited by their kind, including hissecret.

The reason she wanted to stay here longer was that the “Transformer”, Heathtalese, had warned the clan that they would not reach the Divine Domain even if they won the Battle of Divine Will. Valkries had engraved hermentor’s last words upon her heart. Ifthe victory could not perpetuate theclan, whatshould they do? Would the answer exist in this incredible Realm of Mind?

Nevertheless, she had another hidden reason.

She did not want to admit it, nor would she say it out loud.

She felt as though she had traveled back in time to the old days when she had studied in the Cloud School. Every day shereceivednew knowledge and saw a future completedifferent from the other world.

Valkries took out a box of desserts from the bag perched on the top of the books.

The beautiful packagingof the visually-appealing food was just like the food that men normally ate. Each color represented a specific flavor. As she unsealed the box, she could smell the delicious food.

She had never had such tasty confections.

Only inferior life formsin the clan, such as the Inferior Demons and thePrimal Demons, ate with mouth. Normal food hardly provided energies and it was hard to digest. Therefore,usually they put the food in the Red Mist Pond to soften it. The process was pretty similar to baking, despite that they did not use fire like men.

The processed food could only satisfy their biological need. After becoming an Upgraded, she could directly obtain energies from the Red Mist, so Valkries had not eaten for a very long time.

Some clansmen thus associated eating with low lives, for example, human beings.

Even witches needed to eat three meals a day.

She had thought so too. However, now she realized that how amazing the food from the Cargarde Peninsula was.

Valkries put a piece of cake into her mouth and savored the sweet taste.

Without a doubt, these desserts still preserved the taste of the food processed in the Red Mist, but it was better after processed with humans’ technologies.

She soon finished up the desserts.

Could the Cloud School and the “Transformer” make such great food?

Valkries shook her head and put these thoughts behind.

Anyway, the Battle of Divine Will had lasted for hundreds of years, and nothing could stop it. The current situation was beyond her control, and the most important task for the clan was to survive.

Then, she was again back to the beginning.

She knew why she felt so uneasy.

After doing research for a month, Valkries could pretty muchascertain that the great changein the human race had everything do with this world, and Roland was the fundamental person who created these changes. The firearms in the history books were almost exactly the same as those in Ursrook’s report.

She had now finally located the last piece of the puzzle and found out why human beings had upgraded. Although she did not know how a male human accessed the Realm of Mind, hehad indeedlearned a lot from this world. Such extensive knowledge transcended the erashe was living in, and he had applied these knowledge to the development of the human society. Witches served as a channel to convert the knowledge. They no longer fought on the battleground. What the clan was facing now was definitely not the Union 400 years ago but an entirely new human race.

The truth was more than that.

When she read these history books, she found another horrifying fact.

When the human civilization reached a certain degree, their development would accelerate by leaps and bounds! Thousands of years ago, they had still been fighting with firearms. However, now, they had conquered the sky and the ocean, and their weapons could possibly destroy the whole world.

That was why Valkries felt disturbed.

How far had Roland gone?

Notwithstanding Heathtalese’s warning, for the first time in her life, Valkries became unsure whether her clan could defeat human beings.

Chapter 1288: Intertwined Fate

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Well… Mr. Roland, you’ll be responsible for the third defensive line.”

“Leave it to me. I’ll do my best.”

After Roland bade farewell to Rock, he walked out of the Defender’s office and let out a sigh.

Things did not go as well as he had anticipated. The Prism City had failed to trace down more Fallen Evils, and he himself had not found any further information about them either.

The Defender thus asked Roland to help tighten the security for the Martialist Contest.

Since they could not locate any Fallen Evils at present, they had to change their plan and awaited Fallen Evils at the contest. To avoid unnecessary consumption of the martialists’ strength, the executives of the Association drafted a special schedule, and all the celebrity martialists should follow this schedule accordingly.

In other words, the Martialist Contest this year would completely turn into a carefully-designed trap.

The competition thus became a sort of formality. The executives attached great importance to public safety and had actually had a private conversation with all the celebrity martialists in advance. Everybody understood that they were currently at a critical moment, so none of them looked disgruntled.

There would be four defensive lines according to the plan. The government army and the Association members disguised as audience constituted the first defensive line. Their main duty was to find out enemies and eliminate Fallen Evils acting alone. The second defensive line consisted of all the celebrity martialists, whether they were on stage or not. Traditional martialists would be responsible for the third defensive line and the Defenders the last.

The purpose of this arrangement was to ensure the success of the Martialist Contest before the appearance of a great number of Fallen Evils. As some Fallen Evils could manipulate martialists, it was not enough to only set up one defensive line.

Roland, as a licensed hunter, was naturally assigned to the third defensive line. In fact, he would not only monitor any suspcious figures in the hall but also competing martialists.

Although Roland felt a little regretful that they did not find the hiding places of the Fallen Evils, he currently had no better ways than waiting for them in ambush.

The Association definitely knew more about Fallen Evil than him.

Fallen Evils were not attracted to the “Force of Nature” only.

They were controlled by the Divine Will, and their ultimate goal was to destroy the Dream World and return magic power to the Realm of Mind.

Therefore, the Fallen Evils should not miss such a perfect opportunity to collect so many cores.

When Roland turned around at the corridor, a woman suddenly stopped in front of Roland.

It was none other than the last person he wanted to see right now.

She was the genius martialist, Fei Yuhan.

“Oh… it’s you,” Fei Yuhan said while looking up at Roland.

They were the only two people in the corridor, so Roland could not pretend that he had not seen her. He cleared his throat and managed a smile, then said, “Ahem, hello.”

His smile, however, soon faltered as Fei Yuhan spoke on.

“I have to thank you for saving me last time,” Fei Yuhan said while casually extending out her hand. “Thank you for killing that strange monster and saving all of us.”

“Er…” Roland did not know what to say. After a moment, he said with some difficulties, “You, you’re welcome.”

“But the Association gave all the credit to me…” Fei Yuhan sighed.

“No, no, that’s totally fine,” Roland said while waving his hand. “Well… I have to conceal my identity out of some special reasons. I would rather few people notice my existence.”

“Alright,” Fei Yuhan said, who, surprisingly did not pursue this topic. “In that case, I’ll take it.”

Roland wondered why Fei Yuhan easily believed him. If she still remembered everything that had happened before passing out, she should have also remembered Ring’s voice. It appeared that she deliberately chose to ignore that matter.

Like all the rumors Roland had heard, Fei Yuhan was never a careless person. Like many young geniuses, Fei Yuhan was proud and strict, both with herself and others. She was always so distant and cold to people and was definitely not an easygoing martialist.

However, the girl whom Rolandwastalkingto now was completely the opposite of the martialist he knew.

Suddenly, Fei Yuhan seemed to remember something and asked, “By the way, do you think a person who likes to study history would also like science?”

Stunned for a moment, Roland asked, “Why did you ask that?”

“Do you remember that patient from the Cargarde Peninsula?” Fei Yuhan continued. “Miss Valkries is now on my team. I thought she must feel very bored in the sanatorium, but she’s actually interested in books. In the past one month, she almost read all the history books in the library.”

Roland was again surprised that Fei Yuhan would care about someone else. He twitched his lips and was about to speak, when suddenly something flashed across his mind. Hang on, was not Valkries she mentioned the one who resembled the demon he had seen in the memory fragment?

She had been reading history books in the past one month?

“… All of them?”

“Pretty much, especially war history. An interesting hobby, isn’t it?”

Was it a coincidence? Roland revolved his mind quickly and immediately changed his words. “Yes, I believe she wants to read something about social study and humanity. Sorry, I have to take care of the task the Defender entrusted to me and need to go now.”

Roland quickly decided to end this awkward conversation, and Fei Yuhan seemed not to be offended.

“Me too,” she said while nodding. “See you then, Mr. Roland.”

“Ah… see you.”

After Fei Yuhan left, Roland headed downstairs at once.

He accelerated.

Fei Yuhan stopped and listened carefully to Roland’s footsteps.

This meeting was not a coincidence but a carefully-planned “meeting”.

If truth be told, Roland was the most difficult person she had ever dealt with. Unlike Valkries, he behaved so naturally in this world. Had she not heard that “Your Majesty”, she would have probably never suspected him. She had noticed that during their last visit to the hospital, Roland had taken out his phone three times in one minute, and his eyes would linger on pretty ladies. His favorite pop seemed to be coke, just like any ordinary man in this era.

That was why Fei Yuhan started to question about her theory of “the other world”. If Valkries knew Roland, it meant that they came from the same world, but why did the two people act so differently?

With these questions, Fei Yuhan planned this meeting not only to thank Roland for his favor but also to test him.

She was very astonished by the result.

Roland seemed to have realized Valkries’ strangeness after this conversation, but his reaction was so different from what she had predicted. She had thought Roland would have tried to cover for Valkries since they were “friends” from the same world.

But Roland was alarmed after hearing the news, and he was even more nervous than during the joint mission.

Although Roland had tried to conceal his emotion, she still managed to capture the tiniest muscle movement around the corner of his eyes.

Apparently, Roland was not that good at controling his facial expression like Valkries.

She had learned a lot from this meeting.

Fei Yuhan decided to continue withher observation. She believed that the subsequent interaction between the two people would provide her with more information.

A smile curled up Fei Yuhan’s lips as she knocked onthe Defender’s office door.

Roland immediately summoned Phyllis and Dawnen after he returned to the apartment building.

“I need you to watch a demon. She may come from the memory fragment from this building!”

Chapter 1289: The Origin of the World

Translator: Transn __ Editor: Transn

“A demon?”

The two witches, momentarily stunned, asked, “Are you referring to the alien species in this world?”

For ancient witches, they felt it even harder to deal with people from the Cargarde Peninsula than adapting to the modern life. These people who had a strong resemblance to the demons had now become a part of the human society. They lived and reproduced just like human beings.

The ancient witches entered a combat mode almost instinctively when they encountered a demon. It hadactually taken Roland a great effort topersuade them not to easilygo on a rampage. Now, all of a sudden, he asked them to take precautions again, which was quite an unexpected change. Therefore, Roland chose Phyllis and Dawnen who were the first few witches that entered the Dream World with him and who were good at concealing their traces.

“You can put that way,” Roland said and then briefly talked about Valkries and what made her look suspicious. “I don’t see any magic stone on her, which is the biggest difference from a real demon. But you still need to be cautious and monitor her like she has one.”

Learning history was the most effective way to learn about this world. Who was so eager to learn about the past of the Dream World? If the “demon” called Valkries was really from the Cargarde Peninsula, she should have received compulsory education. However, based on what Fei Yuhan had told him, she had read the history chronically. It was indeed very strange considering that both of the two worlds were presently experiencing the Erosion.

“Yes, Your Majesty,” the two witches said with a nod.

“Even if she is a demon, don’t attack her in the sanatorium,” Roland continued after a moment of reflection. “There are many awakened martialists there, and your action may attract unwelcome attention. Plus, I also want to know how she came here through the memoryfragment.”

Room 0510 was not only connected to just a few Senior Demons but indeed a magnificent city in which a foreign race dwelled. If other demons could also come to this world through the gate, that would be great trouble.

“I see, but…” Phyllis said hesitantly. “What if you come across danger when we aren’t here?”

“Don’t worry. This isn’t the real world,” Roland comforted with a smile. “You’ve also noticed that those Fallen Evils could not hurt me. As long as I don’t voluntarily seek them, they won’t be able to do anything about me. You guys need to stay safe and call me every several hours.”

“As you command, Your Majesty,” the two witches chorused while placing their hands on their chests after exchanging a look. “We’ll set off then.”

When Epsiloneentered the meeting room, the room had just moved to a very special spot where the two realms overlapped. The floor and the wall were enveloped by a haze of crimson glow that swayed darkly like guttered candles.

Under such circumstances, this area constituted a virtual space completely separated from the outside world, which no physical entities could affect.

The area was also not traceable.

She sawBetta in a half-kneeling position, with his hands firmlyadhered to thefloor.He was half-transparent like a looming shadow.

Hehad been in this position for more than half a month.

“Not done yet?” Epsilone asked as she stared at Delta who was motionless beside her.

Delta’s mask flickered, and then he realized that he could not communicate directly with his mind at the moment. So he croaked, “This world has expanded a great deal, and it isn’t easy to have a full analysis of it anymore. But Betta is almost done. I believe we’ll soon get a result. What about you? Did you find anything?”

“Those magic power robbers have set up a trap to lure us.”

The rules in this world restricted the oracles’ power. Even though they acted on behalf of God, they still had to follow these rules.

“Just as I thought,” Delta replied flatly. “It does seem a nice plan, but we don’t need scattered magic power anymore.”

Epsilone nodded and remained silent.

A more effective way to destroy those that were out of God’s control was to directly kill the creator of the Realm of Mind. This world orginated from the creator’s consciousness. Like pillars that supported a house, oncethe creatorwas removed, the whole world would collapse, and the magic power would, naturally, return to the Divine Domain.

The problem was that this world was now so sturdy and strong, so it was extremely hard to find out the creator. Therefore, they had to first summon a great amount of magic power to analyze this world and locate the source.

The reason they had attacked the Prism City was to collect magic power for the current analysis.

Nevertheless, locating the creator did not mean they could remove him. The creator was always under the protection of this world, which was why they had failed in the last few attempts.

To fight against the protecting force, they must first lure the creator into the crack between the two worlds, where God could interfere with the rules in this world and thereby crush the enemy.

Even oracles like themmight fail.

But they had little time left.

They were God’s last hope. If they failed, God would directly destroy the Realm of Mind. Then their efforts for the past thousands of years would be wasted and all that they had achieved so far would turn into nothingness. They would not like to see the Realm of Mind end in this way if it was not absolutely necessary.

Beyond a doubt, it was all the creator’s fault.

Epsilone clenched her fists and then released them.

What was the matter?

Why did she feel angry?

As an oracle, she should not have had any emotions.

She should not have worried about the outcome of this mission but focused on working on the task.

Looking back, it seemed that she had never considered about this kind of problem before.

“What’s wrong?” Delta asked as he noticed her strange behavior.

“No, nothing…” Epsilone said as she turned around and sat down slowly at the corner.

When had the change started?

Epsilone thought for a while before she dimly realizedthat the change had started after the murder of the traitor.

At that time, she was under cover and thus successfully approached the traitor. The latter did not notice the danger until she attacked her.

Strangely, the traitor did not resist. When her arm went through the traitor’s chest, the traitor simply held her and whispered one sentence.

Epsilone did not really remember the content, but the traitor’s voice was, unexpectedly, familiar. Epsilonehad even felt a wash of warmth as if she had returned to someone’s arms long since forgotten at that moment.

The traitor had actually smiled tranquilly before she had died.

_ “Damn it. Why do I keep thinking about that?” _

_ “No, why am I so furious over this matter?” _

A multitude of thoughts crowded into Epsilone’s mind.

“What do you want to say?” Delta asked again. “We don’t communicate via mind here. Just say it.”

“I — ”

Just then, a ripple swept over the room, and Betta, who had been half kneeling on the floor, suddenly opened his eyes.

“The search is completed.”

“Finally,” Delta said while resting his eyes on Betta. “What did you find?”

Betta stretched out his arms, and three blurry figures appeared on his palm, which gradually become clearer as the lines restructured and reorganized themselves.

“There are three?”

“That’s right, but we only need to kill two because one of them has been already eliminated.”

Epsilone immediately deciphered the information from the images.

The three creators were —

“The traitor, Lan. Significance level, 1%.”

“Self-cognitive being, Zero. Significance level, 42%.”

“Unidentifiable being, Roland. Significance level, 57%.”

Chapter 1290: Achievement

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

To expedite the various projects in the Design Bureau of Graycastle, Roland adjusted his schedule and decided to have a nap for two to three hours every day after lunch. Therefore, he now entered the Dream World more frequently.

As a consequence, a group of God’s Punishment Warriors started to appear in the afternoon in the Castle District, which attracted a lot of onlookers.

With the help of the Design Bureau of Graycastle, his industrial projects went pretty well. By the last week of fall, the design of the tractor had been completed.

Before then, Anna was solely responsible for the manufacture and testing of all the projects in Neverwinter. Then, the plant took over the parts production and the assembly of the final models. The whole process was not only time-consuming process but sometimes it involved a lot of unnecessary work as well.

As Anna’s Blackfire worked far better than machine tools, workers in the plant, sometimes, could not always produce the parts created by Anna. A machine could produce thousands of parts at a time. However, it took a considerable amount of time to figure out which parts should be assigned to the plants and which to Anna for further processing. The plant could only mass produce the machines after a completed model was available.

In fact, this was the exact problem during the production process of the second generation steam engine. The pressure control valve looked pretty simple, but when it came to mass production, few were fit for its intended use. Because of the high defective rate, they had to start the production all over again, which thus resulted in a huge delay of more than half a month before a final product was successfully made.

But the Design Bureau of Graycastle in the Dream World had helped Anna finish all the preliminary work, from testing all the way to the design of the assembly line. They also determined whether ordinary machineries would be capable of producing certain parts. Given that, once Roland drafted the plan, the Ministry of Industry could immediately start on the production, which largely shortened the production process and reduced the cost.

Roland named this farming machine, which he had put great faith in, the “Harvest”.

Its five pairs of road wheels would run on Graycastle’s soil.

Nevertheless, Master Xie still had a lot to do. The current “Harvest” was nothing but a basic frame that could only serve as a tractor for farming operation. There was still a long way to go before it transformed into a war machine with five pairs of road wheels.

Roland hoped that this machine could meet all the army’s needs.

As for the telegraph machine, Qingqing soon recruited some workers, including fresh graduates and amateur radio technicians. But Roland had a hard time reading the circuit diagram, so he ordered the workers to change the diagram into an actual design plan. Even so, he was still quite slow at understanding it. Therefore, he managed to memorize the design and decided to study it with Anna later.

Apart from these two major projects, they had also made great progress in other war preparation projects in Neverwinter.

The first project was the road construction that connected the south and the north.

According to the letter from Horford Quinn to him, the Kingdom of Dawn had hired nearly 1,000 workers and built several plants to produce cement in two border cities. These plants produced hundreds of tons of cement every day for the road construction. The construction of the road between the Windswept Ridge and the Sparkling River was almost completed, and they had commenced to build the section around the Cage Mountain area. It was estimated that everything would be done within half a month.

Even with Lotus and Molly’s help, Roland had to admit that the Quinn Family was pretty efficient. Apparently, they had put a lot of efforts into it. As the road in the Eastern Region along the Redwater River directly led to the City of Evernight, they were now only one step away from transporting supplies to the front.

Also, the supplementary project, the “Hump” the steam-powered wheeled truck finally came into use.

The truck had a classic cab forward design, equipped with an engine and six wheels. Apart from a long nose (to accommodate a huge water tank) at the front, it was quite similar to a modern truck. It weighed around 10 tons, with a loading capacity of six tons. The truck could run on a hard-surfaced concrete road at a rate of 40 kilometers per hour for about 300 kilometers.

When necessary, the driver could fill the tank with rain, well water and even urine to increase the speed. Even if there was no water supply, the truck could still function pretty well between cities and rivers.

Unlike the armored train, each truck required at least two drivers, which meant that even if Neverwinter could produce a great number of trucks, there would not be enough people to operate them. Fortunately, they simply needed to found a driving school and train people to drive the trucks. There were no traffic rules whatsoever in this world, so the only task for the drivers would be getting the vehicle moving.

The last project was storage batteries.

Although this project was less technologically demanding, it was as important as the other ones.

Storage batteries could, for instance, power the taillights and headlights of the truck, which were also the only electric devices on the “Hump”. With lights, the truck could work day and night.

Electricity could also power up the biplanes and save the ground staff a lot of time. More importantly, if the engine of the plane was seized in the air, pilots could restart the plane again and thereby preserve the stability of the aircrafts.

The numerous immigrants recently relocating to Neverwinter further sped up and took the industrialization process in Neverwinter to a new level.

But Roland also understood that such rapid progress was not only attributed to the increase in the population. Had they still manufactured products in traditional workshops, it would have taken several years, let alone a few months, to train a layman into a proficient worker. However, in a modern plant, experienced workers would voluntarily teach new ones, as they relied on their apprentices to get promoted or a raise. They were always eager to teach everything they knew.

It only took a person one to two weeks to learn the basic machinery operation. Even if this person was illiterate, he could still imitate the steps and thus process parts fit for use.

The new production system and the implementation of universal education, as well as continuous research and development would all further expedite the industrialization in the urban area in the future.

Yet Roland had some bad news too.

Iron Axe reported that the First Army at the front felt it increasingly hard to cope with the demons, as the Red Mist had spread to the Cage Mountain area. Some people even claimed that Devilbeasts were seen in the Kingdom of Dawn.

Back in the battle on the Fertile Plains, Roland had noticed that the demons could run thousands of miles to pursue their enemies. Even a few Mad Demons could cause substantial damage to the rear.

Now, the few Devilbeasts seen in the sky might be very likely the demons’ scouts.

The First Army must send an equal force to the sky to suppress the assault.

Roland sighed quietly. Perhaps, it was time to dispatch the Witch Union and the Aerial Knights.

Chapter 1291: Reunion

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Roland met Wendy and Tilly in the parlor.

He briefly related the situation at the front and said, “This is pretty much it. We probably can’t wait anymore.”

“The First Army needs the witches’ help,” Wendy said darkly. “I’ll let everyone know. They’ve been waiting for this day for a long time, and I believe that they’re now ready.”

“Finally,” Tilly said while twitching her lips. “I still have a few chapters to go for the Flight Manual. I’ve been longing to fight a real battle at the front. Also, where’s my fighter? You gave me your word, brother.”

Roland did not tacitly switched the subject as usual because his voice suddenly abandoned him.

“Your Majesty?” Wendy, who noticed something wrong, asked. “Are you OK?”

Roland managed to calm himself down and nodded slowly. He said, “You know that the Bloody Moon has appeared. This is the final battle of the human race, but no one knows how long this battle will last. Perhaps, it’s going to be a year or even 10 years. You probably won’t come back until the battle ends. If…”

He could not continue anymore.

Nobody could foresee the result of the Battle of Divine Will. Last time, Ashes had sacrificed herself on the Fertile Plains. This time, how many people would survive? Many witches were only in their 20s. They should have enjoyed their university life in the other world. However, they had to fight for their fate here.

This war concerned the entire human race, so everyone must do their best to win. Witches, being also human, were indeed no different than ordinary people. Roland knew that perfectly well, but he had already established an attachment to these girls. He had been living with them for years since the Witch Union had been founded. It was thus hard for him to issue the order because once they were off for the battle, it was probably the last time he would see them.

“If somebody else sees you act like this, they’ll laugh about you,” Tilly said, grinning. “You still haven’t got used to being a king after so many years? Well… I actually like the way you are now.”

“Excuse me, Your Majesty,” Wendy said while rising to her feet. Before Roland could realize it, she had approached him and given him a hug.

“Do you feel better now?” Wendy said gently, “We all know what you’ve done for us. Even if you don’t say a word, everyone will be willing to come forward and protect you. You taught us to fight for things we want. Winning the Battle of Divine Will is essentially the same as protecting the Holy Mountain. I trust that the other witches all agree on that.”

The warmth soothed Roland a great deal. Wendy was right. Everyone knew that this day would eventually come. There was no point in hesitating now. Since all the witches were here to fight, they had made up their mind a long time ago. If he said something like “I don’t want you to go to war” or “you can stay behind if you want”, that would sound pretty lame.

The only thing they needed to do is to try their best.

“Thank you.”

Wendy smiled and returned to her seat.

“Well then,” Roland said after taking a deep breath and stared at the two people. “The Witch Union and the Aerial Knights, prepare for the war.”

“As you command, Your Majesty.”

“Leave it to me, brother.”

…

The news that the witches would go to war in the Kingdom of Wolfheart was immediately spread throughout the whole Castle District. Within half an hour, Lightning had packed up. Her luggage included a backpack that contained ammunition and sigils, a waist bag full of spices and salt, as well as Maggie perched on her head.

As usual, they were normally the first ones to set off. They would be the scouts and guides for the army coming after. However, this time, when Lightning went to bid farewell to Wendy, Wendy stopped her.

“You don’t have to be in such a rush,” Wendy said as she took over Maggie. “In fact, someone told me that he wanted to see you before you go.”

“Me?” A little surprised, Lightning asked, “Who’s that? Auntie Margaret?”

“Well…” Wendy hesitated while covering her mouth. “You’ll see. By the way, he’s waiting for you in the yard.”

“He’s already here?” Lightning said while shrugging. “Alright.”

“Coo — coo!” Maggie followed but Wendy held her back. She thus watched Lightning disappear from the doorstep.

“Sorry, you’ll have to stay with me for a while,” Wendy said smilingly while stroking the pigeon’s head. “I think it’d be better to leave her alone at this moment.”

…

Lightning walked out of the castle and off to the yard after passing the corridor. She immediately saw a flowery figure standing there.

“I see… You’re Mr. Sander Flyingbird,” Lightning grumbled. “What can I do for you?”

However, when Sander turned around, Lightning was rooted to the ground.

Although he was still wearing the same flamboyant clothes, he had a completely different vibe. Despite that they had not seen each other for years, Lightning still remembered what her father looked like.

“Father?” Lightning asked in disbelief.

“Sorry, I’ve been avoiding you,” Thunder said with a bitter smile. “I don’t want my daughter to live like her mother, so I decided not to see you…”

“When did you know that I was here?” Lightning interrupted.

“Not long after you arrived at Border Town.”

“Did Auntie Margaret tell you that?”

Thunder nodded.

“So, you’re accomplices, and so is His Majesty…”

“Don’t blame them. I asked them to keep the secret for me — ” No sooner had Thunder finished than Lightning hurried to him and raised her arm.

Thunder closed his eyes and waited for the punch.

But the pain did not come as expected.

A moment later, Thunder opened his eyes in surprise and saw his daughter pat his forehead gently, with a smile lingering upon her lips.

“In other words, you know everything about my exploration in the Western Region of Graycastle?”

“Er…”

“I found the Holy City of Taquila, a 400-year-old witch, and the ruins of the underground civilization, and I also repelled the demons’ advance unit…” Lightning said while disengaging herself. “What about it? I’m as good as you, right?”

Thunder was stunned for a moment before he burst into a laugh. “You’re indeed my daughter, but I somehow feel both sorry and happy for this reunion.”

“I understand that you’re glad. But why do you feel sorry?”

“Because you grow so fast,” Thunder said airily. “I thought you would hate me and cry in my arms. It appears that I worried too much…”

Had she not experienced the battle at Taquila, she would have probably cried out. However, she had now grown up. She would not shed a single tear before she ended this war as Ashes had asked her to. “So, you’ve been worried that I’ll hate you. That’s why you didn’t tell me? Then why do you reveal your identity now?”

“Because I decided to come with you to the north and fight the Battle of Divine Will,” Thunder pronounced slowly. “You’ll know it eventually, so it’d be better that I tell you now.”

“Really?”

“Yes. I’ll fight over the sea and at the ports. I’ve discussed this with His Majesty.”

“That’s great,” Lightning said while grasping Thunder’s hand. “Since we still have time now, let me introduce you to the team members of my exploration team. You’ll fight together with them as well!”

“It appears that you’ve made some good friends…”

“Of course. But they’re all somehow related to animals. Was I not very good at dealing with people when I was little?”

“Like the pigeon called Maggie?”

“Yes… er, no, Maggie is a witch.”

“Ahem, as far as I know, a person loved by animals is also loved by people. Don’t worry about that.”

“That’s good to know.”

The father and the daughter thus headed together toward the castle. They chatted merrily as though they had never separated.

Chapter 1292: A Person in Need and A Person Who Needs

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Farrina, breakfast is ready.”

Joe stopped at the bedroom with a plate in his hand that contained a loaf of bread and a small piece of cheese.

Over the past two months since the appearance of the Bloody Moon, the couple had lived a simple life. Joe prepared three meals every day before he went off for work to the Administrative Office. Farrina seldom went out. Most of time, she stayed in the house doing nothing. Occasionally, she would ask about the situation in Hermes. This was the only time the couple actually talked.

Joe did not know what Farrina was thinking about, but he felt pleased just to be with her. He would not expect anything more than that at this time.

However, Farrina did not respond as usual.

“Farrina, are you up?”

Joe knocked on the door, wondering why she did not answer the door.

“Well, it’s time to eat.”

“Farrina?”

Still, nobody replied as if the room was empty.

Joe’s expression immediately changed, and he instantly thought of the worst scenario.

“Crap, isn’t things going better slowly?”

He put down the plate and tried to break and enter.

With a loud bang, the door was forced open.

It was not the worst, fortunately. No rope was hung on the roof. No traces of blood could be seen on the bed. Joe was a little relieved. At least, he could now ascertain that Farrina was still alive, which meant that he could still make things right.

However, his heart immediately sank to the bottom.

He could see everything in the little bedroom at one glance. Farrina was nowhere to be seen. The wooden bed, the table and the windows had all been cleaned. Everything looked tidy and neat.

It was as tidy as the first day they had moved in.

Joe strolled over to the table. There had been books about the church, and the Graycastle Weekly spreading across the table yesterday. But now, there was nothing left.

She was gone.

Joe felt sadness prevail him as he realized the fact that Farrina had left.

Apparently, this was not an impulsive decision.

She had even wiped the corners of the table, but she did not leave him a single word.

Did she not want to trouble him anymore?

Joe slumped onto the chair at the table numbly.

Where would she go? Hermes? Her native town? Would she end her own life in an untraversed forest?

Joe naturally wanted to look for her, but he had no clue where Farrina could be. The chance of finding her was pretty slim. Since Farrina did not leave him any hint, it was obvious that she did not want to be found. What could he do even if he successfully found her?

Joe felt empty at the thought that Farrina would not be in his future life anymore. His brain seemed to stop working as though it refused to function.

In the end, nothing had changed.

“Morning, Joe.”

Why had he not noticed it earlier? Why was he simply content with the life he currently had?

“Joe?”

He just cared about himself but had never asked Farrina what she actually needed.

“Joe!”

A hand reached out to Joe and forced him to turn around.

“What are you mumbling?”

Joe blinked.

It was Farrina.

She was frowning and studying him attentively. “Are you OK?”

“You… didn’t leave?” Joe said as he grasped Farrina’s arm in disbelief. “Or you decided to stay?”

“Huh?” Utterly bewildered, Farrina did not wrench away from him. “What are you talking about? I just went to the Administrative Office.”

The two stared at each other for a while until Joe broke the silence in embarrassment, “Then… why did you go to the Administrative Office?”

“To inquire about the requirements for a driver,” Farrina answered in a serious tone. “I saw on the Graycastle Weekly that they’re hiring truck drivers in Neverwinter. I want to give it a shot.”

“Truck… what?” Joe asked in confusion.

“I don’t know what it exactly is either, but it should be similar to a carriage based on its description. I’m good at riding and maneuvering carriages. Perhaps, this is a chance for me.”

A chance? Joe suddenly felt unsettled again. Still clasping Farrina’s hand, he asked, “Why do you suddenly want to become a truck driver?”

Farrina remained silent for a while before she spoke, “I thought the matter over and now I understand. First of all, the initial purpose of building the church was to save the world and the human race. This isn’t just the church’s version of story. Roland Wimbledon also admitted that. The church failed because of the betrayal of the executives.”

“And then?”

“Then the next question is whether the King of Graycastle is really fighting for the human race as he promised. I’ve seen the Bloody Moon that represents the Divine Will in Neverwinter, the wealthy subjects, and the witches who look no different than normal people. All of these fit the story Roland Wimbledon told us. The only question left is the existence of the demons that try to destroy our civilization.”

“But His Reverence Tucker Thor did mention the demons in his will,” Joe muttered.

“That’s right, but I have to see it myself. I have to see that Roland’s army is fighting the demons from hell with my own eyes,” Farrina said while nodding. “I don’t want to make the same mistake again. I now only trust my own eyes.”

“Do you want to go to the Kingdom of Wolfheart?” Joe asked, his eyes wide open.

“Yes,” Farrina admitted flatly. “I can’t join the First Army because I used to be a church member. Therefore, an alternative way is to become a truck driver and send supplies to the front. I’ll know the truth there.”

That was why she went to the Administrative Office to make inquiries of the qualifications for a truck driver.

Joe asked cautiously, “What if it’s true? What if it isn’t?”

“If everything is true, I’ll spend the rest of my life atoning for my sin,” Farrina answered without the slightest hesitation. Apparently, she had thought it over. “Although I never arrested a witch, it doesn’t mean that I can get away with what the church has done. As a member of the Judgement Army, I was also an underlying of the traitors.” She paused for a second and then resumed, “If it isn’t, then I’ll return to Hermes to see whether I can do something for the new church…”

This was the final decision she had made.

Joe gradually released her. He could not find a single reason to stop what she was doing. Farrina bravely confronted her mistake while at the same time still making an attempt to fulfill her promise to Tucker Thor. She had a clear plan for the future. It seemed that she was stronger than he had thought. Apart from supporting her, Joe could do nothing. He did not want to stop her because that would destroy her totally as a person.

Nevertheless, it would be the same result for him.

Once she became a driver and left for the Kingdom of Wolfheart, she would not continue to stay here, which was the reason she cleaned the room.

Farrina was still leaving him anyway.

“I…” Joe took a deep breath, fearing that he would not be able to contain himself.

“By the way, I hope you could do me a personal favor,” Farrina said quickly. “They need two drivers for one truck. I want you to come with me.”

“Huh?” Joe was stunned.

“To be honest, I haven’t dealt with people for a long time, and I’m not sure if I can achieve my goal on my own,” Farrina said while averting her eyes, abashed. “But you can turn me down. You have a stable job here and earn good salaries. I know I shouldn’t have asked for that, but…”

“But what?” Joe asked immediately.

It took Farrina a few seconds to stare into Joe’s eyes and say, “I need you.”

This was the very sentence that Joe had once said to Farrina, but it was his first time hearing Farrina reply back.

Now, the person in need became a person who needed others, and the person who used to need others still remained the same. Joe no longer felt empty. Instead, he felt contented and fulfilled.

“Have some breakfast first. It’s cold now,” Joe said while heaving a deep sigh.

“Oi…”

She did not have to ask him this question actually.

Joe had traveled here from the Kingdom of Wolfheart with her, and he would certainly drive the truck for the army with her as well.

“We can apply for the position after we finish eating,” Joe said with a smile.

Chapter 1293: An Uncertain Future

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

At the airport in the Aerial Knight Academy.

The morning dawned with the roar of engines, and 10 biplanes slid out of the hangar one after another in the morning light. Sun rays gilded their sleek bodies.

“Are you planning to bring the trainees to the battlefield?” Roland asked Tilly as he stood before the “Seagull”.

Tilly nodded and replied, “If everything goes well, I can finish the last part of the Flight Manual within a month, but I don’t want my students to waste their time waiting for me in that one month. I can teach them theories everywhere, and they could probably fly at the front. After all, the airport was at the very rear compared to the battlement of the First Army.”

It was true. Apparently, Tilly had not forgotten her role as the headmistress of the Academy. Feeling a little more self-assured, Roland said, “Give more flying opportunities to the students. Don’t keep the plane just to yourself. The goal is to teach the others how to fly.”

What Roland truly wanted to say was “don’t act recklessly”.

There were a lot of opportunities for Tilly to avenge. She did not have to do so immediately.

“Hmm,” Tilly said while casting Roland a glance. “I will, if you hand me my plane as promised. I promise that I won’t fight for the ‘Fire of Heaven’ with the students.”

Roland was speechless.

Tilly giggled as she saw Roland at a loss for words. She moved her hair out of her face and said, “Don’t worry. I know what you’re thinking. Let’s make a deal. In a month, I’ll give you a group of real aerial knights, and you give me my plane. Before that, I assure you that I won’t provoke the enemies. How does that sound?”

Roland rather hoped that Tilly did not throw herself into a bitter battle at all, but he knew that there was no guarantee that one could stay safe all the time during a war. Only an army that had gone through the pain of battle could win. Therefore, he simply nodded and said, “Stay safe.”

“Of course, I’m waiting for you to bring Ashes back, brother,” Tilly said, her face splitting into a lovely smile.

For a split second, Tilly’s smile melted into the cool morning air of the Kingdom of Dawn and was engraved upon Roland’s heart.

“Your Majesty, it’s time to take off,” the guard reminded him.

“Then I’ll be off,” Tilly said as she turned round, climbed up the stairwell and disappeared behind the cabin.

“OK…” Roland mumbled as he turned away from the runway while constantly looking backward. Although they had held a farewell party last night, he still felt sorry to see them leave. Through the window, he could see many witches wave at him.

Like the expedition to Taquila last time, Wendy, Andrea, Sylvie, Echo, Leaf and the other witches were now heading to another war, only that this time, it would be a more difficult and time-consuming one.

“Everyone will come back safe and sound,” Nightingale said quietly. “I have a feeling.”

Roland nodded but remained silent.

“All clear. We can take off anytime.”

“Green flag for all!”

“Go!”

As the supervisor of the ground staff swung his arms, Lightning rose into the air followed by Maggie who had transformed into a Devilbeast. As there were no GPS coordinates in this era, and they were traveling to a foreign country, Lightning and Maggie served as the guide for the fleet.

Roland noticed that Thunder was smoking his pipe while waving at his daughter, looking proud and self-complacent.”

Behind Tilly was the “Seagull”.

Compared to the noisy biplanes, the “Seagull” was graceful and swift in the air.

Everyone in the crowd, at this point, started to bid farewell to their friends and families.

Both the Witch Union and the Sleeping Spell were concerned about this particular plane.

In the breezes created by magic power, the “Seagull” soon rose after sliding on the runaway for a short distance.

The last that took off was the Aerial Knights.

The 10 biplanes were the main air force of Neverwinter, out of which six were “trainer aircrafts” without any weapons, but Roland understood that the plant was assembling the new planes strenuously. Soon, these man-made iron birds would give the demons a heavy blow and defend the area above for the First Army.

The “Fires of Heaven” flitted across the runway one by one and rose at the edge of the wall before they spread out in a line and disappeared from the end of the horizon.

To help the Aerial Knights quickly get used to the pace of the battle, Roland had asked the construction team to also build four airports in the Redwater City, the City of Evernight, the City of Glow in the neighboring country, and Thorn Town while they were paving the road. These airports could facilitate the transportation across the south and the north and provide fuels for the planes. Since the biplane weighed less than 1,000 kilograms, it could land on any smooth-surfaced areas.

When the pilots became proficient in operating the plane, they could travel across Graycastle and the Kingdom of Dawn, and reach the Kingdom of Wolfheart by the sunset, provided that they commenced their journey early in the morning. This was definitely a tremendous speed by the standards of this era. That was also the reason that Roland paid special attention to the air force. Once a mature air force was built, human beings would enter a new phase of warfare.

Of course, as this was going to be the longest trip they would ever make in this history of time, Tilly created a pretty flexible schedule in case an emergency occurred. The army, according to her plan, would stay one night in the City of Evernight and then head to the Cage Mountain the next morning. In that case, they would be able to fly during the day.

The crowd looked on at the sky in the north after the fleet slid out of their sight.

So did Roland.

He hoped that the new air force could help the First Army get out of their dilemma.

They were really… flying!

Manfeld goggled at the giant birds that disappeared behind the slope of clouds, feeling excited.

“Hey, what are you doing there? We’re boarding the ship,” someone called at him from behind.

“I, I’m coming,” Manfeld said while shaking his head, trying to come back to the present. He trotted back to the team but could still, somehow, hear the ringing roar of the iron birds.

Although Manfeld had witnessed a lot of incredible things in Neverwinter in the past one month, it was his first time seeing the “Fires of Heaven” take off at such a close range. He felt exhilarated at the scene that he beheld.

He was again shocked, but he also felt something else this time.

For example, happiness.

Within a second, he had fallen in love with this job.

Just as the settlement clerk Matt had said, Manfeld successfully passed the screening process conducted by the human resource department of the Administrative Office and obtained a Neverwinter resident identity card. He had also received a property and quickly got used to the life here. It took him not long to find a foothold in this new city. Now, he could either choose to become a clerk in the Administrative Office or a policeman like Sharon who helped maintain public order.

He hesitated for a while and submitted his application to the Aerial Knight Academy.

Manfeld knew that official Aerial Knights would, in the end, join the army. They would be subject to a strict screening process and might also be killed in action. However, he was determined.

He was glad that he made the right decision.

Nothing could be more honorous than becoming an Aerial Knight, for they were the warriors who pledged fealty to the king, who fought against the tyrants and protected the weak.

He could not wait for this day to come.

Therefore, Farrina, Joe and Manfeld, as well as numerous other people all headed to the war in the north.

They were from different kingdoms, different regions, but they were now acting for a common cause.

Compared to the first and second Battles of Divine Will, mankind had never been so united.

Their fate had been tied to the Battle of Divine Will.

And they were all fighting for the human race.

Chapter 1294: An Isolated Island

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

She slept in the sea when she got tired and resumed her trip after she woke up. When she was thirsty, she drank rain water and ate fish when hungry.

Joan did not know how long she had to live like this.

At first, she had been trying to track time. However, after she had missed one or two days, she gradually lost the track of time and finally gave up. She had no idea how long she had been swimming aimlessly in the ocean. Perhaps, it had been more than half a year now.

Joan almost burst into tears at this thought. In fact, she had cried numerous times, but her tears merged with the seawater and became a part of the ocean.

She was so tired.

So tired indeed.

Even when she was asleep, she could not totally relax on the surface of the water, otherwise ospreys and other animals would come to eat her. Even if they could not gulf her down, their pecks were sharp and painful. Also, she could be seen by Sea Ghosts and those ship-like monsters.

Joan had actually encountered them many times during the past few months.

Every time she had been scared to death.

Fortunately, she had always managed to shake them off, despite that sometimes she got additional wounds during the escape.

There were many cuts in her beautiful scales that His Majesty spoke highly of. The skin exposed in the air turned white. As she had been in the water for so long, some wounds started to decay. What was worse, some parastic worms had found her as their new host and nested in her wounds. It was excruciatingly painful to pull them off the body.

Now, her body, which had never been pretty, became even uglier.

She missed the soft bed in Neverwinter and Wendy’s arms.

She also missed the peaceful life there.

Although there were a lot of fishes in the ocean, she had to eat them raw. She used to do that all the time, but now, she somehow could not get used to the fishy smell lingering between her lips.

She wanted to eat the barbeque chicken wings made by Lightning.

Then Joan again cried. She kept swimming as her tears trickled down.

How long did she have to swim before she returned where she came from?

She swam much faster than most fishes.

She was even faster than His Majesty’s “Snow Wind”.

The time she spent in the water could allow her to have five round-trips from Neverwinter to the Shadow Islands. However, why could she still not see her destination?

His Majesty said that Earth was round. Could he have lied to her?

If His Majesty had indeed lied, she would swipe his face with her scales if she got such a chance in the future!

But she had to first get to Neverwinter…

Joan took a deep breath and encouraged herself. She reminded herself that she must not give up and must return to her friends!

Joan began to produce a series of “Ya” sounds over the sea.

A moment later, she heard her echoes, “Ya, ya.”

A little shocked, she traced the echoes. It was a gloomy day today. A thin veil of mist permeated the surface of the ocean, and she could only see things within a few kilometers, just like the Shadow Islands when water went down. Since there was nothing at the front, Joan swam in that direction for another half an hour or so and finally spied something black loom against the mist.

It looked like… a rock on the surface of the water.

Joan’s face lit up.

She knew that many tiny little things on the ocean were actually huge. Like the rock floating in the water, it must be enormous as well. Since it reflected off sounds, it could be a giant mountain. If there was a mountain, there should be lands.

Was it a part of the Impassable Mountain Range?

Joan suddenly had a lot of strength. She picked up her speed and swam as fast as she could toward the black silhouette. Water splashed all over her.

As she got closer, she saw the black “rock” more clearly.

It was indeed a mountain, but at the foot of the mountain was not the port of the Western Region but a flat island. The rear of the island was connected to a vast land. Since the land was so far away, she could not see it clearly.

But anyway, this was a land, which was better than nothing.

Joan pulled herself together and stepped onto the beach.

It was not until then that she noticed that this island was probably even larger than the biggest Searing Flame Island at the Fjords. Except for that verdant mountain, it was as flat as a pancake.

In fact, the island was actually a meadow.

Unlike the deserted islands she knew, this island seemed to be protected from the erosion of wet sea breezes and harsh weather. Grass grew underneath her feet, and occasionally, there were a few flowers. Joan did not understand why a secluded island like this, which could be easily destroyed by a seaquake, could be so vibrant and full of life. As the island was surrounded by the mist, it gave her a feeling that she was on a fairyland.

Joan turned her flipper into legs and walked slowly toward the center of the island.

Gradually, she saw some stone tablets. At first, she paid no notice to them, but later on, she found these tablets, although different in size, were neatly laid out.

The closer she was to the center of the island, the more tablets she saw. In the end, the tablets formed various circles that became denser and denser, as though they were encircling something.

She somehow had seen a similar scene before…

Joan crouched down at one tablet and studied it carefully. There were patterns on it, but she was not sure whether they were arbitrary patterns or some unidentifiable and indecipherable messages. To Joan’s surprise, these stones looked quite old, but they were not dusty at all as if someone was cleaning them on a regular basis.

Was someone living on this island?

After walking for another few minutes, Joan was suddenly frozen to the ground.

In front of her lay an immense pit, whose diameters might be several kilometers. The pit was not only fathomless, but its mouth was smooth as well. Apparently, the pit was not caused by the collapse of the ground. The tablets encircled the pit and formed rings of “ripples”.

Joan dimly thought of something. She stared up at the sky and saw the Bloody Moon peep through the hazy mist. For some reason, she felt that the Bloody Moon in the sky would fit perfectly in the pit on the ground. They looked almost identical. She even had a strange idea that the Bloody Moon would probably fill up the hole if it fell off.

“Hello.” Just then, a beautiful voice came from behind and startled her.

“Ya — ” Joan screamed and stepped a few paces back before she slumped against a tablet.

The owner of the voice seemed to be frightened too, for she was silent for a while before she asked tentatively, “Well… are you alright?”

Joan then discovered that it was actually a very pretty young woman. She was wearing a white dress, two strands of black hair cascading to her chest. Her graceful act of demeanor really impressed Joan. The woman looked a little confused as well. For a moment, she was not sure whether she should come forward to comfort Joan or keep observing her.

“Ya, ya.”

Joan wanted to ask who she was, but she could only produce some inarticulate sounds. As she had not talked to anyone over the past half a year, she again lost her communication ability.

Incredibly, however, the woman understood Joan. A little sorrowful, she replied with a smile.

“Me? I’m just a guardian who’s trapped in here.”

Chapter 1295: Guardian

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Joan’s face lit up.

She was the second person she had met who understood the mermaid’s language other than Maggie.

Nevertheless, Joan was not quite sure whether Maggie truly understood her. She simply produced some “coo” sounds, which were even harder to comprehend. As such, they could only communicate short words and phrases.

Who was this guardian then?

Joan continued to make “ya” sounds. “Are you guarding the large pit? Where am I?”

“This isn’t a pit but a bridge,” the guardian said smilingly.

“I saw bridges before. They aren’t like that,” Joan thought to herself and walked cautiously toward the pit. She took a peek at the edge of it and found the wall of the pit was covered in mud and vines. There was no road leading to the bottom.

“Not everyone can pass this bridge, only the ones with keys,” the woman explained. “You don’t have the key, so you can’t see the bridge.”

“I see,” Joan thought. By why did the bridge builder do something like that? Why did he not let everyone pass? Even if they did not have the key, people could still walk around and pass it.

The guardian summoned a bitter smile and said, “Yes, they could, but this is what I have to do. I’m here waiting for the person who has the key and grant him the access to the bridge.”

Joan studied her for a while and then spoke.

“You aren’t chained.”

“What?”

“Since you aren’t chained, why don’t you leave the island?” Joan said as she pointed at the mist. “I saw there was a continent not far away. It shouldn’t take long to swim there. As you aren’t chained, I can get you out of this island.”

The woman was stunned for a second before she shook her head with a smile. “Never mind me. You’re injured. Were you under an attack?”

Joan did not understand why the woman suddenly changed the topic, but she answered immediately, “the monsters in the sea scratched me.”

“Come here and lie down. I have some medicine and can take care of your wounds,” the woman said while waving her hand.

For some reason, Joan believed that the woman was a nice person, although she had just met her.

After she lay down, the guardian produced a jar of medicational cream and spread it over her hand. She then spread the cream over Joan’s wounds. Instantly, a cooling sensation crept over Joan and refreshed her like a breeze that dispelled the hot air in summer.

“Ya…”

“It feels good, eh?” The guardian tore her dress and wrapped Joan’s wounds after she applied the cream. She asked, “By the way, where are you going next?”

“Going home,” Joan muttered. “I want to return to my friends.”

“Then you can’t go toward the black shadow. Although there’s a continent there, it’s not somewhere you should go.”

“Do you know where Neverwinter is?” Joan asked hopefully.

“Hmm… perhaps it’s on the opposite side of the black shadow, but it’s still quite dangerous to get there by land. You’d better swim there.”

“Really?”

“Yes. But you’d better take a good rest. I can feel that you’re shutting down.”

It was not until then that Joan suddenly felt that sleep broke over her. She finally succumbed to the fatigue that she had been resisting for half a year.

Joan indeed felt very relaxed beside the guardian.

“Just take a rest for now.”

Joan slowly closed her eyes.

The woman stroked Joan’s hair and said quietly, “I’m not chained, but people can be restricted by something other than chains. Sometimes, words can be more powerful than chains.”

“I… don’t quite understand.”

“That’s fine, because I don’t understand it either.”

The woman’s voice gradually became distant and soft, and Joan started to lose her consciousness.

“Perhaps I can ask somebody to answer your question… I’m not smart, but someone is smarter than me, for example, Miss Anna and His Majesty…”

“Really? Then, I thank you.”

“We’ll meet again… right?”

“Yes, if we’ve got a chance…”

Joan completely fell asleep.

When she woke up, it was already dark.

“Oh no, how long have I slept?” Joan sat bolt upright but she could not find the guardian. Joan looked around in panic but could not see anyone around her.

Apart from that, the tablets were all gone as well. She could only see the huge, empty pit in front of her, the meadow, and the mountain with a flat top as if everything she had seen before was but an illusion.

“Was that a dream?”

“No, it isn’t.” Joan immediately realized that her wounds had been taken care of, only that she did not feel the cooling sensation anymore.

Joan unwrapped her wounds but did not find any residue of the cream on her scales. Her wounds had healed up.

While Joan was sitting there, puzzled and confused, she heard a strange roar in the distance.

She then noticed that the mist around the island had dissipated, and now she could see the black shadow clearly.

It was a mountain, but it was a little too high, as though it was leading to Heaven.

The mountain was also extremely large. From a distance, the mountain was even wider than the Fjord Islands put all together. There was not a single tree on the mountain but inky, impenetrable darkness. A haze of Red Mist enveloped the top of the mountain and spurted out crimson liquid from time to time!

Then Joan saw where the roar came from.

At the foot of the mountain were swarms of monsters coming toward the continent. They piled up on the beach and ejected venom. The black soil underneath collapsed, and huge rocks fell into the sea. The whole ocean was boiling! Although these monsters were tiny compared to the gigantic black mountain, they were, little by little, eroding it!

Yet they encountered resistance.

In the area that the monsters could not reach, thousands of Sea Ghosts collided with another kind of monsters. It took Joan a long time to realize that the other kind of monsters were what everyone described as demons!

The Sea Ghosts that scared the sailors so much appeared to be incredibly weak in this battle. There flew in all directions, failing to break into the demons’ defensive line. Despite their constant failure, they continuously crossed over the ship-like monsters and rushed toward the bank.

Joan covered her mouth in surprise.

“Although there’s a continent there, it’s not somewhere you should go.”

“You should go to the opposite side of the black shadow.”

Joan suddenly thought of the woman’s words.

She looked around. Across the black mountain lay just the vast ocean. There was no sign of lands. Joan hesitated for a short moment and began to run in that direction.

She sensed a great danger as she saw the two parties fight. Her instinct told her that she must leave. Another reason was that she believed that the guardian would not lie to her.

Joan thus plunged into the water and left the earth-shaking roar behind.

Chapter 1296: A Visitor from the Sky

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“Father, do we really have to do so much for them?”

Hawn Quinn watched the busy workers at a clearing outside the City of Glow and asked a little indignantly.

Before the two people was a rectangle square, its length about 1,000 meters and width around 500. After the construction team of Graycastle came to the Kingdom of Dawn, the nobles started to use the new measurement.

Unlike the square built with beautiful slabs in the king’s city, this square was built with grayish, plain cement. Although not visually appealing, it was fairly easy to build. It had only taken them less than a week to excavate the ground and build the base.

All the workers for this project were from the Quinn Family, which showed how important this project was.

“Hmm,” Horford Quinn, the current King of Dawn said while casting his son a glance with some interest,” what are you referring to?”

“King Roland probably asked you to do too much,” Hawn said while counting on his fingers. “He asked you to build a bridge and a road. These are both big projects. You summoned all the family workers to work on the construction. Then who’ll take care of the domain? The castle has to be refurbished as well.

Of course, Hawn was unhappy about something else too.

His father was too obedient to the King of Graycastle.

He even prejudiced his own interests.

The cement was apparently a very promising alchemical material. If their family could have a monopoly over that, they would gain huge profits.

Just because that King Roland had instructed in his letter to “produce as much cement as possible”, Horford had summoned all the great nobles to the palace and told them how to produce cement. With the help of those nobles and various chambers of commerce, soon several cement plants were built. As a result, the Quinn Family did not profit much from this new technology.

When it came to the road construction, however, the situation reversed.

The great nobles all refused to cooperate, which left Horford no choice but to do it on his own.

The Quinn Family took care of all the construction work, from the recruitment to the collaboration with the Graycastle construction team. Despite that they had accumulated huge wealth after taking over the country from the royal house of Moya, they had spent a great deal on this project. Hawn’s heart ached when he saw the gold royals in the treasury decrease every day.

Road construction was different than a business investment that could bring in more money. The road connecting the Northside River and the Cage Mountain could not bring anything. The two areas were not even under the jurisdiction of the Quinn Family! Even if the road did, somehow, flourish the local business, only the lords along the road would profit from it.

From what Hawn could tell, King Roland definitely wanted to build something more, for example, this strange, useless square. If they keep squandering money like this, his family would soon encounter a financial crisis. In fact, many distant branches of the family had started to complain about Horford’s action.

What annoyed Hawn most was his father’s attitude toward the Graycastle men.

He not only made inquiries of every project but also summoned the construction team to the palace frequently and asked whether they had any needs. Hawn was particularly resentful after he learned that these “officials” were all civilians rather than nobles. His father was a king, and it extremely irritated Hawn to see they sit equal at the same table.

And today, when Horford heard that Graycastle would send their ambassadors, he immediately went out to the city to greet them. This was so incredible. As a ruler, he could have definitely met the guests in his castle. What royals would greet the guests outside the castle in person?

Hawn suspected that Horford did all this because of his daughter, Andrea. Everything started after his daughter left.

“What can I do?” Horford said, shrugging. “Nobody else is willing to work. I can’t let them do what they want. You’ve seen how powerful Graycastle is. Do you think without the support of the Wimbledon Family, I’d still be able to be the king of the country?”

“No, father… I’m not asking you to resist Graycastle,” Hawn explained while waving his hand. “You just need to ask others to work for you, and Roland Wimbledon won’t say anything about it. You can negotiate with the local lords for the funds. A business deal is a sort of negotiation. You told me that a good businessman has to stay calm to get the maximum benefit.”

“But the Battle of Divine Will isn’t a trade.”

“That’s right, but…” Hawn broke off and bit his lip. Finally, he bursted out, “But you don’t look like the King of Dawn at all but a minister working for King Roland Wimbledon!”

Hawn expected to see his father throw a fit, but the latter simply stared at him for a moment and smiled airily. He said, “Why do you think there are only four kingdoms on this continent instead of three or five?”

“Well…” Hawn was totally unprepared for the question. “Because… because we’re the strongest four families?”

“More precisely, we’re the strongest in our own domains.” Horford said, “Our power can’t extend throughout the whole continent. The so-called border is actually the furthest we could extend our power to. However, the balance between the four kingdoms has been broken. Roland Wimbledon could completely take over all of the Four Kingdoms if he likes. If that’s the case, why can’t I submit to his ruling?”

Hawn retorted fiercely, unable to help himself, “Father! The Graycastle army is powerful, but they can’t control the whole continent! You’re exaggerating…”

“You aren’t realizing the change in Graycastle, child,” Horford sighed deeply. “Perhaps, Roland couldn’t in the past, but now he has extended his power beyond his own territory. You didn’t really look into what he has done, so of course you don’t believe that he has that ability.

“How… how did you know?”

Horford answered with a smile, “Andrea replied to my letter.”

Hawn’s heart sank.

When he was about to talk more sense into his father, somebody shrieked.

Then there was a loud, dull buzz coming from a distance.

Hawn looked in that direction, slightly surprised at a line of black shadows in the sky that was streaming toward the City of Glow.

Were they migrating birds?

However, he soon realized that he was wrong. The black dot expanded immediately, and it became larger than any birds he had seen. It was still expanding.

Hawn’s eyes were wide open. They seemed to be artifacts!

All the workers dropped their tools involuntarily and started to scream.

Many cavarans that passed by also stopped and looked up at the sky.

“That’s incredible… He really did that,” Horford commented while smiling faintly. “My guests are coming.”

Hawn, at this point, was completely aghasted. Were these huge birds the transportation tools invented by the Graycastle men?

How could it be possible?

Chapter 1297: Arrive at the Front!

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Yet Hawn soon realized that what he had throught was impossible was real.

The huge birds hovered above the square and then dropped. Hawn could now see clearly the pilot up there who was also peering down. The artifact was even larger than a carriage. Hawn could not understand how such heavy items could fly like a bird in the sky.

The other spectators also wondered the same question.

When the iron birds fleeted across the square, many workers knelt down and prayed.

This must be a miracle.

“Your sister Andrea is also there,” Horford Quinn commented. “Her letter is just dated yesterday.”

It took Hawn a long time to understand the implication behind the word “yesterday”,

All his hair on his back stood on its end as he realized what it meant.

They arrived here in just one day from Graycastle thousands of miles away?

Now, when Hawn thought of his father’s words that “the balance has been broken”, he realized how ridiculous his previous idea was.

The man-made iron birds landed quietly one after another. When Andrea walked off the plane, Horford could not wait to come up to greet her.

…

A banquet was held in the palace to receive these Graycastle witches. Although no nobles were invited, the news that the guests had descended from the sky immediately spread throughout the entire City of Glow.

So many people had witnessed that spectacular scene.

After lunch, Horford finally found an opportunity to speak to his daughter alone.

He was pleased that Andrea would at least call him father now.

“Are you leaving in the afternoon?” Horford asked a little regretfully.

“We must be at the Cage Mountain by the sunset and meet with the First Army,” Andrea said with a nod. “The ‘Seagull’ could have arrived there in one day had this not been our first time traveling abroad. If that was the case, we would probably not have had time to eat.”

Horford was utterly shocked when he heard that the Graycastle men could travel from one country to another within one day. Although he had learned about this amazing transportation tool from his daughter’s letter, he still could not quite take it. He had lectured Hawn earlier regarding the changes in Graycastle, but in fact, he himself was not fully convinced either. Horford sighed internally and said while stroking his beard, “You did that on purpose, didn’t you?”

Andrea smiled for the first time. She asked, “You knew?”

“I just think the planes shouldn’t have hovered so long in the air before they landed,” Horford said resignedly. “In that case, everyone in the southern city would hear the noise. Well, it’s indeed a good warning to those nobles who are thinking about stirring up trouble.”

“This is one of the reasons. The other reason is that we need to establish confidence among the public,” Andrea explained while shrugging. I’ve heard that there are demons and Devilbeasts lurking around the Kingdom of Dawn. If the residents here know that the Graycastle army also has the ability to fly, they would not easily get panic.”

“It does kill two birds with one stone. Is this also the idea of that Pearl of the Northern Region?”

“No, it’s Princess Tilly’s idea.”

Horford noticed that his daughter was pretty proud of her princess when she mentioned the latter’s name as if she was sharing the honor. It appeared that she had made many good friends in Neverwinter. Horford nodded and switched the subject. “By the way, are you really not interested in taking the throne?”

“Why did you say that again?” Andrea said while raising her brows. “Haven’t I told you that I’m not interested in being the queen of the Kingdom of Dawn? Are you not satisfied with Hawn?”

“He’s a good noble and also a pretty talented businessman. I believe he would be a good earl,” Horford replied while shaking his head. “But Hawn, like all the other nobles, cared too much about personal gains. Many people in the family don’t understand why I’m doing all this. They don’t comprehend that what I’m doing now is to further secure our dominant position in this country.”

After Horford had become the King of Dawn, the Quinn families had all somewhat changed, including his adopted son. Hawn would have never said such things as “you don’t look like the King of Dawn but a minister working for King Roland Wimbledon” in the past. Someone must be insinuating him into making such impertinent comments, or Hawn had already regarded him as the next king.

The word “His Majesty” was a fascinating word, but the power it brought could equally bring disasters. He did not want Hawn to end up like Appen.

Also, another reason that Horford had not told Hawn was that the other two families would probably not acknowledge an adopted son as the ruler of the state.

In fact, the Luoxi Family and the Tokat Family supported Horford largely because of Andrea.

“That’s your problem,” Andrea said indifferently.

“If you don’t want to take over my position, then I have to share the throne with the other two families,” Horford said in a sorrowful tone.

“You don’t mind?”

“That’s nothing,” Horford said half-jokingly. “It actually saves me a lot of trouble. After the war, I can probably move to Neverwinter and stay with you. I can have a peaceful life before I die.”

Horford was serious. If Roland Wimbledon won the Battle of Divine Will, would the Four Kingdoms continue to exist? Horford did not think so. The Quinn Family had risen to power simply because they took advantage of the war. If he let Andrea take the throne, Roland would probably leave the Kingdom of Dawn as it was. However, if someone else became the king, that would, perhaps, become another different story.

Just as he had said earlier, King Roland had broken the balance between the four kingdoms.

Andrea looked at Horford for quite a long time. He could tell that his daughter was not as determined as before. After a long silence, Andrea said, “I have to go.”

“Take care of yourself,” Horford said. It took him a great deal of efforts to suppress his urge to stroke his daughter’s head. “I’ll come to the front if available.”

“… You too,” Andrea replied as she turned around and withdrew from the study.

Horford took a deep breath. He leaned against the chair and closed his eyes.

He did not forget the decision he had made last year.

He would like to spend the rest of his life correcting the mistake he had made.

Four hours later, the fleet landed safely at Thorn Town at the foot of the Cage Mountain.

Within just two days, they had traveled between four cities and covered a distance of more than 1,000 kilometers. This unprecedented operation would definitely become a part of the history.

Iron Axe, Brian and Edith were all waiting for them at the airport. After a brief discussion, the witches entered the headquarters located at the top of the mountain. From the grave expression of the General Staff clerks, the witches judged that the First Army was not in an optimistic position.

Iron Axe spread open a large map on the long table and nodded at everyone before he said, “Now, let me tell you about the current situation.”

Chapter 1298: The Arrival of the Demonic Months

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Iron Axe and Edith had made numerous predictions of the war at the frontier.

They both concluded that before all the troops assembled and brought all the weapons, the First Army should focus on the defense. Even if the main force arrived, they had to adjust their operation strategies accordingly and looked for an opportunity to eliminate the demons at one shot. If they were trapped in the Red Mist area, their situation would become very precarious.

“According to the intelligence collected by the Taquila witches, the Red Mist produced by the Obelisk would eventually cover more than half of the Kingdom of Wolfheart,” Iron Axe said as he pointed at the red curve on the map. “Therefore, we shall extend our defensive line. In consideration of the time for alerts and preparation, we shall set up our outposts in these four cities along the curve, which are the Metalstone Ridge, the Gust Castle, the Sand City, and the Sedimentation Bay.

These four cities formed a polygonal chain that spanned across the Kingdom of Wolfheart on the opposite side of the Red Mist area.

“But the First Army currently doesn’t have enough force to defend the four cities all at once, so they have to pick the more important ones to build their strongholds. The most important two cities are the Sedimentation Bay and the Sand City. They support each other and are situated at the crest of the Red Mist area, only 50 kilometers away from the demons’ battlement. If we lose them, the demons could directly attack the Cage Mountain.”

“Especially the Sedimentation Bay,” Morning Light added. “It’s the port closest to the Cage Mountain. We rely on it to send our supplies. Losing the Sedimentation Bay means that it’ll take the army much longer to assemble. We can’t let that happen.”

“Just tell them the truth,” Edith said flatly. “If the demons take the Sedimentation Bay, then we’ve half lost the Battle of Divine Will. Fortunately, the demons are also short of supplies. Since they erected the Obelisk on the ridge of the continent, it isn’t easy for them to transport the Red Mist.”

Perhaps, Edith was the only person who did not mind saying the word “lost”. Iron Axe coughed in embarrassment and said, “Anyway, let’s suppose that the demons encounter the same problem as us and are now busy creating a “shortcut” in the mountains. Whatever their reason is, the First Army mustn’t miss this opportunity. Before the road construction is completed, we must hold onto the two cities.”

He paused for a second and then resumed, “There are around 3,000 soldiers stationed in the Sedimentation Bay and the Sand City. They’re now building trenches and strongholds. I’ve also built a reserve unit that contains 1,000 soldiers to defend the rear of the two cities as potential reinforcements. Nevertheless, this isn’t enough. I hope Miss Sylvie could serve as a scout to alert us like what we did in the past in the Sedimentation Bay. Miss Lightning and Maggie could help with the other city.”

“Got it.”

“No problem.”

“Coo!”

The three witches chorused.

“As for the Metalstone Ridge and the Gust Castle, I’ve sent a unit of 500 to defend them. These two cities are relatively far from the Red Mist area, so the demons would not likely attack them. Even if they do, they would normally send the Devilbeasts,” Iron Axe continued as he saluted to Tilly. “I hope Your Highness could help with the defense in the air.”

Tilly nodded and answered, “Don’t worry. The Aerial Knights are designed to fight the Devilbeasts.”

“The last is the Archduke Island,” Iron Axe said as he pointed at a large island in the east. “It’ll be eventually covered by the Red Mist, but strategically, we still rely on it. Since it’s not connected to any lands, it’s easier to defend. The Mad Demons need to travel two to three kilometers to cross the channel to land. The Spider Demons can’t cross the ocean. Although the flying Devilbeasts could travel anywhere pretty fast, they can’t attack effectively. Therefore, the Devilbeasts won’t create too much trouble to the construction of the blockhouses.”

“As long as we have the Archduke Island, the Sedimentation Bay would be quite safe. Likewise, the island is a perfect place for us to attack the demons. If we use cannons in the city, our fire would cover the entire beach, as well as the land within a radius of 10 kilometers.”

“But it’s covered in the Red Mist…” Agatha said apprehensively.

“The General Staff has considered about it,” Edith interjected. “That’s why we sent 500 people there. Even if the demons attack us fiercely, the army and the fleet at the Sedimentation Bay would still have time to retreat. There’s no sign so far that indicates that the demons have a powerful fleet that can fight on the ocean.”

“Er… can I say something?” Wendy asked.

“Go ahead.”

“I lived in a monastery in the old holy city for more than 10 years, so I know the several roads in the Kingdom of Wolfheart and the Kingdom of Everwinter leading to the Hermes Plateau. The roads in the Kingdom of Everwinter are mostly in the Impassable Mountain Range. Could the demons use these roads to attack Hermes? There are many God’s Stone mines there.”

There was instantly a heated discussion.

Without a doubt, once the demons erected the Obelisk at the center of the Four Kingdoms, the result would be more fatal than when they did that on the Fertile Plains. The Red Mist could tumble down to the land below from the plateau and permeate the whole continent. By that time, the human race would have nowhere to go.

“That’s a possibility, but it’s hard to achieve,” Edith commented in approval. “During the last two Battles of Divine Will, the demons could only erect one Obelisk. First of all, their army can’t cross the Impassable Mountain Range and reach the Hermes Plateau. These paths were all accessible to the public. We just need to build a few outposts if we want to monitor them. Once exposed, the demons would be in a very disadvantageous position.”

“Therefore, even if the demons intend to attack the New Holy City, they could only do it secretively like what they did to the Misty Forest. One or two units won’t be able to set up the Obelisk so quickly in Hermes. Plus, the Coldwind Ridge is just one step away from the Plateau. It’s highly unlikely that they’ll build an Obelisk under our noses.”

“I see. You’ve already thought about that,” Wendy said, profoundly relieved. “Then it’s OK with me.”

“That’s the basic plan for the First Army at the front,” Iron Axe concluded. “We’re now trying to see where the demons are coming from. To tell you the truth, as we don’t have enough information and are short staffed, the First Army have had a hard time recently. I’m really glad that everyone came to support us. With your help, we could, more or less, solve these problems. Once we have enough people and intelligence, we can fight back!”

The next was to assign work to the witches.

Leaf and Lotus would stay at the Cage Mountain on the border and set up numerous traps.

Andrea and Shavi would head to the Sedimentation Bay. They were combat witches, so they naturally were sent to the front.

Hummingbird and Molly would support the logistics to help unload supplies at the port.

Echo would be responsible for raising the morale of the army.

While everyone was busy preparing for the war, fall had passed.

The sun did not rise as usual on the first day of winter. Instead, flurries of snow drifted down from the sky.

This was the first Month of Demons after the appearance of the Bloody Moon.

Chapter 1299: A Swift Attack

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Outside Thorn Town at the Cage Mountain.

“A, atishoo — ”

Good sneezed as he entered the hangar against rushes of snow and gusts of wind. He placed the heavy ammunition case beside the plane and slumped onto it. “I hate winter. It reminds me of those old days when we were refugees.”

“Nobody likes the Months of Demons, but I have to say that true winter hasn’t come yet,” Finkin said while twitching his lips as he opened his wooden case. “You should feel happy that we aren’t far from the sea. The Months of Demons aren’t that bad on the coast. Before His Majesty became the lord of the Western Region, everyone feared that they would not survive the night. Their houses might collapse at night, and they would then be buried in snow if they stayed in. They could not even run for life.”

“Well, are the Months of Demons in Neverwinter really that terrible?”

“That’s right. The situation didn’t change until His Majesty built concrete houses. Why do you think His Majesty named the new king’s city ‘Neverwinter’?” Finkin said while shrugging. He took out the ammunition from the case and put it into the cabin.

The “Fire of Heaven” was equipped with two machine guns, one at the front and the other in the middle. Although they were both new general machine guns, their loading methods were quite different. The machine gun at the front was half merged with the plane, so they used a cartridge to load shells. The ammunition case was, therefore, made of metal. When they load shells, they had to remove the whole thing.

The machine gun in the middle was fixed to a rotating gun rack. Its operation method was exactly the same as Mark I used by the Gun Battalion, only that they used a saddle-shaped drum magazine that could accommodate 100 shells to load the weapon. The machine gunner at the rear loaded ammunition manually once the shells ran out.

To ensure that every time before the operation, they had sufficient ammunition, they needed to reload the weapons after the plane landed, no matter how many times they had fired. Normally, the ground staff would take care of this matter, but Good preferred to do it himself. He did not want to miss a single opportunity to touch the plane, even if it was just a fleeting second.

Just then, a loud wave of cheers erupted outside the hangar.

Undoubtedly, some students had passed the exam and landed on the runway.

Even if it was now snowing, Her Highness did not stop the training.

She was even busier than usual.

Apart from teaching the new students, she took them to patrol the northwestern area of the Kingdom of Wolfheart twice a day. At night, they discussed flight theories and issues they had come across during the day. She hardly took a rest.

Under her influence, everyone studied hard, and they actually did even better than in Neverwinter. During the past one week, not a single trainer aircraft had crashed.

After installing the new ammunition case to the storage room at the front of the plane with his partner, Good walked up to the window and let out a sigh.

“What’s the matter? Are you homesick?” Finkin asked as he followed Good.

Good shook his head and said, “I’m just worried about…”

“About the war and your sister back home?” Finkin interjected while smiling slyly. “I remember her name is Rachel, right?”

“I’m worried about that I’ll be replaced!” Good exclaimed indignantly as he glared at Good.

“Why?”

“We only have four fighters, one of which is Her Highness’ ‘Unicorn’. In other words, I have to be one of the top threes to operate the Fire of Heaven,” said Good as he turned around and watched the training field at a distance. “Our strength lies in war experience, but we haven’t seen a single demon yet. If there are one or two gifted students among the new people, we would probably fall behind.”

Surprised at Good’s concern, Finkin said in a resigned tone after a long silence, “Oi, oi, you’re worrying too much. We’ve earned a lot of experience by shooting real bullets. Didn’t Her Highness say that even the Gun Battalion needs a couple of months to practice, wasting thousands of bullets before they throw themselves in a real war?”

“But we don’t really do well in shooting, do we?”

“Well…” Finkin was at a loss for words.

Although the Aerial Knights had never met a single demon so far, they had fired on the plane numerous times. Tilly did not ask them to bring back the ammunition but asked them to use up all the bullets. They were told to pick a random target and practice as if it were a real battle. The target, sometimes, was a balloon in the air or a big tree on the top of the mountain.

Good discovered that he was much less talented in shooting than flying. Also, he had heard that many new students had quite outstanding performance during the training, one of whom was called Manfeld. His gift was soon acknowledged by the instructor in just a few days.

Therefore, his worry was not completely groundless.

He could improve his flying techniques by constant practice, but there was no shortcut for shooting.

Suddenly, a sharp alarm broke over the airport.

It pierced the air like a firecracker!

Good and Finkin exchanged dark looks, and their manners instantly tightened.

Once the alarm went off, all the training was suspended. The runway was cleared. The official Aerial Knights must immediately gather at the headquarters at the airport.

It was their first time hearing the alarm since their arrival at Thorn Town.

They thus ran to the headquarters at once.

Soon, there were more than 30 people in the temporary headquarters.

“We received a message from Iron Axe just a minute ago that a troop of demons had appeared 200 kilometers to the north of the Gust Castle,” Princess Tilly said as she pointed at the map. “The message was delivered by the animal messenger, and in the letter, Iron Axe has pointed out that there are also refugees nearby. The demons may aim at these refugees. It would take the garrison at the Gust Castle more than two days to travel there. It would be too late if we wait for them.”

“This is what the Aerial Knights can help with. Nobody can cover such a long distance within two to three hours except the ‘Fire of Heaven’. The demons would have never thought that they would share the sky with us one day! Now, heed my command. Aerial Knights, advance!”

“As you wish, Your Highness!” everyone shouted together.

Good clenched his fists. He had been waiting for this moment for a long time!

By the time they returned to the hangar, the ground staff had finished the preparation work for the takeoff.

Good strode over to the pilot cabin, quickly turned on the engine and spinned the lever. As the motor was set in motion, black smoke spiraled up from the head of the jet. The plane finished its first cycle as it roared.

Once the engine was on, the piston would continue working.

Good put on his goggles, waved at the cheering crowd and pushed down the lever.

Around seven or eight mintues later, four biplanes streaked across the runway and rose into the air in the snow before they headed off to the north.

Chapter 1300: A Ferocious Fight

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

It was definitely not easy to fly in winter.

Although the Aerial Knights were wearing hats made of wolf skins, fur scarves and goggles, the area unprotected by these gears was still exposed to the biting coldness.

The windshield was located at the front of the “Fire of Heaven”. When the wind changed its direction or when the plane set off, flurries of snows would be carried into the cabin by the wind from all directions.

However, Good understood the rationale behind this design.

Above him were the huge wings, so his vision was pretty narrow. If he wanted to observe the situation below, he had to poke his head out of the cabin. In fact, the most thing that Finkin did was to poke his head out. Unlike regular soldiers who simply needed to draw out their weapons on the battlefield, the Aerial Knights had to first located the enemies. It was extremely hard to find their target in the sky.

The “Fire of Heaven” became as tiny as an ant at a height of 1,000 kilometers, let alone the people on the ground.

That was probably the reason why each plane was operated by two people. Four eyes worked better than two.

“Any luck?”

Good turned around and asked.

Around an hour ago, the fleet had passed the Gust Castle. If the demons were pursuing the refugees, they should be around this area according to the map. To expediate the search process, the four planes spread out and formed a fan-shaped formation around the central axis in the north.

This was also the standard search method written on the Flight Manual.

Theoretically, as long as they did not deviate from the course, the four planes could cover the area within a radius of 200 kilometers. Nevertheless, due to the harsh weather condition, the planes had to stick together, which largely reduced their search area.

“Nothing!” Finkin yelled while holding his telescope. “Could demons have already caught up with the refugees and killed them all?”

“Then there should be many bodies down there!”

“Alright, I’ll take another look… I hope the snow won’t cover them up,” Finkin mumbled. “Mate, could you drop a little bit?”

Good lowered the head of the jet a little and cast a glance at the compass and the altimeters.

These were the only two parameters on the “Fire of Heaven that they could rely on to know their current location.

In spite of this, there were also clear instructions on the Flight Manual that they must not trust these two parameters too much. “Due to the limitation of the technologies, the devices could go wrong, especially when the plane is flying through an area that is experiencing a series of drastic changes in weather, altitude and geographical landscape. Make sure that you look out of the cabin every now and then, unless you want to be that key person who prompts a new round of technology revolution — by Tilly Wimbledon.”

“I can only drop another 300 meters. No lower than that. This isn’t the Western Region of Graycastle where the land is flat — ”

However, Finkin interrupted him, “Two degrees to the right! Someone’s moving there.”

Good’s expression changed. He quickly adjusted the direction.

He could hear nothing except the howl of the wind and the roar of the engine. Therefore, Finkin was not referring to sounds but something visible to their eyes. It would be indeed very suspicious if someone chose to come out under this weather condition.

A moment later, Good found many black dots against the vast, white mountain range covered in snow. Instead of a few scattered dots here and there, they actually formed a great number of lines. From above, these lines resembled thin threads of hair in the snow.

“Are they… footprints?”

Finkin answered his question in excitement. “That’s right. I believe that’s whom Her Highness asked us to look for! There are people on the mountain, and there are so many! God, the demons are going after those refugees. I saw hundreds of bodies! Based on their body builds, they should be Mad Demons, and there are 30 to 40 of them!”

“Notify the others!” Good said immediately and pressed down the lever. “Let’s go first!”

Three green flares were discharged and sizzled into the air, forming a glaring constast with the Bloody Moon in the midair.

The plane plummeted, and the two parties were increasingly close to each other. When the plane was only 400 to 500 meters away from the crest of the mountain, Good finally saw the fleeing refugees struggling to run for life in the snow. They rushed down the mountain, and many people almost tumbled down the mountainside, looking desperate.

The Mad Demons, on the other hand, slowly closed in from behind. They were not particularly chasing or slaughtering them, but rather, they were enjoying the pleasure of the hunting game.

All Good’s blood rushed to his head.

He recited the shooting instructions internally and aimed at the Mad Demons at the top of the mountain. After the target was aligned, he pressed the firing button.

The machine gun instantly fired furiously!

This was also the easiest way to shoot a target on the “Fire of Heaven”. When the plane was only 200 to 300 above the ground, he did not need to worry that the bullets would deviate from the course as they dropped. The bullets would travel in the direction the jet headed during the whole process. Even Good, inexperienced as he was, could hit the target!

The bullets rained down at the Mad Demons in the snow and created a straight “borderline”!

It was not until then that the demons finally noticed the descending giant bird. They howled as they drew out their bone spears and threw them at the “Fire of Heaven”, without the slightest intention to retreat.

Just then, the “borderline”, without any warning, scattered the demons.

It was line of life and death.

The metal bullets whistled through the air and penetrated the Mad Demons, dotting the white snow with streaks of blue blood. Red blood mist spurted out suddenly from the back of the Mad Demons that got hit. Their arms and legs were instantly broken. For a moment, limbs and flesh flew in all directions, exhaling piles of snow. The Mad Demons were thus temporarily stopped.

Then there came the demons’ bone spears. Unfortunately, the spears could not harm the “Fire of Heaven”. Even if the weapons did reach the aircraft, they were too weak to cause any damage. It was almost impossible to spear the biplane traveling in the air at a high speed.

But the “Fire of Heaven” was still attacking

While Good was repositioning the jet, Finkin started to fire.

Finkin aimed at the crest of the mountain and fired ferociously. He did not follow any shooting rules or calculate the trajectories but simply shot based on his own instinct.

The demons finally realized that the strange bird in the sky was not some hybrid demonic beast or monster but a weapon created by human beings! However, their understanding could not change the situation. There was no hiding place, and the chance of escaping the furious “Fire of Heaven” became extremely slim.

During the past Battles of Divine Will, human beings had been so afraid of the Devilbeasts that flew high and fast up in the sky. Now, the demons were equally scared. Perhaps, they were more frightened than men.

A moment later, Good began to plunge toward the demons again.

At that time, the other two planes also appeared.

Under the attack of the three planes, the demons fled as fast as they could, but the planes pursued them relentlessly, in an attempt to kill more.

Neither Good Nor Finkin realized that they were the first few people who would still chase the enemies when they were outnumbered. Even the previous evacuation unit of the First Army had not taken the initiative to go after the demons. Now, they were facing 40-50 Mad Demons, but they only got three planes manned by six people.

Chapter 1301: A Battle in the Snow

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

White thought he was going to die when the strange gray bird zoomed toward the mountain.

The only thing he was thinking at that moment was that he should have not come all the way here to do business!

He blamed those sailors!

Had those sailors not been so envious of coachmen and also started to transport refugees, he would not have had to come to the interior of the Kingdom of Wolfheart.

He simply wanted to earn more money and survive the fierce competition!

He had not expected that this time, he would encounter real demons.

He could probably still survive as long as he ran faster than the other refugees. However, when the strange birds appeared in the sky, he knew that he was doomed.

No men could outrun something that had wings, not to mention that he only had one leg.

White buried his head in his arms and knelt down. “God, please send your pious believer to the divine land you created after he dies and make sure that he has endless gold royals to squander…”

But the weird birds did not tear him to pieces. Instead, they produced a series of familiar sounds.

He had heard similar “neighing sounds” at the Sedimentation Bay. When the Graycastle men fired, those sounds would reverberate across the whole battlefield. Within just half an hour, the invincible knights from the Tusk and the Redstone Family were all reduced to ashes.

Did the Graycastle men came to their rescue?

White looked up gingerly and saw the most incredible scene in his life.

A jet of silver white flash erupted from the head of the strange bird. As if it had consciousness, the flash reached the demons. The snow was kicked up into the sky, and the demons fell down one after another, as though the flash contained indefinite power.

He was flabberghasted.

What excited White more was that the demons were also caught totally unprepared. They not only stopped chasing them but also started to flee.

“Mr. White, what, what’s that?” some refugees asked tremulously.

White shook his head involuntarily, and suddenly, a bold idea flashed across his mind.

White pinched his leg and forced himself to stand up. He spread out his arms at the horrified refugees and yelled in a quavering voice, “Don’t be scared. This is the Graycastle army I told you before! I summoned them here!”

“Graycastle men?” the refugees echoed in disbelief. “From the sky?”

“That’s right!”

“Do you mean… that we’ll be saved?”

“For now, yes, but it’s not free. Indeed, their service is quite expensive! I don’t have much savings, and I don’t know when they’ll leave — ”

Before White could finish, the excited crowd interrupted him, “Don’t let them go! I’m willing to pay double!”

“I’ll pay two silver royals!”

“If I could arrive at the Sedimentation Bay safe and sound, I’ll give you my gold ring!”

“And me as well…”

The refugees, who had been desperate just a moment ago, again burst into life as they saw a ray of hope.

“I’ll deliver your message to the Graycastle men. Now, please follow me. Well, my leg doesn’t work properly. Can someone carry me on the back?”

“I’ll do it!” a burly man answered and immediately carried White on his back.

In that way, White did not have to be worried that he would fall behind.

If everything went well, he would probably retrieve his carriage with the money from the refugees.

White did not mind telling a little lie. The most important thing now was to raise the morale and help all of them escape.

“Don’t be panic. Open your eyes and watch the others’ footprints. Make sure that you don’t roll down the mountain!” White instructed on the man’s back at the front as the latter ran toward the foot of the mountain.

…

After firing at the demons for a while, Good noticed something had gone wrong.

One plane seemed to be missing.

Although the demons were completely flattened, it was still not that easy to exterminate 30 to 40 demons all at once. Apart from the harsh weather, the power of the gunfire was also quite limited compared to their training.

Good rose and made a count. He shuddered at his finding.

The “Unicorn” operated by Her Highness was missing!

The Unicorn was completely the same as the Fire of Heaven, only that the former could only accommodate one person. It was normal that he missed the Unicorn in such a great blizzard, but Tilly was His Majesty’s sister. If anything happened to her, nobody could be absolved of the responsibility by blaming the weather condition.

Before Good could inform Finkin of the news, three more green flashes ignited the sky in the north.

That was the signal indicating that there were more enemies!

But were the demons not here?

Good’s heart skipped a beat. He immediately abandoned the severely injured demons and tore toward the green light.

“Hey, hang on, where are you going? We’ll be prosecuted in the military tribunal if we desert our post!” Finkin said while still shooting fervently.

“Shut up,” Good said irritably. “Haven’t you noticed that Her Highness isn’t here?”

Finkin turned around and gasped.

Apparently, he had also seen the three flickers that were now slowly descending.

Fortunately, as the planes were relatively close to each other, it took Good only seven minutes or so to get where the signal was.

He was a little relieved.

The biplane firing downwards not far away was none other than the “Unicorn”.

Her Highness was attacking a group of demons hiding in the forest. There seemed to be more demons here than where the refugees were.

Why were there two troops of demons?

Why did the smaller group go after the refugees?

Good was still lost in thought when Finkin at the rear shouted in excitement, “There are more demons here! Let’s follow Her Highness. I can’t wait to pull the trigger!”

The other two “Fires of Heaven” also arrived.

“Whatever,” Good thought to himself, ” the Mad Demons can’t fight back anyway.” Perhaps, the troop of demons they had met earlier had completely lost their fighting capacity. They could probably kill more of the enemies if they chose to fight here.

Just at that moment, however, a pack of Devilbeasts flew over the forest and shot up in the air. They streaked toward the “Unicorn” while howling.

It was their first time seeing their “imaginary enemies” in person, but Good instantly recognized them.

All his blood froze.

There were at least a dozen Devilbeasts.

He was only 400 to 500 meters away from them. How could he win without abandoning the princess?

He revolved rapidly a multitude of thoughts in his mind but denied his ideas. It was a split second that seemed to last forever. Before Good found the answer, Tilly reacted.

The “Unicorn” rose abruptly and jerked around before she flew toward the east. At the same time, a red flare was sent into the air and lit the sky.

It was a signal of retreat.

Good pressed hard on the gas and followed the “Unicorn” to retreat to the east.

The biplanes flew at a tremedous speed.

The fleet immediately passed the Devilbeast that was almost close enough to spear at them, and soon the four planes shook the enemies off and disappeared in the snow.

Chapter 1302: Perspicacity

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

Five days later…

“Is that Your Highness?”

“Yes, this is a piece of news that just arrived at the headquarters. We’re still in the process of confirming the number, but there are at least 600 people.”

“The garrison at the Gust Castle has taken them in. They’ll travel to Neverwinter by land after they recover from the trip.”

“No, this is our obligation.”

“Thank you. Please take a good rest.”

Edith hung up the phone after she delivered the report.

As the most advanced communication tool, wind-up telephones had become indispensable to the General Staff. However, due to the limited data transmission, the service in the Cage Mountain area was only available to the encampment of the Aerial Knights outside Thorn Town.

Edith saw an amazed Lance Kant, her third brother, as she turned around.

“What’s the matter?”

Unlike the way she treated her second brother, Cole, Edith directly hired Lance to work for the General Staff in her official capacity after the latter passed the elementary education exam. As her third brother had an exuberant and audacious personality, she thought it would be better to keep an eye on him.

Another reason was that Edith enjoyed seeing him deflated like a punctured balloon upon a failure.

“Ah… nothing. I was just surprised that you’d be so respectful to another person, sister,” Lance said as he walked up to Edith while holding a stack of documents. “You’ve never even been so polite to father.”

“I thought you’d become a little smarter after you grew up,” Edith said indifferently. “I don’t need such formalities when talking to father because I know he doesn’t care. But Tilly Wimbledon is His Majesty’s sister. If she says something about me behind my back to her brother, what do you think will happen to the House of Kant?”

“But I feel that His Majesty… doesn’t care about that either…”

“Because he’s a man, so sometimes, it works even better when you take the initative.”

“Er… I don’t quite understand…”

“To understand people is always the hardest part. It’s perfectly normal that you don’t follow,” Edith said while shrugging. “Even if you’re extremely talented, you can’t gain the final victory if you don’t understand people.”

“Could you teach me, sister?” Lance asked hopefully.

“Naturally,” Edith replied while casting the latter a glance with some interest. “However, it’d be more effective to learn on the go than just taking the lectures. Cole actually does pretty well in that. Do you want to give it a shot?”

Lance felt a coldness prevail him as he thought of Cole’s act of demeanor at home. He swallowed hard and said, “Well… I think I’d hold off on that.”

Edith replied casually, “It’s up to you.”

Lance instantly switched the subject as if he had just been exonerated from a horrible crime. He said, “By the way, did you call Her Highness to tell her that the refugees have arrived safely?”

Edith confirmed with a nod, “Her Highness asked the General Staff to take care of this matter, so I must report to her in a timely fashion.”

The whole rescue operation exceeded everybody’s expectations. Not only had the Aerial Knights reached the battlefield 200 kilometers away within less than two hours, but they had saved a great number of refugees and crushed the demons as well.

That was right. This was not just an ordinary hunt. From the information they obtained, the refugees were probably a bait the demons used to lure the army. The troop coming after was the real deal.

What if the First Army had really sent their force to support the refugees?

Due to the harsh weather and the long distance, the army must ride light and swift. The demons, on the other hand, would have awaited an exhausted troop as a hunter awaited his prey. Once the two parties clashed, the rescue team would have found themselves not only being outnumbered but also surrounded by a group of Devilbeasts.

Even if the army retreated immediately, they would have to travel nearly 100 kilometers in the snow. How many soldiers would survive this trip? Perhaps, not a single one.

This was the demons’ first tentative attack after the First Army reduced their force.

Even if the First Army had turned a blind eye on the refugees or completely overlooked the demons to the north of the Gust Castle, there was nothing to lose for the demons.

The demons had probably noticed that the Graycastle men were completely different than the soldiers in the Kingdom of Wolfheart and the Kingdom of Everwinter. Killing tons of local civilians would make no difference to the outcome of the Battle of Divine Will. However, they could weaken the human race if they managed to exterminate a rescue team.

Nevertheless, the Aerial Knights had caught them totally offguard.

The whole battle became somewhat similar to the one at the Northbound Slope a year ago. Both the demons and the First Army made judgements that they believed to be in the best interests of their own party, but the result was completely different.

Even if Tilly had not discovered the troop hiding in the forest at the rear, the outcome of the battle would not have changed.

The fleet all returned safely, and the refugees survived the hunt. It was indeed a major victory.

“The Aerial Knights are so amazing…” Lance sighed. “They not only killed dozens of Mad Demons but also got themselves out of the battle while being besieged. Even the Blessed Army of the Union couldn’t do that, right?”

“Yes, they’re wonderful.”

Edith sighed deeply and cocked her legs onto the desk while swivelling in the chair, looking a little dejected.

A bit surprised, Lance said, “You don’t look very happy.”

“I’m not unhappy, but I feel… that the General Staff has become somewhat useless now.”

“Huh?” Lance’s eyes were wide open.

“The four planes could repel more than 200 demons. What if the First Army has 100 or 1,000 of ‘Fires of Heaven’?” Edith said with a faint smile. “In that case, we simply need to send the Aerial Knights where in need. Military tactics and strategies would be simply unnecessary. Everybody can command the Aerial Knights. If that happens, what’s the point in keeping the General Staff?”

In fact, the first time Edith had seen this type of automatic flying machine, she had foreseen its great military potential. She had indeed discussed a lot with Roland regarding the application of the air force. She had even founded a research group within the General Staff to specifically study the Aerial Knights, in an attempt to maximize their power.

However, when the Aerial Knights really revealed their strength in a real battle, Edith felt somehow regretful.

The overpowering force that the Aerial Knights presented made military strategies less important. Before knights had been replaced, military tactics and formations used to be two major parts of a war. Now, they were much simplified. Since the Aerial Knights could see the entire battlefield clearly from above and possessed immense power, they could literally take over the whole battle.

In other words, they would see every move of the enemies in the sky while the demons could see nothing. The demons were groping in the dark without the ability to fight back or develop any countermeasures.

Furthermore, this was just the beginning. The “Fire of Heaven” was just a very crude model, like the original flintlock that was later transformed into more powerful and advanced Mark I.

“Then… we can go back to the City of Evernight,” Lance answered quietly.

“It’s probably too late now,” Edith said smilingly. “I’ve offended so many people to come this far. Do you think those people will let us go?”

Edith knew very well that if Roland became the ruler of this continent, nothing like this would happen. However, she had to think about the worst scenario because foul languages could always hurt people.

“I’ll… protect you,” Lance said while biting his lip.

“With what? With your current social status and official capacity? If you can’t become a leader, you’d better save these empty promises,” Edith snapped, a hint of callous pleasure in her tone. “Otherwise, it’d only be worse. For example, your enemy will probably humiliate me right in front you — ”

Edith broke off.

Soon they heard footsteps outside the door, and Ferlin Eltek entered.

“Your ladyship, you’re here…”

“What’s the matter? Any news?”

“I wish,” Morning Light said, looking troubled. “I just checked the supply list for the Aerial Knights. Perhaps, we have to adjust the logistics.”

“Yes?”

“You probably don’t know that they used thousands of bullets in the past few days, not including those consumed in the real battle,” Ferlin said agitatedly. “There are only 20 or 30 of them, but they request more ammunition than 10 Gun Battalion units put altogether! Not to mention that we have to supply them fuels and spare parts of the planes. If the number of the students doubles or triples, what should the logistics department do? Your ladyship?”

Lance suddenly found that the languid air his sister had presented just a a moment ago was gone.

Edith rose to her feet and replied casually, “You have to figure that out. You must make sure that the Aerial Knights have enough supplies.” She then turned to Lance and said, “What are you doing here?”

“Yes?” Lance was still in a sort of daze.

“Come to the intelligence room with me. It isn’t time to take a break yet,” Edith said while swinging her sheet of hair in a trenchant manner and walked out of the room.

Chapter 1303: Hints and Clues

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

The intelligence room was the largest organization in the general headquarters of the First Army. This organization was responsible for screening and storing tons of information. Lotus and Fran created an underground chamber specifically for the General Staff, and 70% of the 200 General Staff members were working here.

At the same time, it was also the most energy-consuming office. The room was not only illuminated with the Stones of Lighting, but the workers here were also offered free Chaos Drinks at night. Many other departments were envious of the intelligence agents.

However, only the intelligence agents themselves understood the hardship they had been going through every day.

After Edith proposed the intelligence collection plan, they started gathering information. Every week, they received two to three encypted letters from the Kingdom of Everwinter and the Kingdom of Wolfheart, and now, they had collected nearly 100 so far.

Although the General Staff’s main duty was to analyze information, most of the time the letters were from the scouts, which were usually well-written, concise and easy to understand. However, the 100 messages they had recently received were all pieces of information written in broken sentences. It took them quite a while to first decipher the messages. As such, the screening process was as boring and time-consuming as playing a puzzle game.

This was, nevertheless, not the worst part.

The hardest part lay in handling the encrypted letters.

The agents did not understand why there was an increasing number of messages all of a sudden, as it was quite hard to obtain information now when the demons had closed the border of the Red Mist area. Yet after Hill Fawkes became the main intelligence officer, his agents started to use various strange ways to get the messages out.

For example, the letters could be hidden in animal skins or the interlayer of a shoulder pole. Sometimes, they could be inserted in the stomach of a pickled fish. Trading merchants in the occupied area became a fantastic channel to communicate information. A lot of times, those noble merchants unknowingly became the couriers.

Because of this, the encrypted letters were sent in all kinds of manners. The agents, for instance, had to take out a silk ribbon from the stomach of a fish while enduring the terrible odour. Before reading the message, they had to clean up the letter first.

Everybody would feel resentful when their work suddenly switched from writing reports leisurely while sipping the tea to transforming a variety of garbages into useful letters and information.

Nevertheless, although full of complaint and disatisfaction, nobody slacked off, as both Edith and Iron Axe were keeping an eye on this department. Therefore, nobody would be foolish enough to delay the work under these two people’s noses.

Edith saw Ion Axe discuss something with Hill Fawkes as she entered the intelligence room. There were around dozens of pieces of paper on the desk in the center of the room. Apparently, the clerks had made a copy of the letters.

She skimmed them through and found that most of them were from the Kingdom of Everwinter.

A large part of them seemed to be useless information providing few clues, such as “a new troop of demons garrisoned in the northern city today”, “a noble suddenly passed away, and someone inherited his title”, and ” a giant stone monster is lurking around the border area”.

Edith was not surprised that the intelligence collection plan could go so well in such a short time. The success was not only attributed to Hill’s hard work but also the “Black Money”.

After she suggested Iron Axe making contact with the sender of the black card, the mysterious man agreed to work at the front. Although he only sent a messenger, he overtly expressed his wish to provide help to Graycastle. The “Black Money” was started in the Kingdom of Dawn and also had certain influences on the Kingdom of Wolfheart and the Kingdom of Everwinter, mainly on the underground market and the Rats.

Rats could not collect very useful information due to various rumors and misinformation circulated in the neighborhood, but it was better than nothing.

Edith also noticed a particular message that indicated that “sailors were forced to work” in some cities.

“What do you think of it?” Iron Axe asked as he also noticed what Edith was staring at.

“If I remember it correctly, the third princess, Garcia, brought many ships when she attacked the Kingdom of Everwinter,” Edith said thoughtfully. “If the church didn’t destroy those ships, they’re probably still in somewhere in the Kingdom of Everwinter.”

“It appears that you’re quite concerned about this matter.”

“Compared to the others, this piece of news was obtained from various sources and is relatively reliable,” Edith said while extending out her hands. “Ships are mainly used for transportation. The demons may use them to transport their army or they plan to launch an attack on the sea. However, I don’t think they’ll attack us from the ocean.”

“What’s your reason?” Iron Axe questioned.

“The demons must have known the power of cannons after so many battles. They should have known that we’ll use cannons to repel them if they sail to the Archduke Island and the Sedimentation Bay. They won’t survive on a sailing ship,” Edith explained. “If they choose to go around the port of the Kingdom of Wolfheart and get to the interior of the Kingdom of Dawn, they won’t have enough Red Mist supplies. Therefore, I’m inclined to the former possibility. To win the war, the demons must assemble their army at the front as fast as they could and attack us by land and water.”

With these words, she looked toward Hill and asked, “What do you think?”

Hill bowed to Edith and answered, “Your ladyship, I’m not good at analyzing wars, so I don’t know which way the enemies would go. The only thing I can do is to collect the information and send it to the General Staff.”

“This is a smart man,” thought Edith.

He did not blindly follow her but made his own jugdements based on the information he had. He certainly knew what his strength and weakness were. No wonder the king asked him to organize the intelligence collection work.

“Even you can’t find more clues out of it. It’s probably a dead end,” Iron Axe said resignedly. “So, we only know that the demons would assemble armies, but we don’t know where they’ll go or what their intention is. This is so frustrating.”

“The Kingdom of Wolfheart has been completely evacuated, which is why Hill can’t put his man there. If you didn’t evacuate the country, we would have probably found some clues as to the whereabouts of the demons,” Edith said half-jokingly.

“I must obey His Majesty’s order,” Iron Axe defended while shaking his head. “Plus, the First Army can’t put their hope in some Rats.”

“We’ll send you more useful information in the future, sir,” Hill Fawkes suddenly spoke.

Iron Axe raised his brows and asked, “Are you saying the information later on will be more in detail?”

“That’s right,” Hill replied. “I’ve been staying in the circus in the Kingdom of Dawn for so long, and the most important thing I’ve learned is that as long as we plan it well, we’ll naturally obtain more information.”

“Really? Could you tell me more about it?” Edith demanded with some interest.

Chapter 1304: Hints and Clues (II)

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

“In short, we just let those birds conduct the search themselves.”

Hill Fawkes produced a pencil and sketched a tree diagram on a piece of paper. “Since we pay for information instead of the person who collects them, the more information he gets, the more he earns. To obtain more information, he’ll find a way to hire more people to do the work for him. In His Majesty’s words, it’s called a top-down approach.”

“I see,” Edith commented, who immediately grasped the nature of this management style. “To expand the lower-level organization, we, as the stem of the tree, must give them some incentives to make sure that they keep working for us.”

Hill nodded and said, “Exactly. Scouts and detectives are all at the very end of the chain. They won’t change much over time. Therefore, the information would become more reliable as time progresses, although their search area can be fairly limited.”

“But they’re essentially Rats…” Iron Axe said, frowning.

“No, sir. This is the interesting part. The stem and the branch don’t have to be managers and subordinates neccessarily. Soldiers have to listen to officers, but Rats don’t necessarily need to obey Rats.”

“As long as we promise that they’ll benefit from their work, Rats can also make nobles work for them,” Edith supplied slowly.

Hill looked at Edith approvingly and said, “Yes, these incentives don’t have to be gold royals. Everyone has their own need. We simply need to know what they desire, and it doesn’t have anything to do with social classes. This means that secondary agents can be people of different socio-economic status. The reason that the information we’ve collected so far is not that comprehensible is that the Rats are still digging the surface. Once nobles start to join us, we’ll have more valuable news.”

Iron Axe pondered for a moment and said, “Even if that’s true, it’ll probably take a long time for nobles to work for us.”

“That might be the case in peacetime,” Hill returned. “However, the Kingdom of Everwinter is now undergoing dramatic changes. I believe that this process will be largely shortened. In fact, some messages have already provided us with a hint.”

“Like?” Iron Axe questionsed while stroking his chin.

Hill explained smilingly, “According to our statistical report, we’ve been receiving fewer reports about the nobles. Most of them, if any, are negative news, such as debaunchery, public brawling, etc. Rulers shouldn’t be like that in wartime, which reflects that the rulers of the Kingdom of Everwinter have abandoned their duties to protect their people. They’re having a lot of pressure, so they need to let these negative emotions out in some way. I believe that such things started after the evacuation unit of the First Army defeated the alliance army formed by the nobles.”

Hill took a pause and resumed, “Although at that time, I was in the City of Glow in the Kingdom of Dawn, I can imagine what a huge blow it was to the nobles. When people begin to feel insecure, they would put their hope in anyone that could help them, even if this person is someone that they despise the most. Sir, please rest assured. You won’t wait for too long.”

*******************

In the Snow Reflection Castle in the Kingdom of Everwinter.

“Sorry for the long wait. His lordship isn’t feeling well today, so he can’t come out to greet you. I would advise that you call on us on another day,” the butler suggested as he swept a bow. “Once his lordship feels better, he’ll let you know.”

The hall was instantly stirred.

“We’ve been waiting for weeks! Even if he’s infected with some serious disease, at least he can come out and say a word.”

“I don’t believe a single word he says. We fought for him, and where’s our lands?”

That’s right. Even if he’s not well enough to meet us, he should at least hand us the deeds!”

“This bulter is lying. I saw Viscount Narnos come out of the castle four hours later after he got in.”

“Not only the viscount but also many dancers from the tavern. Is the duke now seeking women instead of scholars to cure his disease?”

“Please, mind your language,” the butler said coolly after clearing his throat. “You’ve been without a land for too long, so you’ve probably forgotten that you’re still the subordinates of the Duke of the Northern Region. The duke is your master. You should know better than me what a crime it is to slander a lord! I don’t think you would like to sit in a cell instead of your hotel room in this weather.”

At these words, the guards at the door came forward, their armors clanking on their sides.

The hall immediately fell quiet.

The nobles knew it would not do any good if they engaged in a verbal altercation here.

The butler lowered his voice and continued, “I know you’re anxious, but the most important thing now is to defeat the Graycastle soldiers. By the way, his lordship will hold a banquet tonight in the castle parlor to receive you. Although he can’t come, he wishes you a lovely evening.”

Because of the perspective banquet, the crowd finally withdrew from the hall while muttering under their breath, looking a little more satisfied.

They immediately began to talk about the delicious food and beautiful women they would encounter in the evening.

Only Fueler still felt unhappy when he returned to his hotel.

After dealing with Marwayne for a while, he became morbidly disappointed with the duke.

The defeat at Frost Town was mainly because of the fact that the Graycastle soldiers were more proficient in using the weapons and had higher morale. The nobles could have learned the lesson and fought again. However, what had the duke done? He was not only the first person that had fled the battleground but he also locked himself in the Snow Reflection Castle, having completely forgotten about his ambition prior to the battle.

Apart from that, he failed to fulfill his promise to grant the nobles lands and treated them equally. Viscount Narnos had now the access to the castle, but the knights relying on the great nobles were shut out.

Yet before the battle, the duke had sought Fueler’s counsels a lot.

A competent lord should never broke his promise, but Marwayne broke this rule simply because he wanted to hold onto his tiny territory.

Fueler worked for Marwayne, in a hope of reviving his family. Now, all his squires and guards had been killed in action. He literally had nothing at the moment.

Could a knight with neither squires nor land be really considered as a noble? The others could still afford to wait, but what about him? Who would acknowledge his family half a year or one year later? If the demons did defeat Roland Wimbledon, Marwayne would rise to power and easily help him revive his family. The problem was that, a dishonest man as he was, would the duke really help a person with practically nothing?

Should he put his faith completely in such a careless duke or find himself a way out?

Fueler paced up and down in his bedroom and finally came to a stop.

He walked up to his desk and took out a folded envelope at the bottom of the drawer.

After a moment of hesitation, Fueler tore it open.

There was a velvety black card in it.

Chapter 1305: Lurking

Translator: Transn Editor: Transn

This is an easy job. You won’t need to take any huge risks. All you have to do is place the message in the allocated location and no one will know that you did it. The voice of the silver-masked man who called himself the leader of Black Money sounded from beside his ear once more.

Utterly ridiculous! Why earth would I help Graycastle? They even eradicated the nobles, what will I gain even if I win? Images of the conflict seemed to occur before his eyes once more.

I had thought Black Money were intelligent merchants, to think that you would utter such foolish words! Aren’t you afraid that I’ll just tie you up right now and hand you over to Lord Marwayne in exchange for a generous award instead?

If you really wanted to do that, then this conversation would have never taken place in the first place.

The man’s tone did not change, as if he didn’t care for his own safety at all.

The fact alone that I’m still sitting here is enough to prove your intentions, and it’s because that you are clever, that we’re willing to give you this opportunity.

Fueler replied in response, Unfortunately you have misjudged me. My loyalty to the Duke is unshakable. Now scram before I change my mind!

Of course, I’ll take my leave now. But my lord, this is how “opportunities” are. By no means does Black Money want to force you into this, it is your freedom to decide how you act.

The silver-masked man stood up, gave a deep bow and then lightly placed a black card onto the tea table.

I want to say something before I go: Graycastle will never forget anyone who serves them. Now…I hope to see you again.

Fueler inhaled deeply, interrupting his chaotic thoughts. The room became quiet.

Will Graycastle never forget anyone who serves… them?

How ironic. He served Duke Marwayne for the sole purpose of reviving his family’s prosperity. Roland Wimbledon, the enemy of all nobility was originally the most unforgivable person, yet now, Fueler was finding himself to be uncertain.

Although those bastards from Black Money were scum, they were utterly right. If he was really going to serve the Duke of the Northern Region to the very end then he would have ripped the card into threads ages ago, rather than carefully hiding it beneath the drawer.

After a long period of silence, Feuler arched his head backwards, sighed, then sat down in front of his desk.

He pulled out a white sheet of paper and a goose-feather quill.

Was there anymore he could lose?

The notion of taking back his territory was becoming more and more distant. It seemed like he didn’t really have a reason to grit his teeth and keep persevering.

Who cares. He wouldn’t be affected negatively in any way as long as he followed Black Money’s instructions. It would simply be akin to placing a bet on both sides. If the demons win, the current situation couldn’t possibly get any worse. If the people from Graycastle are triumphant, there may be a way for him to acquire compensation through other ways.

Finishing his thoughts, Fueler put down his quill.

…

At dusk, Fueler put on his trench coat and felt cap and walked into the “Horn Alley” of the inner city.

Horn Alley was territory belonging to the Northern Chamber of Commerce. All of the passers-by were merchants. By sunset, there were very few people out and about.

Fueler found the location that the silver-masked man had described in a place on a gentle slope. In between two brick houses sprouted a large, silver fir tree.

In fact, the delivery method that the masked man spoke of was also one of the reasons that prompted Fueler to make his decision.

With no physical contact with the recipient, the risks were largely diminished. With this, at least he wouldn’t have to worry about Black Money blackmailing him with the message, or someone seeing him interacting strangely with an unknown person.

Fueler wandered around the vicinity for a while and upon affirming that there were no suspicious people near him, quickly strode towards the back of the silver fir tree and felt at the hole in the middle of the trunk—sure enough, there was a secret compartment hidden inside. The door of the compartment was made completely out of an ordinary wood, if he hadn’t touched it with his own hands, he wouldn’t have noticed it.

He stuffed the letter containing the message inside the compartment and pushed the wooden plank back in place. Now he had completed the task of placing the message. He had intentionally written the message in script so that even if a third party discovered it, it would be impossible for them to connect the handwriting to him.

Of course, his mission was not entirely complete yet.

Next, Fueler returned to his residence and placed a flower pot on the window sill of his bedroom. For a person living in the high-end section of the Inner city, such decorative items were easily accessible. Nobody would care about an inconspicuous pot plant. However, to those that were observing him in the dark, this was a sign that the message had been delivered.

From the beginning to the end, he didn’t need to meet anyone in person. In regards to who would take the message, or how it would get into Graycastle’s hands, these things no longer had anything to do with him.

In the moment he set down the flower pot Fueler almost seemed to experience a liberating feeling.

To think they’d be so meticulous in even the simple act of gathering intel, the gap between the two kings is truly redoubtable… Fueler thought as he stood before his window, gazing into the distance at the castle district, ablaze with lights under the red haze. When he thought about how the “losers” of the battle were still cheerfully enjoying the evening party, any hope he had in Marwayne died.

There was only one more question remaining.

Could Graycastle really defeat the demons?

*******************

The messenger pushed a thick stack of paper onto the damp and dilapidated wooden table.

“Is this today’s portion?” Smarty lit a candle, “Thank you.”

The messenger gave no reaction.

Smarty sighed and repeated himself with hand signals.

Only then did the messenger nod.

Indeed, this messenger was a silent warrior trained by his master. He was deaf and mute and could only be commanded or interrogated through simple hand gestures. Unfortunately, there wasn’t a hand gesture to express gratitude.

“Keep watch outside, don’t let anyone inside.” After he got silent warrior to leave, Smarty began carefully reading through the messages page by page.

This place was the allocated property where Black Money organized their underground chamber of commerce. Typically only the invited could enter so in theory the possibility of outsiders breaking in was small. Nevertheless, Smarty chose to go through the intel in the basement, in the case that if something did occur, he would have more time to destroy the evidence.

Although Smarty did not know why his master was so serious about Graycastle’s battle, this was not an issue he could intervene in. Since his master had commanded to support Graycastle with all his power, the only thing he could do was obey to the best of his ability.

Currently, his most important mission was to organize the intel and deliver it into Graycastle’s hands silently and without a trace.

Although the people from Graycastle demanded that not a single piece of intel could be missed, opportunities to secretly sending things outside the city were scarce, thus there was an issue of prioritization to consider. Considering that the trading caravans qualified to pass came through once a week, he had to turn the most reliable intel into a confidential letter and mingle it amongst the trading goods going towards Wolfheart within a week. As for the rest of the intel, he could only search for another way.

Most of the time, intel came from a Rat’s words, causing them to be extremely disorganized. Usually he would have to waste huge amounts of time to filter it. However this time, Smarty noticed a letter amongst the intel that stood out from the rest.

The characters on it were neat and organized. They definitely were not words that were carelessly copied down in a bar or on the streets. The words were also written with high-grade ink and there was not a single wrinkle on the paper. Clearly, the letter was written in an environment far superior to ones that Rats are usually found in.

Subconsciously holding his breath, he read the letter carefully from start to finish.

Indeed, the contents of the letter were far different from the rest.

It was the first to mention the core of the Army of Demons: Sky Lord Hect Zod.

Chapter 1306: The Bloodstained Message

Translator: Henyee Editor: Henyee

After flipping through the letter, a chill ran down Smarty’s back.

A demon lord that could open the gate to Hell, letting troops come and go as they like?

Unquestionably, this intel was of utmost importance—In truth, he had been perplexed by the oddly unscathed fall of Snow Reflection Castle. The only thing that could be said from it was that the demons invaded from the north side. All the other explanations varied and contradicted each other. Evidently, all the citizens who witnessed the arrival of demons with their own eyes had died during the invasion.

At last he had conclusive affirmation to his questions.

But what shocked him even more was that the demon lord spoken of was familiar with human laws. Not only was the demon lord able to engage proficiently with the nobility, but in a short span of time, he was also able to become the real ruler behind the scenes of the Kingdom of Everwinter. Currently, the enlistment of citizens in the domains of the kingdom was all his doing. The handsome benefits promised by the demon lord were also far greater than what the people of Graycastle were capable of.

Additionally, the letter’s illustration of the patterns in the drafting of citizens was extremely valuable. Although it wasn’t the same as information on the power distribution of demons, one could at least infer from it approximately where resources were allocated.

What was certain was that this letter was definitely not written by the likes of a Rat or merchant. The writer’s perspective betrayed that he was undoubtedly a member of Everwinter’s upper class.

The contents of the entire letter were organized, logical, clear and concise. There was no need for transcription—it would be difficult to make it anymore concise than it already was. All Smarty had to do was send it out in one piece and it would already be a critical piece of intel. In terms of priority, it was without a doubt the highest.

The problem now was that the merchant group used to deliver intel left Snow Reflection Castle yesterday. In order not catch anyone’s attention, Black Money only planted one of their members inside the merchant group, and that member was merely a cart driver, making it virtually impossible for him to make the entire group pull back in the direction they came. The next merchant group would only be able to leave the following week.

If we were to add on the time spent stopping and moving along the way, the delivery time would be drawn out even longer.

After hesitating for a long time, Smarty finally jumped up, gathered the rest of the paper on his table, and put them away in his drawer, leaving only the letter on the table.

Next he had to seal it with waterproof wax.

After he finished, he blew out the candle, slotted the letter somewhere close to his body and returned to the first floor. Using hand gestures, he told the silent warrior, “I’m going to personally leave the city for a while. If something unprecedented happens here, light the fuel oil downstairs.”

Just when Smarty was about to turn and go out the door, the silent warrior caught Smarty’s arm and very slightly shook his head. Then, the silent warrior pointed to himself.

Stay, and leave the dangerous things to me…?

Smarty chuckled lightly. “I’ll only be sending a letter. I’ll be back in two or three days at most. You can’t speak, nor do you know where the exchange point is, so you can’t help me with this mission.”

However there were no hand gesture to express such complicated words so he only made one hand gesture: “This is a command.”

The hand gripping him released.

Smarty patted the silent warrior’s chest and left the room without looking back.

Since his master told him to support Graycastle with everything at his disposal, the most important thing he had to do now was deliver this letter as soon as possible. After all, in the words of the Graycastle folk: intel is dependent on timeliness; the longer that intel is held back, the more changes that occur and the less reliable it is.

For such occasions, they had even set up an emergency contact point a bit over five kilometers away from the border of the city. At the contact point, they prepared an incredible animal courier. Smarty had heard that it could deliver messages to the Kingdom of Dawn within a few days.

That village would be the destination of his journey.

Leaving Snow Reflection Castle without permission indeed had its risks, but in general they were all within his control. In reality, people were escaping the Northern Region via all sorts of different methods everyday. There were even people leaving Everwinter—the red haze and blood-red moon above people’s heads didn’t actually affect their lives in any way, it was just that Graycastle’s propaganda and the rumors about the demons had already cemented themselves in them; no matter how much the feudal lord tried to stop it, he was unable to completely dissipate the fear the people had of these terrifying barbarian races.

Undoubtedly, these daily escapists were Smarty’s best camouflage.

Smarty knew that as long as he moved alone, the probability of him getting caught by flying demons was low. The guards on the streets were even easier to deal with as in the end, gold royals were the ticket to all passages in the human world.

Reality was not much different to Smarty’s predictions.

As dawn broke the following morning, Smarty safely passed through the southern gate of Snow Reflection Castle. In order to enjoy the gold royals all to himself, the guard even made sure not to alert anyone else, quietly opening a small door for Smarty on the inner side of the city wall.

Once he crossed the icy abyss, the rest of the journey would be free of obstruction.

Everytime Smarty caught sight of a black shadow in the sky, he would quickly tuck himself under the snow. His white coat was a natural camouflage and for those flying in the sky, his footsteps did not really look much different to the ones left by wild beasts.

When it was afternoon, Smarty could already vaguely glimpse smoke curling upwards from the kitchen chimneys of the village.

Wiping the white frost from his nose, he couldn’t help but quicken his pace.

Just like the system inside the city, Smarty didn’t need to directly meet with anyone from Graycastle. All he had to do was place the intel in the agreed spot and leave a secret signal.

Yet at this moment, Smarty heard the clip-clopping of horse hooves coming from behind him.

Smarty jumped and twisted around. His heart dropped slightly. What the hell, why are there Snow Reflection Castle soldiers here?

Graycastle had chosen this village specifically because it was remote. It would be difficult to notice even if one or two outsiders snuck in. Usually if the nobles wanted to intercept runaways they would choose to do it near the main road since they unlikely had any reason to be here.

The distance between Smarty and the soldiers quickly shortened. Clearly they had seen his figure, so there was really no point in hiding anymore.

Smarty decidedly stopped walking and turned towards the oncomers with an ingratiating smile plastered across his face. There were two riders in total, this probably wouldn’t be too difficult as long as he gave enough gold royals.

One soldier reined in his horse in front of him and looked down at him condescendingly. “Older brother,” he said, “I just knew that these fugitives would choose a remote path for their escape. We found one just like I said.”

“Ah, lucky us.”

As he thought… Were they one of the patrol parties sent to catch escapists?

“M-My lord, I beg of you, spare my life!” Pretending to be scared out of his wits, Smarty fell to his knees into the snow and held up his money bag in both hands, revealing a sparkle of the gold royals inside. ” I couldn’t stand staying in the same place as those demons from hell, they’re monsters who’d eat you without a blink of an eye! I can give you all of my savings, just please let me go!”

“Oh? You’ve saved up quite a bit there.” The rider took the money bag with a hint of pleasure in his tone.

“It’s all yours now… O-oh yeah, I have some relatives in the Kingdom of Wolfheart, as long as you don’t take me back, I’ll definitely find a chance to repay you in the future!”

“You can stand up now.”

Smarty silently released a breath. Usually, once he reached this point he had basically made it through. Refugees who had saved up gold royals were definitely a small minority; what’s more he had “relatives in a neighboring country,” so coming across someone like him was unbelievably unlikely. If killing people didn’t give them any advantages, the soldiers wouldn’t want to cause any more unnecessary trouble. After all, letting one or two refugees off didn’t incur them any losses, so there was no point in destroying the possibility of being repaid in the future.

But the rider didn’t wave his hand for him to scram. Instead, he raised his vizor and said, “Look at me carefully.”

A glaring scar was scrawled over the rider’s cheek, as if his face had been gnawed on by some ferocious beast. His entire ear was gone and even half of his eye was deformed and twisted.

The flapping of his skin showed that this injury had only recently healed.

“My lord, this is…”

“This was caused by Graycastle’s firearms,” the knight said slowly, “I thought I was a goner then, but I managed to survive. Until now, I can still feel the heat piercing my face. It reminds me constantly, who it was that caused all of this—”

At the end of his speech, the rider’s tone turned completely cold.

An intense feeling of alarm arose inside Smarty.

But before he had the chance to create a distance between them, the other person who was referred to as the younger brother raised his hand and struck Smarty’s face hard with his horse whip.

The scene in front of him turned black. Smarty collapsed with his hands to his face.

“Yes, it’s you! If it weren’t for you damned runaways, why would I be fighting Graycastle with my life? What ‘Battle of Divine Will’, what ‘fate of mankind’, that’s all bullsh**!” At this point, the knights voice had already escalated into a roar. “Be at ease, I won’t take you back and I won’t kill you here and now—the only thing I want to do is let you fugitives taste my pain!”

Afterwards he raised his reins and ushered his horse towards Smarty’s legs.

“Crack—”

A wave of indescribable, excruciating pain immediately shot through him as Smarty subconsciously let out a strangulated yell.

Then came his second leg.

Until the snow was spotted with blood and his legs had become a clump of vaguely connected muddy flesh did the rider stop the horse’s trampling.

“Relax, you are not the first and you will not be the last,” the knight laughed sinisterly. “Now… you can run away as much as you want.”

Smarty didn’t pay attention to when the two riders left.

Only after biting and breaking open his lip, could he force his wandering attention together.

The lower half of his body had already turned completely numb and the snow was sapping his body heat away from him bit by bit.

He felt at the clothes on his chest—the letter was still in its original place. In those two riders’ eyes, he was probably no different to a corpse now.

Surprisingly, he bore no hatred towards the two, nor did he feel any intense dissatisfaction at being so easily trampled over. Under the ruthless torture of both the piercing pain and cold, thinking had already become an unbelievably difficult task. The only thought lingering in him was of the message close to his chest.

With the last of his energy, Smarty began shifting his body towards the agreed location.

By the time he wriggled to a place on top of a hill that overlooked the village, the curtain of night was slowly draping over the horizon. The occasional coruscating lights inside the village seemed to be right next to him; yet at the same time, as far from him as the stars of the night sky.

He had not put the letter into the hiding spot, because he himself was the final vessel of the letter.

In the moment when the darkness was about to swallow all living things, his master, Banach Lothar’s kind face emerged before Smarty’s eyes.

Smarty closed his eyes and lightly murmured, “Father…”

Chapter 1307: Flaw

Translator: Henyee Translations Editor: Henyee Translations

Three days later, after the letter had been transferred several times, it finally landed in the hands of the command headquarters at Cage Mountain. After Hill Fawkes opened the letter and scanned it, it was once more classified as “highest-priority intel” and immediately transferred into Edith’s hands.

After skimming over the letter, the Pearl of the Northern Region furrowed her brow.

“How many people are on Archduke Island right now?” she demanded loudly.

The advisors immediately exchanged looks. Morning Light was the first to reply.

“My Lady, there are over three hundred people stationed on the island from the First Army, around twenty-five hundred from the construction team, and about the same amount of island civilians. If you’d like the finer details on staff composition, I can get the data—”

“There’s no need,” Edith interrupted. “Invite Iron Axe and the other military officers inside. We need to adjust our plan immediately! Quick!”

“Adjust…?”

“It doesn’t matter if they’re soldiers, construction workers, or people from Graycastle, Kingdom of Dawn or Kingdom of Wolfheart, everybody needs to evacuate Archduke Island immediately!” she declared gravely. “That place is already a dead island.”

A clatter of shock followed; however, even in their surprise, their long training in their professions prompted them to immediately follow through with the command.

In the midst of the clamor inside the office, Edith’s gaze fell onto the piece of paper in her palm.

It had come along with the letter.

After several breaths, she clenched her fist and lightly released a sigh.

The high-ranking officers of the First Army very quickly gathered together and took turns in reading the letter sent from the Snow Reflection Castle in Everwinter.

“Sky Lord Hackzord…” like the others, Brian’s face was pale and unsettled. “If the contents of the letter are completely accurate, this damned ability is way too overpowered. A range of several kilometers, one that can be used repeatedly… If that’s the case, it would not not even take a few days before the entire Everwinter will be obliterated, even the most stubborn city wouldn’t stand a chance.”

Lightning and Maggie had come across a high-ranking demon near the rapture before. Its untraceable power was enough for it to be classified as an opponent to be highly wary of. Now, they knew that this demon was most likely the Sky Lord Ursrook talked about, and what they witnessed was far from its real power—not only could he pass through the portal himself, he could even maneuver entire troops through it. Such formidable power was terrifying on a strategic level.

The full weight of the title, “grand demon lord”, settled on everyone’s shoulders.

Evacuating Archduke Island was now a crucial task nobody was doubting.

After all, getting on the island was easier than leaving it. If the strait, a natural barrier, was unable to obstruct the movements of the enemy, it would become a cage trapping them all.

Moreover, they had to utilize every single minute!

According to the citizen drafting patterns described in the letter and the clues derived by the general staff, the demons had probably gathered an army of a considerable scale on the frontline. A massive attack could be launched at any time.

Iron Axe commanded, “Stop all construction and fortification on Archduke Island. Start moving everyone on the island immediately! This is not limited to the rented ships, I want to see everything that can float participating in this evacuation!”

“Yessir,” the troops responded in unison.

After everyone left with their orders, Agatha said worriedly, “Why didn’t such a powerful demon shown up in the second Battle of Divine Will?”

“I believe it’s due to one of three reasons.” Edith’s voice was still calm as usual. “One, Hackzord had yet to evolve into a grand demon lord and didn’t possess his current abilities back then. Two, they believed humans were insignificant and regarded the Sky-sea Realm as their top priority. As for the third reason…” she said as she paused intentionally, “perhaps the higher-ranking demons believed that Hackzord was not suitable to battle humans.”

Iron Axe seemed to be able to read her mind. “You think it’s the third reason?”

The Pearl of the Northern Region shrugged. “Although the first reason is valid in theory, it’s really just avoiding the issue. The second one’s does not have a solid reason—although the demons have always been battling with the Sky-sea Realm, considering their strong attention towards the relic of the gods, they definitely wouldn’t have let the relic escape their hands if they could have easily defeated the Union. Underestimating the enemy is undoubtedly the most foolish thing you can do in a battle that determines the fate of your race. In other words, I’m guessing that they have already used their power to their maximum potential.”

At this, the Ice Witch’s dulled-gray eyes finally seemed to brighten up a bit. “But… the Union hadn’t learned of how to make firearms at that time. If even the city walls are no longer effective, I’m afraid that the Union will be defeated even faster this time. They might not even have the time to move the relic of the gods.”

“Thus, this is something worth thinking deeply about.” Edith lightly tapped the table surface, not directly answering the Ice Witch’s worries. “There are some descriptions in this letter that interest me—according to the few interactions that the writer has had with the Sky Lord, not only does Hackzord never used his power to directly enter the feudal lord’s castle, he barely ever meets with multiple nobles at the same time. Most of his commands are conveyed through Sigils, as if he is wary against them. Such behavior is clearly disadvantageous for him if he wants to win their loyalty; this is evident from the contents of the letter. But the question is, what threat could those nobles possibly pose to him?”

The Ice Witch looked dazed. “Could you be thinking of… God’s Stone of Retaliation?”

“No matter how I look at it, it’s the only possible reason.” The Pearl of the Northern Region nodded in reply. “Since Extraordinaries can be ashes or books, why must a grand lord be a Magic Slayer?”

“That…” Agatha failed to react immediately. The biggest difference between a high-ranking demon and a Mad Demon was the amount of power they had. Indeed there was no concrete evidence that a demon would then have the power of a Magic Slayer upon advancement. What’s more, this would answer all the questions she had previously—the reason why the Sky Lord didn’t appear on the frontline of the Fertile plains was because he simply wasn’t good at direct battle!

It didn’t matter whether he was invading the the Holy City built via the God’s Stone mines, or battling the Extraordinaries wearing God’s Stones of Retaliation, or suffering the blow of Divine Will, which was even stronger than the Extraodinaries’ power—all of this was a great threat to any demon that was not a Magic Slayer. The Sky Lord’s power was vital for the demons, so he didn’t show up in the previous two battles!

“But this time he is participating personally…” Iron Axe said in a low voice.

“Perhaps some change left him with no other choice.” Edith walked towards the window and gazed out towards the mainland in the north. “For example, the first main attacker could have been Ursrook or some other grand demon lord, but under some circumstances, Hackzord was forced to emerge from behind the scenes. If this is really the case, it’s definitely good news for us—no matter what, facing one grand demon lord definitely beats facing several grand lords at once.”

“Have you already figured out how to deal with Hackzord?”

“His ability to maneuver armies at his will is unique in terms of strategy, but using it to attack is not actually a great choice,” Edith said slowly. “As long as we don’t suffer too many losses on Archduke Island, the outcome is still up in the air. Thus, the most important thing for us to do right now is evacuate as many people and firearms from the island as possible, especially the cannons. ”

Iron Axe released a long sigh of relief. “From what you’ve said, this piece of intel is really valuable. I wonder who the writer and sender is? If the information is reliable, we really owe it to him.”

After a long silence, Edith handed the crumpled piece of paper over to Iron Axe.

There were only a few simple sentences written on it.

It was written by Hill’s subordinate before he sent it to them.

I do not know his name.

When I discovered him, his body was already frozen in a way no different from ice.

At his chest, I found this letter.

Only this item still held a trace of warmth.

Chapter 1308: The Great Evacuation of Archduke Island

Translator: Henyee Translations Editor: Henyee Translations

Via the flying animal courier, the evacuation command rapidly spread outwards from Cage Mountain.

The instructions were carried out to the maximum capability wherever there were Graycastle forces. There was no prevarication or fooling around. Over half a year under Roland Wimbledon was enough to make the nobles who chose to serve him clear about the way he did things.

Honestly, they were shocked by the unexpected “power” they were exhibiting themselves—going all out in the current situation, they were achieving demands they used to think impossible. When they encountered a complex problem, they thought about it and then solved it. Although they were still the same group of people, they produced vastly distinct results under a different governing system.

Baron Jean Bate was one of these people.

Jean Bate felt conflicted as he watched the busy scene inside his mansion. Originally, he regarded his family as an insignificant family lacking in both ability and ambition. It was only because he posed no threat to them that the King of Wolfheart, Tusk and Redstone allowed him to perpetually manage Sedimentation Bay, thus maintaining the fine balance between the noble families.

Now, his scholars and subordinates were responsible for planning the movements of tens of thousands of people and thousands of ships. Even though a large number of those were fishing ships, they were under his jurisdiction nevertheless as even the smallest of ships needed to be docked before they could be unloaded. Tens of thousands of people was equivalent to the total population of a large inner city in the continent and the number of ships he now controlled was more than all the merchant ships docked on the shores of Wolfheart added together.

Ordinarily, the baron would never believe that his family could manage a project of such immense scale. If someone had suggested it prior, he would have thought that they were either joking or didn’t understand the complexities of management at all.

Now, Jean Bate realized that not only had he underestimated his own abilities, he had underestimated his clan’s.

As long as they were given a hard push, and led via appropriate methods and regulations, astonishing potential could be squeezed forth from the people.

In the beginning, he mostly served Graycastle because he had no other choice; after all, the fate of his family and assets had been completely in Graycastle’s hands; disobedience was not an option. Gradually, however, he found himself taking a liking to this feeling. Thousands of people moved just from a single command of his, accomplishing their given task with high precision and efficiency. Perhaps this was the true essence behind power.

Even though he had many more superiors above him compared to the past, the power he held in his hands was now far more physical and tangible, and he was certain from the energetic expressions on their faces as they rushed about that his subordinates shared his sentiments.

Leading one hundred intelligent people surpasses leading ten thousand idiots by far.This was probably the most memorable lesson the baron got out of this.

This governing regime, which was polar opposite to the “aristocrat way”, could turn not-so-bright people into clever ones. Then what would be the potential of people who were naturally geniuses?

Jean Bate no longer held any doubts that Roland Wimbledon would become Emperor over the four countries.

—That is, as long as humans could survive the Battle of Divine Will.

…

Reminiscent to the higher-class managers, the situation among the civilians was also hectic.

What Graycastle had demonstrated in the past—that they were true to their words and always repaid their debts—caused their evacuation announcement to be held in high esteem. Upon hearing that the First Army was handing out a munificent reward to all who helped transport soldiers and weapons, everyone who had the ability actively participated in order to get a share of the spoils.

People who relied on the sea to make a living were the first to respond. The sailors had been searching all over the place to borrow carriages in hopes of transporting goods on the mainland to earn a living. Now, they were all returning to their main professions.

Following them were the fishermen. The value of the reward given by the First Army was calculated by the number of people and weight of cargo transported. Because the strait separating Archduke Island and the mainland was not wide, people were bringing out their sloops and even their heirloom dinghies. If they didn’t have sails, they used paddles. Just one round trip across the strait earned them several gold royals. Anyone could do the math.

Thus, in order to hold a larger number of people and supplies in one go, civilians even created multi-bodied dinghies and dinghies connected to each other in a train-like formation. To them, it was still worth it even if their creations broke apart after one or two voyages.

The First Army only made one requirement: “Boats are forbidden to contain any sort of shade that would block falling snow”. Aside from that, all other floating apparatuses were accepted without a question. Within a short period of time, the sea was covered in boats of all sizes coming and going from the shore. From afar, they looked like the migration of ants to different nests.

Of course, the Witch Alliance was not idle either.

“Seagull” was the most effective transporter out of all the transporting apparatuses. Within a day, it made almost fifty round trips between the two shores. Lightning and Maggie accompanied the Aerial Knights in patrolling the western side of Archduke Island, fighting away the occasional beasts that were scattered around the area. Molly and Hummingbird, coined the “ultimate pair”, made the originally extremely time-consuming labor of unloading a breeze. It could be said that without their help, it would have been impossible to undertake such a large-scale moving operation, especially when the handling capacities of a few harbor city wharfs were considered.

People, weapons, construction equipment… What had taken several weeks to transport onto Archduke Island were all transported back within a couple of days. Most people had expected such a hasty evacuation to end up in a catastrophe. It would have been unsurprising if over half of the paraphernalia went missing; in fact, managing to transport all the people back alone would have been a great feat. But reality proved that pretty much all of the objects came back in the same way they were delivered on the island. Excluding the abandoned construction materials and some insignificant tools, the losses incurred in items such as weapons and explosives were less than ten percent. The shockingly efficient management of this whole event reminded everybody of Graycastle’s prowess once more.

Just when the evacuation was nearing completion, Sylvie sent a warning of the highest threat-level to the command HQ!

Traces of a huge number of demons had appeared in the red haze!

…

At almost the exact same time, Hackzord “saw” the observer through the parasitic Eye Demons. It was as if she had suddenly materialized in his mind; her every single movement was clear and precise.

She was a female Awakened with long, curly green hair, the one described in Ursrook’s report as the key extermination target. With her extremely expansive wide field of view, she was strategically a huge threat to the demon race. Only a God’s Stone could stop her.

He silently remembered her appearance and looked away from her.

She was staying in the center of a highly guarded city. Getting rid of her was a good suggestion, but it was not something he needed to do personally. He was the King’s most important asset, his right-hand man. If he was harmed, it would be an indelible pity for the whole race. Thus there was no reason for him to put himself in danger.

What’s more, Hackzord had a more important target right now.

According to the reports of his sentries, the humans had been moving about a lot near the coast of Wolfheart, especially around Archduke Island. Clearly, his enemy had set their eyes on the strait and was not ready to hand it over to him on a silver platter.

Without question, the humans were going to pay a terrible price for their mistake.

According to the intel he acquired from the nobles in the Kingdom of Everwinter, the Graycastle’s army numbered in the tens of thousands. If he could devour all of the defending troops on Archduke Island in one fell swoop, it would deal a huge blow to the humans.

He was going to prove to all the other demons and grand lords that he, the Sky Lord, was also a grand lord that could lead the western front to victory!

With this in mind, Hackzord summoned the first distortion door!

Chapter 1309: Thunder

Translator: Henyee Translations Editor: Henyee Translations

The outbreak of war on the western front had dramatically changed the Sky Lord’s mindset.

In the past, his understanding of humans came from various battle reports and Holy See meetings. Along with their obvious contempt for the lowlifes, it was the general consensus of virtually all grand lords that humans lacked Awakened warriors. It was just as difficult for humans to upgrade as demons. The humans’ overall strength was volatile as it was impossible to tell the extent of an Upgraded’s power beforehand.

Human males who possessed no magical power at all were on the battlefield purely to add to the headcount. They were akin to the Inferior Demons of his race; however, Inferior Demons were utterly abandoned after the first Battle of Divine Will. Now, they weren’t even allowed to participate in battle, and were only used for manual labor at most. Just from this, one could see the difference in strength between the two races.

The Sky-sea Realm inhabitants were even more highly-evolved. From their land-engulfing ships to their most basic soldier, every one of them possessed remarkable magical power, as if they were designed just for war. Even several of the demonic beasts that they corrupted and controlled eventually grew into ones containing magical ability. Undeniably, the Sky-sea Realm was the strongest among the four races.

Precisely because of the difference in strength, senior demons regarded the legacy that would be left behind by humans after the second Battle of Divine Will as something in the bag.

This was also why Ursrook’s last words caused such a great stir on the Presiding Holy See.

Now however, Hackzord had come to believe with a greater certainty that Ursrook had not been exaggerating.

Even if humans’ exceptional utilization of fire was not enough to raise the King’s concern, the new weapon Hackzord’s people had discovered two weeks ago was a completely different story.

Without the help of witches, human males—creatures that were supposed to be merely extra trimmings—actually flew via a strangely modeled iron bird!

His first reaction when he heard the news was that it was definitely impossible.

Since ancient times, excluding birds, the sky was a place dominated by magic users. The saying that God resided in the place above the sky layered the blue dome above their heads with a greater sense of holiness and divinity. Yet how could species without even a drop of magical power intrude this holy domain?

However, there was more than one witness to this phenomenon. Upon accepting the news, he realized that that the humans’ rapid growth in strength may not only be owed to their manipulation of fire.

Indeed, he was slowly being convinced of Silent Disaster’s shocking “Upgrade Theory”—It was likely that the Nightmare Lord had realized this possibility before him, which was why she decided to enter the Realm of Mind in search for answers.

After all, the rate that the humans were evolving was way too fast.

There wasn’t any mention of the iron bird in Ursrook’s report. If humans already possessed such a weapon at the time, there would be no reason not to use it. The only explanation was that in less than a year, the developments of humans had already reached the realm of the sky.

Such a sudden change could only be explained by upgrading.

Once males also become a main force in battle, the humans’ fighting ability would undoubtedly multiply dramatically. Perhaps this was Ursrook’s real warning in his last words.

Fortunately, Hackzord was substantially more familiar with the sky than fire. The iron birds the humans created were not much stronger than Devilbeasts. As long as he was here, nobody else was allowed to touch the sky!

This time, the attack will not fail like the previous time.

His confidence was not because he looked down on his enemy. At this point, underestimating the enemy was unquestionably stupid.

His confidence came from his own title.

Because he was the supreme lord of the sky!

After passing through the door, the Sky Lord appeared on the edge of the island.

Constantly lingering by his side were Parasitic Eye Demons who came with him. If Eye Demons were regarded as a rare species, than the scarcity of Parasitic Eye Demons was on a whole other level; they were an extremely precious resource.

Despite the high price, Hackzord placed them on the front line without hesitation, letting them travel by his side. This was the only way he could handle the other key target mentioned by Ursrook: a witch that specialized in exceptionally long-range attack.

Up until he arrived on the island, the witch’s appearance still hadn’t materialized in his mind. This meant that humans’ only asset that could threaten him wasn’t present on the island.

At the same time, he didn’t see any observers that would be able to catch sight of him.

There was no better time than now.

Hackzord didn’t hesitate any more and activated the complete form of the Distortion Door!

A black hole rapidly spread out from behind him and very swiftly extended several meters outwards. Any natural barrier would be rendered useless against the Door!

A red haze gushed out. Siacis, a higher ascendant, was the first to appear before him. “My lord, your army is ready.”

“Convey my command: Seize this island and kill all who resist!”

“As you wish!” Siacis let out a piercing scream. As a psychic who had undergone three upgrading ceremonies, this scream was more than enough to drop any human who didn’t wear a God’s Stone instantly. Even if they did have one on them, the mind blast would cause them to fall in a trance. Simultaneously, it was a signal to commence the attack. When the scream ended, massive numbers of Primal Demons and Symbiotic Demons poured out from the Distortion Door towards the center of the island.

The strength of humans’ fire bolts lay in their long range. As long as they could close the distance, these new Symbiotic Demons would definitely be able to break through the enemy’s line of defense in one go.

Very quickly, the vanguard traversed the peripheral of the island and closed in on the humans’ settlement.

Yet there were still no sounds of fire.

This caused Hackzord to feel a shred of astonishment.

Just when he had managed to get himself to view the humans as equals to his own race, what was with the huge oversight they were making? Could it be that they still hadn’t noticed that their territory was being invaded?

“My lord…” A quarter of an hour later, Siacis hastily hurried over. “We have already captured the inner city; however… we didn’t discover any traces of humans. This place is an empty city!”

“What did you say?” Hackzord’s eyes widened.

“There are still many uncompleted buildings inside the city. From their color, it seems that the buildings were recently under construction, I’m afraid the humans have probably abandoned Archduke Island one or two days ago.”

So he was saying… the boats spotted by the sentries were not for sending weapons onto the island, but evacuating the soldiers from the island?

But… how could this be possible?

The humans acted as if they knew he was going to attack Archduke Island! He had intentionally made his troops avoid all cities and towns. Every path he traveled had been checked by Eye Demons. The easiest way this secret could be leaked was via those human workers, so he ordered his subordinates to put them under centralized supervision, removing all possibility of communication with the outside. Even if the enemy had noticed that something was odd, they wouldn’t have evacuated so quickly!

How did the information get leaked?

Before he could think about the problem properly, an ear-splitting explosion suddenly erupted from the island centre. In an instant, the earth began to violently shake.

A cluster of blindingly bright fireballs illuminated the cloudy day. In the midst of their light, rolling clouds of black smoke shot into the sky and an intense air wave swept across the entire inner city. All the soldiers in the city were engulfed by the surging smoke in a blink of an eye.

Chapter 1310: Trapped Beast

Translator: Henyee Translations Editor: Henyee Translations

Hackzord closed the Distortion Door with a grim face.

Even the stupidest person would be able tell that they had just been completely outwitted by the humans!

“Those lowlifes—!” Siacis roared furiously. His murderous intent was clear in the wild twisting of whiskers on his cheeks.

“Shut up!” Hackzord interrupted him. “If they were lowlifes, than who are we, the ones got outwitted by lowlifes? From now on, I don’t want to hear you calling them ‘lowlifes’ ever again!”

Then he leaped up and flew toward the other end of the island.

The black smoke was still billowing upwards ceaselessly, forming a thick column of smoke. The indistinct flashing of firelight from below it caused the column to resemble a jet of magma shooting upwards from the ground. The interior of the city was in disarray. Even in places where the fireball’s shockwave hadn’t reached, there were bodies of several Primal Demons strewn in across the area at different angles, dead or alive.

However, this was not what he was focusing on at the moment—the milk had already been spilt. Staying there would not make his losses any smaller and would only add fuel to his fury. If he had the energy, he would rather use it to make his enemies pay.

As expected, on the south side of the island, the Sky Lord spotted some boats that had not yet gone far from the island. Even though they were in full sail, in the face of his abilities, they were equivalent to being stationary.

Just when he was about to close the gap in a single stride, a ray of light below him caught his attention.

A silhouette flew out from the outer region island and rapidly towards the southern side.

No wonder! He had believed that the person responsible for the detonation of the explosion had been buried in the flames together with his vanguard troops. To think that the humans had actually planned a full retreat!

Getting a witch to activate the explosion in order to retreat easily from the battlefield?

As if it was going to be so easy!

The Sky Lord immediately switched targets, opened a distortion door and appeared in front of the witch.

She was a female with pale, blonde hair. She revealed an expression of shock, as if she didn’t expect him to suddenly appear. Without another word Hackzord reached out to grab her—

Yet his hand grasped thin air.

The female before his eyes suddenly moved with an explosive speed, tearing hundreds of meters away from him in a blink of eye. At the same time, the shock wave from her movement slammed into Hackzord and the Parasitic Eye Demons like a wall. The spell blast glistened and rippled outwards before slowly easing away.

After the witch flew out a distance and slowed to a stop, she looked like she used up over half of her energy.

He harrumphed and then chased her once more!

He planned to close the distance in one step again, however this time just as he exited the Distortion Door, the witch was already miles away, leaving a trail of white clouds behind her.

Hackzord was furious. He used his ability for the third time, thinking that he might as well open the door three hundred meters in front of the witch.

However when he exited the door this time, he suddenly felt the gazes of numerous eyes on him. It was as if he just entered a city center from an empty plain.

Shocked, the Sky Lord looked in the direction of where he felt the gazes—numerous black figures were coming in his direction, both from the horizon of the sea and from the land. Among them were iron birds and witches.

This is…a planned ambush?

So that b*tch was intentionally stopping and starting, fooling him believe that she could only perform brief moments of accelerated flight because she was being limited by her magical power?

“Ha… humans… hahaha…”

Hackzord laughed as his fury rapidly boiled up to its limit.

Not only did they outwit his troops, they were also planning to trick him?

Retreating now would be as easy as taking a breath.

But he didn’t do so.

Indeed, he wasn’t a Magic Slayer and it always bothered him, but that didn’t mean males wearing God’s Stones of Retaliation would be able to defeat a grand lord!

He had to let his enemies know who the real ruler of the sky was!

In an instant, eight iron birds had already charged towards him, spitting out streaks of fire from their heads—

Hackzord waved his left hand, directly opening a Distortion Door at his side, swallowing the iron bolts that shot at him; at the same time he opened the other side of the door beside the iron birds. After the fatal iron bolts passed through the door they swept straight back towards where they came from. In an instant, several iron birds were struck and their formation fell into a disarray.

But what surprised him a bit was that the iron bolts which were supposed to be fatal didn’t cause the iron birds to break apart; instead, they only left a few dents in their iron bodies.

The Sky Lord quickly pushed his surprise to the back of his mind and made a stride to a higher place, putting the entire battle area under his feet. The iron birds were clearly unable to follow his pace. As much as they tried to climb up, their stupid and clumsy bodies were slower than worms.

Just as he was planning to rip them apart one by one, a passing bird suddenly transformed into a devilbeast and propelled towards him with its jaws wide open!

His Eye Demons hadn’t regarded the birds that were commonly seen at sea as threats at all. Hackzord dodged abruptly, just avoiding the attack in time. Fuming, he widened his palm and a black streak of light instantly appeared in the space between them. This was also a Distortion Door, except it’s width was only a finger thick, any body that passed through would not emerge in one piece.

As if it realized that it was in danger, the devilbeast shrank back into a seabird. But it was too difficult to stop its momentum in such a short amount of time, and half its wings swept through the black line. The sliced wing tip and feathers burst apart like blossoms.

But before he could attack again, a thunderous roar erupted once more.

The golden-haired witch turned into a streak of golden light and shot straight towards him! Not having enough time to use the same tactic, Hackzord could only gather all the magical energy in his body and turn it into a shield cocooning his entire body!

“Bang!”

The two collided, and the immense impact caused the witch’s golden light to shatter into innumerable small pieces and raised a feeling of stuffiness in Hackzord. The opponent’s injury was clearly more serious; not only was blood seeping from the edge of her mouth, one of her arms was bent into multiple sections. Yet the witch thought nothing of her injuries. With her remaining hand, she pulled out a short fire fork from her waist.

Damn!

Left with no other choice, Hackzord opened another Distortion Door. If she was going to shoot, the iron bolt would be directed towards her companions.

But what infuriated Hackzord was that not only had the previous attack been a guise, the witch didn’t shoot anything at him but accelerated downwards to catch the falling seabird.

“I’m going to smash you all into pieces!” he roared for the first time in this battle.

But at this moment, the highest-priority warning rang inside the Sky Lord’s mind—the source came from a large iron bird that was in the clouds below him. Through the Eye Demons’ view, the source was indeed the witch that Ursrook made sure to point out as a key target.

He felt his body being latched on by something—

Feeling an increasing sense of crisis, Hackzord expanded the Distortion Door to its biggest range, covering his enemy’s entire attacking range!

One of his Eye Demons violently pushed him.

There was a flash of fire. After what felt like both a long time and a brief moment, a black shadowy cluster flashed across like lightning. Innumerable cracks appeared on the Distortion Door and then it shattered apart in a deafening explosion like glass.

After the door, the next victim was the Eye Demon that pushed him aside—the blue light on its body pulsated and blood, flesh, and organs squirted outwards, raising a wave of blue fog among the lingering shattered pieces. The two events occurred almost simultaneously, so quick that Hackzord couldn’t react.

Finally, it was his turn.

Even though the attacking God’s stone had already shattered, it still sliced away half of his hand, leaving multiple dents in his armor. The turbulence in his magical power caused him to lose control of his body, and he fell straight towards the ocean.

The iron birds, having finished redirecting themselves, surged straight towards him.

After he left the Forbidden Area, Hackzord used the last of his energy and opened a new door below him.

Then, as if he had fallen into a bottomless pit, he vanished above the ocean.

Chapter 1311: Loss

Translator: Henyee Translations Editor: Henyee Translations

“My lord…” When Siacis saw the Sky Lord once more, he almost couldn’t believe his eyes.

The Sky Lord was soaked from head to toe, as if he had just been scooped out of a pool of water. He was exhausted, injured and one half of his armor was splattered with blue blood. It looked as if he had just experienced a dreadful battle.

The Parasitic Eye Demons that were supposed to be by the Sky Lord’s side had disappeared. Being vigilant creatures with the sharpest reflexes, Eye Demons were only useful if they were next to the grand lord. The current situation would only suggest that some great misfortune had befallen the Eye Demons.

The scene before his eyes would be more understandable if their enemy had been the Sky-sea Realm; however, their opponents were only the lowlifes—mere humans.

Hackzord was in no mood to explain it to him. He grabbed his subordinate in one hand and dragged him into the Distortion Door.

In the next moment, they had already returned to the region of Red Mist.

“Sky Lord, the soldiers on the island—”Siacis reacted to the situation very quickly. His expression couldn’t help but change for the worse. Even though the unexpected explosion in the city caused great losses in their vanguard troops, there was still a portion that luckily managed to survive. Leaving like this was equivalent to abandoning them all on Archduke Island.

The troops carried a limited amount Red Mist with them and they could only hold up for a few days at most.

“I’m already unable to open another door.” Hackzord’s response made the high-level psychic shut his mouth. The value of Primal Demons was far below a grand lord no matter what the circumstances; there was no need for discussion when deciding between the two.

“I’ll escort you back to the Sky City then.”

“First tell Totolock to get the humans to send our vanguard troops back with sailboats, as many as they can. As for those Symbiotic Demons, let them hide on the island for how,” the Sky Lord spoke through gritted teeth. “Once the Red Mist has enveloped the entire Archduke Island, the main troops must immediately launch attack on Sedimentation Bay and the other places. You two will be responsible for the warfare!”

“My lord, isn’t it a bit hasty to do so?” Siacis asked with surprise. “It wouldn’t be too late if we started once you have recuperated—”

“This is my command, so say no more!”

“Yes, I have overstepped my boundaries.” Siacis hastily nodded his head. “As you wish!”

Gazing at his subordinate’s figure as he left, Hackzord viciously clenched his remaining hand into a fist.

How could he not be aware that what he was doing was hasty? But it was better than dragging it out with the humans. For the first time, the Sky Lord realized that time was not on their side. The humans’ absorption of their legacies was faster than he had imagined; within a year, just relying on a few witches and some magically-inert males they managed to threaten a grand lord. What would it be like after a few more years then?

They definitely couldn’t give humans any more time to catch their breath!

The Western Front must be steered back onto the right track!

Several days later, Hackzord finally returned to the bottom of the great rupture. The place had already become filled with rich and dense Red Mist. Just by virtue of his presence, he could feel his spirit being rejuvenated and the piercing pain in his palm lessening.

He went straight to the Red Mist Pond which was located at the bottommost point of Birth Tower.

Staring at the still motionless Nightmare Lord, the Sky Lord suddenly felt angry at everything. If she hadn’t been immersed in the Realm of Mind all this time then he wouldn’t be in such a difficult position!

It wasn’t supposed to be like this!

If he was focused on simply moving the troops around, the advancement of the frontline wouldn’t have been so slow, and if the Nightmare Lord lead the troops to battle, none of the Graycastle people who were meeting up with the fugitives would have escaped! Then, they would have launched a direct attack while the humans were still panicking, and he would have lead the troops from the west side in a pincer attack, capturing Hermes Plateau immediately—that was the real Western Front battle plan!

Furious as he was, when the moment came that he was really about to pull the Nightmare Lord out of the Realm of Mind, hesitation flickered across Hackzord’s face.

In the end, the Nightmare lord was the person he always looked up to in the past.

He even… even once thought, that the Nightmare Lord would become sovereign of the race.

No, no, no… Hackzord shook his head. He was utterly loyal to the King; those were only his ignorant thoughts when they were participating in the upgrading process. In terms of ranking, Nightmare was essentially no different to Hackzord now.

At most… she just had a slightly deeper understanding of the Realm of Mind.

He made up his mind.

His actions might harm the Nightmare Lord’s memory, making her furious and it might even cut off all the clues to the mystery of the humans’ upgrading, but these things paled in importance as the battle on the Western Front.

At worst he would simply have to stand on Silent Disaster’s side during the Holy See meeting, and admit that Upgrade Theory was correct. As for where that legacy shard came from, he could study that after they won. As long he could swallow the humans’ legacy shard, then everything they held in their hands at the moment would turn into a stair that advanced their entire race a step further!

With this in his mind, Hackzord inhaled deeply and made a violent pushing motion towards the Nightmare Lord.

The magical power in his palms broke off the connection between the Realm of Mind and the Nightmare Lord, pulling her out from the Fountain of Magic—

In theory, that was what was supposed to happen.

Yet Nightmare didn’t open her eyes, her body fell down to one side like a empty shell in the Red Mist Pond.

Hackzord instantly felt as if fear gripped his throat!

He had never felt this much terror, even when his mind was almost destroyed at the loss of control over his magic during his upgrading process, or when he was ambushed by the Sky-sea Realm!

He stepped forward, lifted the Nightmare Lord up and tried to catch her consciousness, but only found emptiness…

Being alive but forever in deep sleep—this was the characteristic of being lost in the Realm of Mind. Yet once one had been submerged in that never-ending red sea, returning was impossible. Even if one could maintain lucidity for a moment, it would eventually be eroded by the surrounding surging and chaotic consciousnesses and become a part of them eventually.

Hackzord’s heart dropped to his feet.

This meant that they had already lost the Nightmare Lord!

How could this happen?

With the Nightmare Lord’s ability, as long as one was careful and didn’t make any terrible mistakes, she shouldn’t go to the extent of being trapped in the Realm of Mind!

What on earth did she encounter in her search?

The Sky Lord didn’t dare to think any more about it. He got up and leaped upwards towards the top of the tower, he had even forgotten about his own injury.

He must inform the King of the news immediately.

The situation of the Western Front has changed dramatically!

*******************

“How is everyone recovering?”

At the Cage Mountain command post, Iron Axe asked Agatha in a concerned tone.

“With Nana here, what could go wrong?” Agatha put away her Sigil of Listening and smilingly shook her head. It was obvious that she was in a great mood. “According to Wendy, Maggie had already healed up so much that she could skip and jump about on the first day, Lightning recovered completely on the second day and both are now doing frontline patrolling. My only regret is that I didn’t participate in the ambush this time.”

“We were taking a big risk after all… Moreover, in order to pack that huge flintlock, we even had to take apart all the seats on the “Seagull.” We couldn’t have taken another passenger.” Iron Axe smiled as well. “I thought your only regret would be that we couldn’t get rid of that high-ranking demon in one go.”

“Winning against a grand lord with such a lineup is already an extraordinary victory.” Agatha turned to the Pearl of the Northern Region and said with her hand to her chest. “I underestimated you in the past; reality has proved that that was indeed a mistake—except for His Highness, Roland, there are still many outstanding people among those with no magical ability that should not be taken lightly.”

Edith calmly accepted her compliment. As the strategist behind the entire ambush, there was no need to be humble in that moment.

“Even though it’s a pity that we let the bastard called Hackzord escape alive, we reaped a lot from this battle.” She patted the documents in her hand. “At least we are now no longer clueless about our enemy.”

Chapter 1312: Countermeasure

Translator: Henyee Translations Editor: Henyee Translations

As a grand demon lord, the Sky Lord’s strength could indeed be described as terrifying. The magical ability to open a portal through space allowed for instantaneous movement, and could simultaneously be used as a shield or a weapon. However, through careful analysis, one would discover that it was not without flaws.

“We can first be certain that this high-level demon can only open one passage at a time and the entrance of the passageway must be within arm’s reach,” Edith said. “Secondly, although it’s difficult to ascertain the range of the portal, it must be at least over two kilometers.”

“Sounds like the advanced version of Orbit’s ability.”

After spending a lot of time with Roland, Edith learned from him several strange pet phrases that he liked to use, for example: “advanced version”, “special advanced version”, “enhanced advanced version”, etc.

“Just by looking at the range that indeed seems to be the case.” The Pearl of the Northern Region nodded. “However the number of passages Orbit creates depends on the amount of magic she has. The Sky Lord, on the other hand, can only open a new passage once the previous one has been closed. He was in a very tight situation at the time so it’s unlikely that he wasn’t using his true ability. This information is vital because it determines the essence of our countermeasure against him—if the Sky Lord could use multiple passages at once, the situation would be a hundred times more complicated.”

After the other two digested her words, she continued on and said, “Another important point is that even though he can easily expand and shrink the passage entrance and exit ways, Hackzord must be standing nearby the door in order to maintain them. According to Miss Sylvie’s observations, he spent several seconds closing the large Distortion Door when the explosion occurred on Archduke Island before flying to the south side of the island.”

“This means… the larger the door the door he opens, the slower it is to close it?” Iron Axe said thoughtfully.

“It’s very likely that this is the case.” Edith said, spreading her hands. “The final point is his Achilles heel—Hackzord isn’t a Magic Slayer; he cannot stop the movements of witches and doesn’t pose enough of a threat to people wearing God’s Stone of Retaliation. Even though his body is not weaker than that of Extraordinaries, he will be trapped in anti-magic regions if he engages in close combat. I certainly don’t think he will want to not sacrifice his own life in exchange for the lives of two or three mere humans.”

Edith paused. “To summarize, the Sky Lord’s main ability is to open a two-way passageway that is centered around himself, has a radius of several kilometers and can only be opened one at a time. No matter if it is the entrance or the exit, as long as both sides of the door are affected by a God’s Stone, the passage will break apart.”

“So if he appears once again, our countermeasure will be…”

“If he is located at the periphery of the battlefield and the exit of the door isn’t facing the battlefield, Miss Sylvie will directly bombard him with artillery,” Edith said systematically. “If the exit of the door is inside the battlefield, or if he uses the door to directly charge into the First Army’s formation, then get the soldiers to do nothing and leave it to the professionals.”

“Do nothing?” Iron Axe was a little surprised, then, as if he realized her meaning, he said, “…oh I see.”

“Indeed,” Edith revealed a smile, “In reality the Sky Lord’s most effective method of attack is using our own weapons against ourselves. If our soldiers can hold their attack, there is actually a limit to the threat he poses to our lineup—just as I said before; strategically, his ability is irreplaceable for maneuvering troops, but using it to attack is not a good idea.”

With the frontline of the First Army ignoring him, it was not like the grand lord could just charge into the ditch and engage in close combat with the soldiers. If he did that, then when the professionals—God’s Punishment Witches, arrived on the battlefield, his death would be inevitable.

“What if he counterattacks during the intervals between artillery fire?” Agatha asked after a moment of thought. “For example, he first opens a passage to the outside, making us think that he was gathering more troops, and when our artillery fires he opens a new large door and positions the exit inside our battleground, subjecting us to our own artillery fire.”

Just from being able to think of this was enough to prove that the Ice Witch had put a lot of work into Graycastle’s new weapons.

“This is indeed something that could work in theory; however, I don’t believe the Sky Lord will do that,” Edith explained. “Opening a door for only one person can be done in a blink of an eye, but expanding it so wide so that it would completely protect him would need time. The time difference between the two is very limited and if it fails, the result would be being blasted into pieces by the shells that have fallen behind him. To a grand lord, such a move is too risky.”

“All in all, I can take it that the Sky Lord is not as much as a threat to the frontline as we thought, right?” Iron Axe said while rubbing his chin.

“So far that is the conclusion that the General Staff have reached.” Edith gave a definite reply. “Of course, this only applies if Hackzord leads troops into battle by himself. If he was accompanied by other grand lords, then the threat he poses will instantly multiply dramatically.”

—Like bringing Ursrook along and directly charging into the middle of their battle formation.

Iron Axe and Agatha couldn’t help but heave a sigh of relief. Luckily, Ursrook had already died in the Fertile Plains.

“But this doesn’t rule out the possibility of a new Magic Slayer appearing; so if it’s possible, it’ll be best if we find a chance to rid ourselves of this problem.” There was a hint of murderous intent in the Pearl of the Northern Region’s tone.”He will only be no threat to us when he disappears completely.”

Upon hearing this, Agatha couldn’t help but feel impressed. Not only was a ‘mortal’ seemingly showing no fear towards a demon, but she was also plotting the death of a grand demon lord. What would have definitely sounded delusional in the past didn’t sound strange at all to anyone at the current moment, as if it was the logical and obvious thing to do.

Over the past four hundred years, humans had indeed changed a lot.

Whether it be people or things.

Perhaps the Union’s silence wasn’t all together a bad thing.

At least, they didn’t pass down the fear of the strong from their era to this era.

Now that she thought of it, there might as well have been many normal people possessing potential like Edith Kant in the Union’s time, but the pessimistic views and fear that pervaded the race restricted their thoughts and willpower. Together with the estrangement intentionally created by the upper classes, the era was very bleak on the whole.

But this time, before humans had gotten the chance to taste real hopelessness, Roland Wimbledon curbed its spreading.

As she was feeling a surge of emotions, she once more recalled the moment when she woke up from deep sleep in the Frozen Coffin, and met Roland for the first time.

“Mortals can also defeat demons”. Everything started from those words…

“Hackzord probably won’t fall for the same trick twice, do you have a good plan?” Iron Axe asked.

“As long as the First Army’s movements are flexible enough, even if we don’t set a trap, we still have the chance to get rid of him—for example, equipping ‘Fire of Heaven’ with a large caliber weapon that can shoot God’s Stones.”

“True,” the commander in chief mused. “But that would need quite a lot of God’s Stones. Don’t tell me you have already thought of a way to process God’s Stones?”

“How could that be possible.”

“Huh?”

Edith shrugged. “I’m the chief of the General Staff, not god. I’m alright at making suggestions but as for how to realize them, that will obviously be up to His Highness, Roland, to figure out. Relax, I’ve written everything in the battle report. In order for the frontline to achieve victory, he should be doing his best as well.”

The other two people couldn’t help but twitch their mouths.

It appears like His Highness’s white hairs… are going to increase again.

Chapter 1313: The Information Age

Translator: Henyee Translations Editor: Henyee Translations

In Graycastle, Neverwinter.

The reports regarding the battle on Archduke Island as well as the situation in the Kingdom of Wolfheart were delivered into Roland’s hands two days later.

Compared to the past when it took a week to send a letter from the City of Evernight to Neverwinter, it was undeniable that their communication speed had made huge progress. Both short-distance, quick delivery by flying couriers and long distance delivery through twenty-four hour steam-powered boats were now a part of the messaging system. There were dedicated personnel and boats responsible for the delivery of crucial messages, and in some cases even planes were used. This time, the reports were delivered by Tilly.

“Good job.” Roland solicitously handed her a Chaos Drink. “Is the situation over there okay?

“Wouldn’t you know if you just looked at the report?” Tilly took the cup and glanced at him sideways. “For you to act so considerate, do you have something you are guilty of? Could it be that you still don’t have a clue about my plane?”

“Pfft…” The sound of Nightingale stifling laughter came from behind him.

“How could that be, I’ve already selected the best model from many blueprints. When Anna can find some time, we will start the prototype production right away.”

“For Anna’s sake, I’ll let you off this time, Brother.” Tilly downed the drink in one go, wiped her lips and walked towards the exit of the office, “‘Seagull’ will be heading back soon so I’ll be returning to the Aerial Knight Academy first.”

“You’re not even going to stay for one day?” he asked, slightly surprised.

“I have no choice. Right now the only things on the frontline that can threaten the Sky Lord are ‘Seagull’ and Andrea. Also… I don’t want to miss a single opportunity to get my revenge.” Tilly waved at Roland with her back facing him. “Well then, I’ll be going now, Brother.”

Nightingale sighed softly as she gazed at the closed door. “Everyone… is working hard.”

If it was possible, I would rather they worked hard in other areas, not in warfare , Roland thought. However he didn’t say it out loud—because before the Battle of Divine Will ended, before the fate of humans was determined, nobody could free themselves of this burden. Apart from shirking responsibility, there was no meaning in saying this now.

After a moment of silence, he unsealed the report.

After he finished reading all the reports, Roland at last understood the meaning behind Tilly’s words. To be able to pass down the evacuation command in time and successfully ambush a grand demon lord whose movements were untraceable above the vastness of the sea was an incredible feat. Edith Kant and Andrea were undeniably the key contributors to the battle. But in the same way, the sender of the vital intel couldn’t be ignored—victory would not have been possible without this person’s selfless act.

“What do you plan on doing?” The issue had clearly caught Nightingale’s attention.

“No matter what his original motive for sending out the secret letter was, his name and contributions shouldn’t be forgotten,” Roland said in a low voice. If this was in Roland’s previous life, finding an unidentified informer after a long, drawn-out battle would be virtually impossible. The words on the epigraph of the gravestone would likely be: “Your name is unknown; however, your deeds are everlasting.” Here, the existence of witches changed this. They allowed every single warrior who contributed to saving the fate of humankind have their name remembered in history. “After the First Army regains control of the Kingdom of Everwinter, get ‘Black Money’ to help Summer determine this person’s name and background.”

If the culprit who murdered him was still alive by then, they would not escape severe punishment by law.

Nightingale nodded. “If only we can quickly create the communications equipment that extends over thousands of miles that you spoke of.”

“Unfortunately that is not one of my strengths.” Roland couldn’t help but rub his forehead. Recalling the circuit diagram that he had been forced to memorize made his head throb.

“Now you finally understand my feelings during an exam,” Nightingale said with her hand to her mouth.

“Hard as it is, I’m at the very l east not like a certain someone who simply falls asleep on the table and hands in an empty test at the end.” Roland glared at her. “I’ve actually almost done creating the prototype.”

Indeed, although extremely slow, the radio communications project had never stopped.

Like the piston engine, after considering numerous designs proffered by the Design Bureau of Graycastle, he decided to select two among them and have them worked on simultaneously.

These two were the spark-gap transmitter and the amplitude-modulated transmitter.

The spark-gap transmitter was the father of telecommunication. Its design was extremely simple and didn’t need any electronic components. All that was needed was a transformer coil to step up the voltage to charge the capacitor until the voltage in the capacitor was large enough to ionize the air and produce an electric spark. This part was similar to a lighter, except the current discharged by the spark would not be wasted and instead, would oscillate rapidly back and forth between the plates of the capacitor through the inductor and spark gap, creating electromagnetic waves. Finally, these electromagnetic waves would be transmitted through an antenna.

In other words, as long as one could control the switch of the power source, intermittent electromagnetic waves could be sent out, and by listening to the duration of the sounds, receivers could translate them into the corresponding signal. The beeps of varied lengths of telegraph codes originated from this principle.

Although it still sounded a little confusing, Roland took the most ingenious approach, which was to have the radio communications team at the Design Bureau of Graycastle to build a machine that worked with readily available materials, and then copy it.

For example, if you place a piece of oiled paper between two pieces of tin foil and then seal it with wax, it becomes a basic high-voltage capacitor.

The inductor would be even easier to make. It was nothing more than a coil of wire wound round and round an insulated pipe.

When not taking mass production or specifications into consideration, Roland could complete the device by himself. Although compared to the industrial products that came in a package the size of a fingernail in his previous life, these devices would appear bulky and crude, but the effects were basically the same. After the construction of the launch tower was completed, he would be able to perform the first wireless transmitting experiment of the era.

However, the shortcomings of a spark-gap transmitter were also very obvious.

Even if it passed the trials, he would have to design a code that matched the language of his kingdom if he wanted to use it officially. Training senders and receivers would also require a lot of time. Also the spark-gap transmitter had an extremely wide frequency spectrum so only one transmitter could work within a particular region. It wasn’t suitable for the intelligence personnel to use on the frontlines.

Thus, his ultimate goal was still to use an amplitude-modulated transmitter (AM transmitter) that amplifies a signal using a vacuum tube.

The biggest advantage of the AM transmitter was that it could directly transmit voice signals.

In principle, radio and telephones were very similar in nature. Both transform the oscillations of sound into the changes in current or electromagnetic waves. After these travelled over long distances to the receiver’s location, it would be turned back into sound once more. The only thing was that the frequency of the human voice was too low, causing the wavelength of the signal wave to be too long. The longer the wavelength, the larger the required antenna size—if the voice signals were directly transmitted, the length of the antenna would be over a hundred kilometers. This would be something impossible to create with their construction capabilities.

So in order to send out the voice signal, it would have to be carried by a higher-frequency wave.

This was where ‘modulation’ came in.

Once the new wave form created by the combination of the two was received, the receiver had to filter out the high-frequency waves through a series of demodulations and only keep the meaningful low-frequency waves in order to turn it into the final sound of the voice.

Once the AM transmitter succeeded, both the First Army and the intelligence community would be granted with real-time communications capabilities.

For war, the significance of this required no explanation.

Chapter 1314: Dilemma

Translator: Henyee Translations Editor: Henyee Translations

Of course, the difficulty of producing the two types of radio communications equipment was not on the same level. The engineering team was still in the process of trying to create the evacuated tube, the core part of the AM transmitter.

Failed prototypes had already piled into a small mountain outside the lab.

Edith’s suggestion of modifying ‘Fire of Heaven’ in her report excited Roland. On the technical level, it was not difficult to move a thirty-five millimeter sniper cannon onto a biplane. All they had to do was embed the entire body of the cannon below the belly of the plane and remove the shooting seats. If they limited the ammunition they carried to less than ten rounds, the weight would be balanced out. Other than that, nothing needed to be changed.

The problem was that if they wanted to acquire large-caliber God’s Stone bullets, they had to first use witch or demon blood to melt and separate God’s Stones in the mine until they formed God’s Stones of Retaliation in the desired size and shape. Only then could they be subjected to further processing. If the stones were too big, the blades and lathes they had at hand wouldn’t be able to do anything about it. If they were too small, the God’s Stones would be too brittle. The process of selecting base materials expended large amounts of magic blood. Even if the Witch Alliance and the Sleeping Spell supported him, the amount they had would not be enough to satisfy the requirements of war.

The real solution to this problem was in the demons.

Either they found out the reason why demons could process such large God’s Stone pillars…

…Or they used their blood for creating the bullets.

‘Fire of Heaven’ could now return to Neverwinter from the frontline within a day. With the additional help of Agatha’s refrigeration ability, directly transporting fresh demon blood from the battlefield didn’t seem impossible.

Roland silently recorded his idea onto the agenda.

…

When it was nightfall, Roland followed his custom of entering the Dream World.

In order to accelerate the advancement of the Design Bureau of Graycastle’s projects, Roland had dramatically increased the amount of times he entered the Dream World in the past month, causing time in the Dream World which had been falling behind the real world to catch up a fair amount. The city which had previously been in late summer now already had snowflakes floating about, as if this place and the outside belonged to the same world but just in different regions.

A typical morning in the neighborhood of his apartment was bustling with people. The expansion of Erosion and the great disaster in the Prism City didn’t affect the residents at all; the two sides of the street were still full of breakfast food stalls with owners yelling about their sales without rest. People hurriedly moved about the street and the white snow that had accumulated throughout the night was already covered in footprints.

Even though Lan said that this world was also going to face a Battle of Divine Will, in comparison to the Red Mist-covered battlefield in the Kingdom of Wolfheart, this place was undeniably milder by a good deal.

Also, the long time he spent in the Dream World had not only caused the seasons to change, the demon world-traveller’s attitude had also appeared to change significantly.

After observing for some time, Roland was basically certain that the demon who called herself Valkries was not actually a native from Cargarde Peninsula. Although the registration information restored by the Martialist Association verified it, there was no such person among the visiting group from the Peninsula. Yet, her behavior was difficult to explain with common sense.

Roland was not alien to the phenomenon of possessing a real identity but a greatly changed personality because he himself was an example of this. The best explanation was to describe her as a “world traveller”.

In the beginning Valkries was able to maintain her guise of a normal martial artist, flipping through various different types of books and talking as little as possible. But with the passing of time, she became more and more agitated.

Especially after her injuries healed. Once, she secretly sneaked deep into the forbidden area of Prism City and stood silently and attentively in front of the Erosion rupture. According to Dawnen’s report, at the time there was an evident expression of anxiety on Valkries’ face, as if she was yearning for something. Dawnen even thought on multiple occasions that Valkries would leap into the Erosion, but in the end Valkries stopped herself from doing so.

It would be too much to claim that her actions were her mourning of her companions’ deaths, because Valkries didn’t stop for a single moment when the visiting group encountered danger; in fact, she was aiming for the Erosion from the very beginning.

If he thought about it from her perspective, it wasn’t hard to understand the change in her attitude.

At the start, coming to this modern metropolis from the Demon city, she might had been able to keep her composure in order to figure out where she was. But the more time passed while her hope of returning still obscure as ever, it was unavoidable for anxiety to begin building. This might have been the real reason why Valkries sneaked into Prism city. She wanted to see if she could return to the world familiar to her through the chasm she arrived in.

Unfortunately, the memory fragment did not satisfy her desires.

No matter what, being able to disguise herself to this point was an incredibly difficult feat. After all, Valkries didn’t know that her every move was being watched by Dawnen. If it wasn’t for the small things that betrayed her when she was by herself, there was not a single flaw from the way she interacted with other martial artists that would give her away.

When Roland considered what would have happened if he were in her shoes, he thought that he definitely could not have achieved this.

Now that her identity had been confirmed, he had to think about what to do next.

At this moment, he received a SMS on his phone.

It was from Phyllis.

“Your Majesty, everyone is ready.”

Roland put his phone back into in his pocket, turned and walked towards the living room.

Zero was busy carrying a bowl of egg noodles onto the meal table. Upon seeing Roland, she put her hands to her hips and said, “Uncle, you haven’t forgotten what you promised me, have you?”

“What, you woke up so early because you were afraid that I would sneak off?”

“It’s not the first time you’ve done that after all,” she said, pouting.

“Relax, I definitely won’t this time.” Roland laughed, walked over and patted her head. “Let’s eat breakfast first, afterwards we’ll go next door, call Sister Garcia and then set off together.”

Apart from New Years, the biggest event this winter was the Martial Arts Contest which occured once every four years. To all the junior high school students throughout the city, whoever could watch it live on the arena would become the center of discussion. Zero, who usually had no interest for such contests, was no exception. After her ceaseless begging, Roland had no choice but to agree to take her near the arena to experience it live when the school’s winter break came.

There were guards supervising today’s competition and it was still in the round robin stage so it was unlikely for Fallen Evils to appear. Besides, Zero had to return to her hometown everytime the holidays came around, so he could hardly refuse the little girl’s ‘only request.’

Roland decided to confront that demon world traveller directly.

*******************

It was already the fourth month.

Although Valkries looked like she was focusing all her attention on the rowdy battle ring, her heart was somewhere else.

The past four months had given her a basic understanding of this world and human legacies. On some levels, she herself had become a part of accepting legacies. As long as she could return to reality, she would definitely be able to bring huge benefits to her race—however the major problem was, all this time, she hadn’t been able to find a way to leave the Realm of Mind.

Valkries had an enormous heap of intel, yet she didn’t have anyone to share it with. It was as if she was in a desert and finally found a bottle of water, only to find it firmly sealed, unable to be opened.

Whether she sent out a signal for help to Hackzord, or used her mind to sense traces of the King, she didn’t receive any reply. Even if she stood in the gap of this domain and meditated, the Realm of Mind didn’t respond to her call at all—it was her first time encountering such a situation.

Valkries couldn’t help but feel a little hateful towards the Sky Lord.

Why hadn’t he, even after all this time, tried to wake her up?

Chapter 1315: First Direct Contact

Translator: Henyee Translations Editor: Henyee Translations

If the Western Front plan was successful, the Red Mist should have already spilled over the ridge of the continent and spread through the territory of the humans.

This meant that the Birth Tower in the great rupture was no longer a secret. No matter how slow the opponent was, they would have reacted already. So why was Hackzord still not doing anything? Could it be that the humans were so weak that he could face them all by himself?

However, when she thought about it, Valkries found it unlikely. If their enemy were as frail as that, Ursrook wouldn’t have been defeated on the Fertile Plains.

She knew very clearly that having been separated from reality for too long, it had caused her to lose her ability to judge the current situation.

This feeling made the Nightmare Lord feel extremely uneasy.

There was also that human…

She looked over to the other side of the battle ring and saw that Roland was standing beside two females, showing much amusement and interest in the competition.

Damn him! Didn’t he have better things to do?

If he knew how a way out, then he might just be her only chance—he was definitely the one taking the legacies and knowledge of humans out of this world; he must have some sort of passage to communicate with the outside world.

As long as he left the Realm of Mind, she would have a chance to grab that opportunity, after all, in the King’s Presiding Holy See, she had often sensed the King’s communication with the territory. It was because she had such an ability that she dared to follow the fluctuations of the legacy shard’s power and enter the Realm of Mind to find Roland’s trail.

Yet, he had always remained active in this world and there was absolutely not a moment when he could have done anything.

Could it be that human monarchs have so much free time that they still didn’t need to do anything to manage their kingdoms’ matters even after several months? They would rather waste their time on a meaningless Martial Arts Contest than spend time reading a few more books. The only explanation was that the demons’ frontline was not giving the humans enough pressure.

So this is still all Hackzord’s fault!

In the midst of her mood swings, Valkries suddenly noticed Roland leaving the two females and walking to a corner by himself. Standing there was a hooded female as though she had been intentionally waiting for him.

Valkries pretended to casually walk out of the crowd, but her eyes never left Roland.

They discussed a few words before the female pointed in the direction of the exit. Roland appeared a little hesitant but nodded in the end.

Had the Association noticed something?

Valkries had originally decided to stop once and for all, but for some reason she felt a familiar aura from the female. This odd feeling prompted her to walk a few steps closer, so as to sneak at peek at them from a closer distance.

Just with this one glance, Valkries felt all her hair stand—under the dim light, she saw a face similar to to that of Heathtalese, or… Lan, from the Martialist Association!

Could it be that Transformer had always been hidden in this world?

And the reason that Roland could appear as a male in this world was also because of her?

This news was too shocking. Valkries could no longer hold back the impulse in her heart and quickly followed them.

Roland and the person that Valkries suspected to be Transformer didn’t walk in the direction of the arena’s exterior after passing through the exit passageway; instead, they turned and entered an underground parking lot. The Nightmare Lord tried to make her footsteps as light as possible and kept a fair distance between them until they entered a civil air defense passageway.

As Valkries tailed after them, she discovered that the passageway was only a bit over ten meters long and didn’t have any forks at all. On the other end of the passage was a sealed cement wall. There was even a “No Entry. Construction Incomplete” warning sign hung up on the wall. Even though it was a dead end, the two had vanished.

Oh no, it’s a trap!

Valkries reacted instantly but it was already too late.

Before she could turn and retreat, Roland was already calmly standing behind her, blocking her only route of escape. Standing beside him were several females. From how they used their abilities, which was polar opposite to martial artists, Valkries didn’t even need luck to guess.

Unquestionably, the females standing beside him were witches.

She finally realized where that feeling of familiarity came from. That was the miniscule difference between magic power and natural ability. If witches could enter the Realm of the Mind as well as possess their original strength at the same time, then the exposure of her identity would have occurred sooner or later.

After all, Roland could surreptitiously conceal this many people to set up an ambush. That meant infiltrating her surroundings and observing her would be trivial—the reason was easy to understand if one thought about it. She focused all of her disguise on her superficial interactions. But against witches who had uncanny abilities, her guise would have been a joke. It was likely that her movements had already been seen through by the witches in the past four months.

“We meet once more, Miss Valkries,” Roland said serenely.

Valkries didn’t respond.

Saying anything at this time would only bring humiliation to herself.

Even if she still didn’t understand how he could get the witches to enter this realm, it was no longer important.

He had intentionally set an ambush in this secluded place. His goal was self-evident.

The only thing she could do now was die in battle.

The Nightmare Lord summoned all the magic power in her body and slightly leaned her body forward. In this situation where she was fighting against a group of witches without a magic stone or Magic Slayer power, she didn’t even consider the possibility of winning. It was impossible for her to surrender no matter what!

“Could I invite you to drink some Cargarde Peninsula coffee?” Roland spoke once more.

“—” Valkries came to a halt with her foot out. She stood frozen in her spot, her upper body still maintaining a slightly forward-leaning posture. The way she stopped herself seemed overly stiff. “What… did you say?”

“I want to treat you to coffee,” Roland repeated himself. “Although it wouldn’t count as real coffee, it’s a special drink that is very similar.”

Valkries stared at him for a long time before voicing the confusion in her heart. “… Why?”

She couldn’t guess what this male was thinking at all—reality was different to this place, the coexistence of her race and humans was an imagined illusion. Since he had already confirmed her true origins, it wouldn’t make sense to let her off. If she was not going to be greeted by death, then it would only be an outcome worse than death.

“Because some things are better laid out in the open than hidden,” Roland said slowly, “especially when the ‘Battle of Divine Will’ is not the ‘Final Battle’ yet.”

The ‘Battle of Divine Will’… is not the ‘Final Battle’ yet…

Valkries couldn’t help but be surprised.

She never would have thought that she would hear something like this from a human.

It was only after a long period of silence that she regained her wary composure. “Where do you want to have the talk?”

“Not far from here, only a few minutes away.” Roland snapped his fingers, the sound of a car engine came from behind him. “Board the car, I’ve already booked a table.”

…

Roland didn’t lie to her.

The location he chose was a high-class restaurant situated inside a high-rise building. Sitting in front of the floor to ceiling glass windows, she could see the snow covered urban skyline. Soothing music filled the restaurant and the atmosphere was peaceful and elegant.

Valkries knew that choosing this place to discuss was Roland’s way of expressing his sincerity—if he had wanted to kill her, a public setting like this was certainly not a suitable execution ground.

Noticing the group of witches who were staring intently at them, she inhaled deeply after sitting down. “Why didn’t you just ask to meet me here directly?”

“That would waste too much time, I didn’t think you would agree straight away—when not being cornered, it’s easy for people to refuse and avoid, so it’s much easier to do it this way.” Roland shrugged. “Since we’ve already reached an initial understanding, then let’s get to our main point of discussion quickly. Honesty would benefit both of us. I am Roland Wimbledon, the King of Graycastle and one of the creators of the Dream World. You are?”

One of… the creators? Although she had already guessed that he wasn’t a simple visitor, his identity shocked Valkries greatly. This was her first time hearing that a territory in the Realm of Mind could be created by multiple people. But this may be why he couldn’t take complete control of this domain like the demon king could. Suppressing her impulse to ask who the others were, the Nightmare Lord slowly replied, “Valkries. That’s my name.”

“How about your title and rank? Like “Sky Lord” for example… could you be more specific?”

She paused for a moment. “Nightmare Lord, that is what I’m called.”

Roland spat out his drink.

This time it was Roland’s turn to be shocked.

Chapter 1316: History

Translator: Henyee Translations Editor: Henyee Translations

“What’s so strange about it?” Valkries said coldly, “Do you think anyone can just casually stroll into the Realm of the Mind? Or… are you actually just proud of yourself for capturing a grand lord?”

Clearly, she hadn’t abandoned her pride even if she was in a sticky situation. Roland even had a feeling that if he pushed her too much she would directly lunge at the witches and into her death.

But her title really did surprise him—he had only asked for her title out of procedure; after all, most high-ranking demons had their unique title, and a demon who could conduct a upgrading ceremony couldn’t be just some no-name entity. He just didn’t expect this demon’s identity to be far more complex than he had imagined.

Roland originally thought that Valkries was a consciousness that coincidentally escaped from the memory fragment, but now another possibility had risen to the surface—she could have come from the real world!

The name, “Nightmare Lord,” first appeared in Ursrook’s documents, and it was followed by a greeting, proving that the “Nightmare Lord” was not a historical figure, and was still active in the higher-ranks of demons. Additionally, Roland had repeatedly watched the memory fragment numerous times, he hadn’t heard any referral of her as a grand lord. If the demon language he learned from Kabradhabi was correct, this meant that the figure presiding over the rest at the time wasn’t a grand lord yet.

Combining Vakries’ statement that she “voluntarily entered the Realm of Mind” and the Pearl of the Northern Region’s analysis of the situation at the frontline, Roland was becoming increasingly certain that his latter theory was right!

In other words, the Valkries sitting in front of him had waded through at least eight hundred years of history. Her strength and knowledge had to be extremely rare among the demon race. If one counted her aberrant reaction to Lan, things went back even further. This type of discussion far exceeded the spirit that was copied from a memory fragment; even if they had not exchanged words at all, it was still equal to ruling out a grand lord ranked demon from the front line. Just this point alone had huge significance!

“I need to correct your words. First, I haven’t captured you—at least at the moment, you are free.” Roland pretended to be calm as he spoke. “Second, intruding the Dream World is your subjective behavior, I don’t think I have done anything wrong.”

“…” Valkries was speechless for a moment. Only after a long time did she stiffly release a sigh. “You call this place the Dream World?”

Pride made her find any humiliation intolerable, but at the same time, made her unable to make any illogical protest—her speechlessness from before confirmed the Nightmare Lord’s origin; she indeed came here voluntarily through the Realm of Mind.

“That’s because I find myself in here every time I fall asleep. So in a certain sense, it is no different from dreaming.”

“Absurdity!” Valkries growled. Opening up a territory in the Realm of Mind not only required talent, but it needed a high focus of spiritual energy and a will of steel in order not to lose oneself in the sea of magic power. In the end this magically-disabled male could do this just by taking a nap? That’s too unfair!

“Hello, this is your order, please enjoy.” At this moment, the waiter served their meals. The table was filled with various types of deserts and drinks, all of which looked mouth-watering.

“This is the truth.” After the waiter left, Rolant spread out his hands and said, “Just as I said before, honesty benefits the both of us. I would not go as far as to lie to you about something like this. Moreover, what I just said wasn’t the important point, the important point is the truth about the Battle of Divine Will… and the future of all races. He picked up his chopsticks and made a gesture for her to help herself. “We can talk about this while we eat.”

Valkries confirmed another point. This male was different to all the humans she had met before. Who talks about matters regarding the future of their entire race while eating? If it was another normal person, they would have most likely be extremely grave, as if they were facing a formidable enemy. But he didn’t seem like he was intentionally messing with her, as if to him, his behavior was completely normal.

She raised that cup of murky Peninsula coffee and took a sip.

In an instant, thick aromatic liquid slid down her throat.

It was actually… not bad.

For some reason, she suddenly had a feeling that she had just lost.

No, she must take control of the flow! Valkries forced herself to set down her cup and said in a low voice, “Where did you hear that the Battle of Divine Will was not the Final Battle?”

Roland dug out Lan’s photo from his wallet and put it on the table. “You’ve seen her before, right?”

As the picture of Lan which appeared in the video data left behind by the Reflection Church was likely one that happened before the establishment of the Union in terms of age, he intentionally got Ling to make herself look like Lan with makeup and see if the demon from the memory fragment made any reaction. Even though reality was a little different to what they expected, Valkries’ shock at the time proved that she had indeed seen Lan.

After a while the Nightmare Lord nodded. “Who exactly is she?”

“A traitorous Oracle.” Roland slowly described the secret discussion in the Rose Café to her.

After hearing those unbelievable words, even Valkries couldn’t help but widen her eyes and stutter, “Could it be that… the Oracle that my mentor mentioned was her?”

“Mentor?”

“‘Transformer’ Heathtalese, she taught me many things…” After hesitating for a few moments, Valkries revealed Cloud School’s past. “Her failure to upgrade caused the unstable School to lose their last measure of protection.”

“So it was… due to this…” Realization dawned on Roland. The intel of the two races was combined into one for the first time in history. He finally pieced everything together with the missing puzzle piece in his mind to reveal the full picture.

“Your Majesty, did you think of something?” Phyllis asked.

“Do you remember the portrait hanging on the wall at the meeting where the vow of the three queens took place in the Union?” Roland took a deep breath, ” I’m afraid the person in the portrait was the high-level demon called Heathtalese.”

“What did… you say?”

“The Union would enshrine the portrait of that demon?”

“How… could this be possible?” The Taquila witches all revealed expressions of disbelief.

“If we thought about it according to the influence the Cloud School had in the first Battle of Divine Will, something like this happening isn’t actually very strange. Since the demon in the school can become a grand lord, then it would have been normal for witches or normal people from the higher-ups to come from the school. I’m guessing that before Heathtalese died, she always had suspicions about the Battle of Divine Will, right?”

In certain people’s eyes, such behavior was equivalent to standing on the humans’ side.

“…I cannot deny that.” Valkries closed her eyes, “She and the current king have had conflict, but the tides of war isn’t something that one or two people can resist.”

“It is the same for humans,” Roland said calmly. “The disbanded Cloud School is at most a cherished memory to people now, and when the outbreak of the second Battle of Divine Will comes, even this memory will cease to exist. That period of their history is not recorded in any scripts. It is highly likely that that the Three Chiefs destroyed all records—a past where they coexisted with demons would make people hopeful, especially when the situation is bad, it would only eat away at humans’ determination to resist, so the Cloud School must be forgotten as an undesired blemish!”